Chapter 1713 – Climbing the Divine Seal Altar

The 33 stone platforms each resonated with each other like chords of music in a strange sympathetic harmony. Countless runes flashed and wove together, stretching to the ends of time, emitting a fearful, heart-stopping pressure.

Compared to this massive Divine Seal Altar, the largest mountain in the fourth level was nothing but a little stone.

It was like every step of this Divine Seal Altar was its own ancient world.

However, what shocked Lin Ming the most was that he could faintly see large phantoms on every step. The aura of Laws emitting from these phantoms were all different, but they fused together flawlessly with the Great Dao Laws of the stone platforms, perfectly harmonious.

As for the peak of the Divine Seal Altar, the giant space crack there released endless beams of energy and arcs of lighting. The flashes of light carried with them a terrifying strength, one able to tear through space and reach into the far off distances.

Giant tornados emerged from the pitch black abyss that had been dug out from the earth. The surrounding martial artists found it hard to remain steady.

“Divine Seal Altar… it’s really the Divine Seal Altar…”

Lin Ming could already confirm that every step of the 33 levels of this Divine Seal Altar contained different Laws. It could be said that within this entire vast world, the only one who possessed the ability to create something so magnificent was the Asura Road Master.

But what about Empyrean Divine Seal’s Divine Seal Altar?

Could it be that… Empyrean Divine Seal was the Asura Road Master’s reincarnation within the Divine Realm?

Lin Ming immediately thought. The Asura Road Master had reincarnated 33 times. One life one Empyrean, one life one Divinity. According to the preface of the Asura Sutra, the Asura Road Master had used 100 million years during each reincarnation to become a True Divinity powerhouse. Afterwards, he had fused all 33 reincarnations together and surpassed the boundaries of a True Divinity.

If this were true, then Empyrean Divine Seal was unlikely to be the Asura Road Master’s reincarnation. This was because the Asura Road Master had lived 10 billion years ago. 10 billion years ago… that was a time when ancient races filled the universe, each one striving for supremacy. At that time, the Asura Road Master should have already experienced his 33 reincarnations and established the Asura Road.

As for Empyrean Divine Seal, he had only existed 3.6 billion years ago. During that era, the three races of humans, saints, and spiritas ruled the 33 Heavens. The difference in time was far too great.

Moreover, Empyrean Divine Seal was a tragic story. He seemed to have perished because of humanity’s calamity. If he really was the reincarnation of the Asura Road Master then perhaps he wouldn’t have died saving humanity.

Even his Divine Seal Altar seemed to have shattered. The reason Empyrean Vast Universe had been able to create an imitation of the Divine Seal Altar was because he had obtained a fragment of the True Divine Seal Altar. Otherwise, Lin Ming wouldn’t have seen the phantom of Empyrean Divine Seal when he climbed up the 33 steps of the Divine Seal Altar.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming came up with his own hypothesis. 3.6 billion years ago, Empyrean Divine Seal should also have come to the final trial, and he saw this same scene as he tried to go from the fourth level to the fifth. After climbing the 33 steps, Empyrean Divine Seal had relied upon the comprehensions he obtained here to create his own Divine Seal Altar.

Afterwards, that Divine Seal Altar became one of Empyrean Divine Seal’s lifetime magic weapons.

Lin Ming found it hard to keep his calm. He never thought that 3.6 billion years ago, Empyrean Divine Seal also climbed up this ancient 33 step altar.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and turned his head to look at Soul Empress Sheng Mei. He only saw her staring at the Divine Seal Altar, he eyes shining with a splendid light as she too found it hard to remain calm. From her expression, this was clearly the first time she had seen the Divine Seal Altar.

The tests one faced in the final trial were ever changing and not every situation would be identical. During the last final trial that Soul Empress Sheng Mei attended, she had probably experienced something else when she went from the fourth level to the fifth.

“What large stone steps! Are we supposed to crawl our way up?”

Many martial artists were left utterly speechless as they stared at the incomparably gigantic Divine Seal Altar.

“It looks like that’s what we will have to do. It’s impossible to reach the fifth level by flying. We’ll have to crawl up, and this stone altar doesn’t look easy to crawl up at all.”

“Heh, every trial from here on out is far, far harder. Let’s rush up and get as much as we can completed!”

Many martial artists looked at each other, their resolves steeled. It wasn’t easy for many of them to arrive this far. As for the fifth level of the final trial, that would undoubtedly be far more difficult than the fourth!

Unless there was some major upset, they would likely be stopped here.

“Go!”

For a time, numerous trial challengers shot up towards the Divine Seal Altar, climbing up high!

The ground beneath their feet shattered from the recoil force. Using all sorts of secret techniques, they were like fish diving through the dragon gate, soaring towards the top of the Divine Seal Altar!

Beneath the space crack leading to the fifth level, one could still fly up to around a thousand feet. But the further one went, the greater the pressure would be.

Many martial artists flew up around a thousand feet and weren’t able to withstand the dreadful pressure anymore. They fell onto the walls of the Divine Seal Altar and were forced to grab the rough stone cliffs. Then, with their grip on the stone cliffs, they propelled themselves upwards once more.

Again and again, these trial challengers would jump up hundreds of feet at a time; they were considerably fast.

Beneath the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming watched all of this occur from the corners of his eyes. He soon discovered that the pressure falling down from the Divine Seal Altar affected different people in different ways. Martial artists with higher cultivations experienced a suppressive force far more intense than those with lower cultivations.

“The higher one’s cultivation, the more pressure there is?”

It wasn’t just Lin Ming that discovered this, but many other trial challengers also. The pressure coming from the skies above the Divine Seal Altar revolved according to some strange Laws. The higher one’s cultivation, the greater the repulsing force was. Thus, martial artists with higher cultivation had no advantage here at all.

If one only had a high cultivation but was a complete mess in every other aspect, they would truly suffer climbing upwards.

In other words, the Divine Seal Altar was a test of one’s foundation.

“How interesting… the Gate of Laws’ difficulty was dependent on my skeletal age, but the difficulty of this Divine Seal Altar is dependent on my cultivation. When I broke through into the half-step Holy Lord realm on the third level, it seems that it made this Divine Seal Altar more difficult for me to climb instead…”

In this final trial, an endless variety of methods could be brought out to test a trial challenger. Their talent, absolute strength, foundation, comprehension of Laws, all sorts of qualities could be tested here without end.

Lin Ming immediately thought of all this and increasingly anticipated just what the last levels of the final trial would be like. But, he didn’t immediately climb up the Divine Seal Altar. Within his heart, he felt faintly restless.

So much time had passed and yet he hadn’t seen a hint of Xiao Moxian.

Although Lin Ming felt that with Xiao Moxian’s strength and destiny, it was impossible for her to meet some calamitous danger in the fourth level. But, worry was irrational to begin with. If he didn’t see Xiao Moxian, Mo Brightmoon, and the others appear, he couldn’t help but find it hard to remain calm.

On another side, Sheng Mei also didn’t move. She floated 100 feet higher in the air, her blue clothes fluttering about her, her eyes as deep as moons and her black hair as soft as snow.

There was a man standing behind Sheng Mei. This man had a naked upper body and his entire chest was covered with strange mysterious tattoos. His muscles were thick and overlapping, as if they had been shaped by the endless washing of water. He emitted a deeply masculine but magnificent atmosphere.

When Sheng Mei requested three spots from Soul Emperor Divine Void, the two extra spots were for her followers.

This man was one of them. Throughout this entire time he had kept an extremely low profile, not revealing the least bit about himself. Even Lin Ming wasn’t able to judge his strength.

“Lady Soul Empress, this level seems disadvantageous to us…” The tattooed man looked at the Divine Seal Altar, frowning as he spoke.

Sheng Mei lightly shook her head. “It’s far from being disadvantageous. This is a fair test, one that doesn’t look at age and only at one’s foundation. From here on out, the trials we face will not discriminate. Cultivation will not bring one any advantages, but… I never needed those advantages to begin with.”

Sheng Mei said with supreme confidence.

The final trial’s nondiscriminatory trials were the most basic of trials. In these tests where trial challengers would obtain greatly different results from each other, everyone would be placed at the same starting line.

The Gate of Laws was this way and so was the Divine Seal Altar.

The fifth level of the final trial would also be like this.

Towards these things, Sheng Mei had already mentally prepared herself.

“Dragonscar, let’s go.”

As Sheng Mei spoke she flew towards the Divine Seal Altar. Behind her, Dragonscar followed closely.

As Sheng Mei flew up into the skies, because her cultivation was far too high, the pressure she had to withstand was far greater. As her true essence fiercely collided with the pressure of Laws, the friction emitted a dazzling divine light!

Chi chi chi!

Underneath the impact of this divine light, the layers of ice crystals that floated around Sheng Mei began to shatter in abundance, freezing the void!

The momentum with which Sheng Mei climbed the Divine Seal Altar was one that no other martial artist could compare with.

For a time, many trial challengers slowed their pace to look at Sheng Mei, their eyes full of awe and praise.

Even beneath a pressure that far surpassed what anyone else was experiencing, Sheng Mei was still able to rise like a rising beam of light, her speed far faster than the rest!

Chapter 1717 – Overlord

Sheng Mei mounting the top of the Divine Seal Altar’s 33 steps was like a signal. Those trial challengers who failed to reach the 31st step could only stare on unwillingly as the space crack began to slowly close up, sealing them away in the fourth level.

Currently, their position was only several tens of thousands of feet away from the space crack. Normally this distance would only take the blink of an eye to cross, but today it had become an unpassable moat.

As the space crack began to close up, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian trudged on against the intense astral winds and dreadful pressure to climb up the 33rd step.

After completing two nirvanas, it wasn’t difficult for Xiao Moxian to climb up and her speed was no slower than Lin Ming’s.

“These two people are quite fearful…”

Dragonscar breathlessly said from beside Sheng Mei. Although he had just managed to follow behind Sheng Mei, it was a strenuous task for him to climb up the 33rd step.

If there wasn’t an accident then it would only be the four of them that reached the top of the 33 steps. That was Sheng Mei, Dragonscar, Lin Ming, and Xiao Moxian. As for Moonpond and Soulsky, their hopes dimmed with every second. The most they would be able to reach would be halfway up the 33rd step.

“Indeed… these two people might be a great boost to our efforts to pass the fifth level…”

Dragonscar was startled upon hearing Sheng Mei. “Soul Empress… are you planning to try rushing past the final trial’s fifth level?”

Dragonscar knew about the final trial’s fifth trial. In fact, it could be called the limit of the final trial.

Whether it was the Soul Empress or the Good Fortune Saint Son, neither of them had been able to pass the fifth level in the past!

And in fact, according to what Dragonscar knew, for the last billion years no one had been able to pass the fifth level’s trial. Until now, it was still a complete mystery as to what lay past the fifth level.

“That’s my plan… but my hopes aren’t too great. Even if I am unable to pass the fifth level my completion percentage should be 85% or above… if there is even the slightest chance of me passing the fifth level, then my completion percentage will be 88% or even higher…”

Sheng Mei sucked in a deep breath. 88% was considerably close to 90%!

But a completion of 90% was a leap upwards. The rewards from this completion percentage were unimaginable!

As Sheng Mei and Dragonscar spoke, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had already climbed past 25,000 feet and were only several thousand feet away.

At this height they still hadn’t slowed down. As for the others, they had already given up. At this time, the trial of the Divine Seal Altar had more or less ended.

Half an hour later, Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming smoothly ascended to the top.

Standing at the top of the 33rd platform, Lin Ming directly faced Sheng Mei and Dragonscar. Standing in front of them, Lin Ming could clearly feel an icy cold aura wildly gushing out from Sheng Mei, as if she was the source of endless winter wind.

This was an unrivalled woman, one that made all others feel inferior in their heart. Just by casually standing there, she was like a fairy of the highest heavens, ethereal and ephemeral.

“Lin Ming, right…?”

Sheng Mei parted her deep red lips and asked Lin Ming.

To many people, it was the greatest of glories to be remembered by Soul Empress Sheng Mei. This was because in her eyes, most people were as worthy as ants.

“I am Lin Ming. I greet senior Soul Empress.”

Lin Ming cupped his hands across his chest and slightly bowed.

Sheng Mei nodded. “There is no need to be overly polite. Your achievements in the future will be limitless, and perhaps they might surpass my own…”

Sheng Mei’s voice was light. Although these were words of praise for Lin Ming, they were actually extremely grating on Xiao Moxian’s mind as she heard them.

In her opinion, Sheng Mei was only someone that had passed the heaven-step difficulty Gate of Laws. Although she had perfectly passed it with ease, she was far from being comparable to Lin Ming who had passed the Asura level Gate of Laws. And yet, she actually said that Lin Ming’s future achievements might surpass her own.

If Sheng Mei had passed the Asura level difficulty too then Xiao Moxian wouldn’t have any opinion on this. After all, it was as it should be for a senior to speak encouraging and appreciative words to a junior.

‘But hell, you only passed the heaven-step difficulty, so what qualifications do you have to say all that crap?’

Xiao Moxian was originally a fearless character who dreaded neither the heavens nor the earth. Even in front of Soul Empress Sheng Mei, she felt no jitters at all. She raised her chin, curled her lips, and muttered, “My Big Brother Lin’s future will naturally be limitless.”

Although she didn’t say that Lin Ming would inevitably surpass Sheng Mei, her expression and pose indicated her intent.

Regarding this, Sheng Mei only faintly smiled, not replying.

But nearby, Dragonscar frowned and his gaze became much colder and gloomier.

When Sheng Mei was speaking with others, then as a follower, Dragonscar naturally wouldn’t say anything. But Xiao Moxian’s words had left him far too disgruntled.

He coldly coughed and said, “The finch doesn’t know the beauty of the swan and the mole cricket doesn’t know the passing of spring and fall. In life, it’s best not to be so needlessly arrogant. The Empress’s future achievements cannot be imagined by the likes of you. What you have seen so far of the Empress is only the tip of the iceberg. You think you have seen the Empress’s limits? What a joke!”

Dragonscar sneered. He originally thought that Sheng Mei’s praise of Lin Ming just now was far too exaggerated. Future achievements that surpassed her own? Wasn’t that just polite praise to encourage a junior? Yet not only did Lin Ming not respond, but the girl next to him didn’t even appreciate the kindness. One Xiao Moxian and one Lin Ming, both ungrateful.

In the 33 Heavens, no one dared to speak like this!

Although Sheng Mei had only passed the heaven-step Gate of Laws, one couldn’t forget that Sheng Mei had only cultivated the sixth revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art. There was still the seventh, eighth, and ninth revolutions, and they were the most difficult and most terrifying to practice.

Once Sheng Mei cultivated the seventh revolution she could challenge the Asura level Gate of Laws.

Once she completed the eighth revolution she could likely pass it with ease.

As for the ninth revolution, it was unimaginable what she would be like!

Moreover, Dragonscar was faintly aware that even though Sheng Mei had been following Divine Sovereign Soul Rapture for all these years, the truth was that she was slowly brewing a plan that was unimaginably terrifying!

Although Dragonscar didn’t know what this plan was, what he could confirm was that if this plan succeeded, then Sheng Mei and Divine Sovereign Soul Rapture would reach inconceivable heights. It might even allow the spiritas to control all of the 33 Heavens!

Of course, this was one of the greatest secrets of the spiritas. Dragonscar naturally wouldn’t reveal anything.

In this situation, Xiao Moxian naïvely thought that Lin Ming’s future achievements would surpass those of Sheng Mei. Dragonscar naturally couldn’t help but snort in contempt.

Xiao Moxian wasn’t convinced. Just as she was about to continue arguing, Lin Ming pulled her back. And at this time, Sheng Mei also stopped Dragonscar. She icily said, “Dragonscar, do not be rude!”

Dragonscar immediately stopped. He respectfully said, “Yes, Empress.”

Towards Soul Empress Sheng Mei, Dragonscar was absolutely loyal. This was a respect and reverence that came from his heart.

Sheng Mei nodded and said to Lin Ming. “At the fifth level I fear I might need your help…”

Lin Ming was surprised. With Sheng Mei’s strength, she actually needed his help?

Sheng Mei didn’t explain in further detail. She said, “After a while you will understand what I am speaking of. Let us go first. This fifth level is very special…”

As Sheng Mei spoke, the space crack to the fifth level had completely closed and thoroughly separated them from the fourth level. The pressure upon the Divine Seal Altar suddenly vanished and everyone felt their bodies lighten. They all let out a heavy sigh.

Standing on the 33rd step of the Divine Seal Altar, Lin Ming could see the entire space of the fifth level.

The fifth level wasn’t as vast and boundless as he had imagined. Compared to the fourth level, the fifth level was far, far smaller and would only have occupied a tiny corner. In fact, if Lin Ming focuses his sense into a straight line, he could make out the boundaries of this world.

This was a broad wilderness. The earth was a desolate wasteland and clouds hung high in the skies, a deep crimson red that seemed as if it would drip blood at any moment.

Within the air, a dreadful burning heat percolated about. Streams of flame seemed to flutter atop the ground. The rocks and gravel seemed to burn.

A tyrannical and wild aura rushed towards them, making the mind shake!

“This level is…”

Feeling this burning hot wilderness, restlessness surged in Lin Ming’s heart. It seemed that this was a truly terrifying level!

Many of the other trial challengers on the Divine Seal Altar were thinking the same thing. But due to the temptation of lucky chances, they were eager to leap down the Divine Seal Altar and see what the fifth level was like. After all, many lucky chances were first come first serve, and they were willing to take this risk.

“You all… would do best to not continue forwards.”

At this time, a cold voice passed into everyone’s ears. They paused and looked back. The one who had been speaking was Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei’s clothes floated about her as she descended from the Divine Seal Altar like a fairy maiden exiled to the mortal world. “In your current state, entering the fifth level will be far too perilous. There will only be dangers, no lucky chances. Rather, it could be said that the lucky chance in the fifth level can be obtained after defeating the Overlord of the fifth level. And, the Overlord’s strength is extremely terrifying. No matter which one of you it is, if you encounter it alone then you will die without a doubt.”

Sheng Mei’s words caused everyone to feel a chill crawl up their backs. No one dared to suspect her words. They all stood motionless.

“Rest here for three days and then we shall continue onwards together. The fifth level is extremely special and I do not have the confidence that I can pass it alone, thus I will require the cooperation and support of everyone here.”

As Sheng Mei spoke, everyone was shocked. Sheng Mei wanted their support?

With Sheng Mei’s strength, it would only take a single thought to kill any one of them here, but she actually said she wanted their support?

What was so peculiar about the fifth level, that even Sheng Mei feared it so? And what use would they be?

Without questioning, everyone began to rest and meditate. If this level could have Sheng Mei be so serious, just how dangerous was this level?

Undoubtedly, a single mistake and they would lose their life!

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian also sat down to rest. The further they progressed in the final trial, the more dangerous it would become. They wouldn’t overestimate themselves either.

Like this, three days slowly passed and everyone restored themselves to their top condition. And at this time, Sheng Mei stood up. She faintly said, “Let us go…”

Chapter 1719 – Reaping Souls

“Attack!”

Someone shouted.

Those that were able to arrive on the fifth level were outstanding elites amongst outstanding elites. They were all proud children of heaven of their respective races and were able to accurately gauge the combat situation.

Now that the golden skeletons were weakened by the freezing ice domain released by Sheng Mei, this was undoubtedly the best chance to destroy them all.

A purple-clothed spiritas youth attacked first. In an instant, countless white lights drilled out from his flesh, like endless strands of silk that tore through space. These threads emitted brilliant waves of white light as they whistled through the air, passing over everyone’s heads with staggering momentum.

Some of these white lights crashed onto the metal-hard bodies of the golden skeletons. There was a loud grating sound like metal striking on metal as the golden skeletons weren’t wounded at all. This amazing defensive power proved Sheng Mei’s words.

But there were still some white lights that crashed into the eye sockets of these golden skeletons.

As long as the white lights fell into the eye sockets of the golden skeletons, the ghostly flames within crackled as they were slowly extinguished.

Several golden skeletons that had just risen froze where they were… without the support of soul force, their bodies began to collapse, like brick and stone buildings caving in.

In the crowd, Dragonscar’s aura erupted. Snow-white scales appeared on his body as a billowing origin energy surged through the world, astonishing all.

He wildly dashed around, his body so fast that blazing white flames were produced from the friction between him and the air. Horrifying shock waves reverberated around him as he leapt a hundred feet into the air and came diving back down. A bolt of lightning seemed to flash within his arms as he forcefully shattered the eye sockets of one of the golden skeletons.

There was also a proud son of heaven from the saint race. By relying on his amazing bodily talent, he punched at one of the golden skeletons. Originally, this punch was able to shatter mountains and rivers, but as it struck the golden skeleton he only managed to sink it into the earth, and even his fist had torn apart.

As the golden skeleton began crawling up from the ground once more, the saint youth genius finally learned his lesson. He began to strike at the quiet ghostly fires in the skeleton’s eye sockets…

This battle unfolded like a clash royale. Everyone fought with heated spirits!

“Hahahaha! Feels great!”

“These golden skeletons are too weak! It only takes one step to kill ten!”

At this time, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian also attacked. Lin Ming shot out spear lights with his fingertips, easily extinguishing the soul fires in the golden skeletons’ eye sockets.

As for Xiao Moxian, she released a mass of black flames that were as thin as willows.

Although these flames seemed small, when they touched a golden skeleton they rapidly inflated as if they would grow to destroy the world. As long as they covered a golden skeleton, the soul fires in their eyes would rapidly be destroyed.

Although these golden skeletons had a formidable combat strength comparable to a middle Holy Lord saint martial artist, their weaknesses were too obvious. They were easily focused down by others.

As Sheng Mei slowly moved forwards, all of the golden skeletons that crawled out from the sandy earth were quickly cut down by the numerous proud children of heaven, not able to create any trouble for the group.

Suddenly, the sandy world before them disappeared.

Thick twisting beams of fires flowed about like a den of pythons, exuding a spectacular heat that gushed out in all directions.

Within this endless sea of flames was a giant mass of phantasmal flames that surged with a strange strength, floating up and down like a lonely island.

But even more than that, it resembled a fire phoenix.

This bizarre mass of flames had dazzling wings and a great body formed from pure fire essence. It was over a thousand feet tall, enough to block out the skies.

The space behind it was completely burnt down by the hot flames, exposing nothing but an endless abyss of darkness.

From time to time, small sparks of fire would shoot out from its body, and large holes would be burnt in space by these small sparks, like someone touching a piece of cloth with a burning torch.

Although the group hadn’t yet approached, they could feel an astonishing pressure exuding from that fire phoenix’s flame-formed body. It was a pressure deep enough to cause their souls to shiver, as if they could be grinded into the ground at any time by the pressure alone.

Strange fire runes seethed around the fire phoenix’s entire body, like layers of flattering stars.

As the runes flickered they released a dreadful conflagration of flames that turned into thick fire tornados on the ground. The fire tornadoes tore through the earth, burning and combusting until they left behind deep rivers of fire.

Space storms howled from the tears in space, wildly spinning around.

Even the freezing ice domain that Soul Empress Sheng Mei released began to evaporate due to the unimaginable power of fire.

Hu – hu – hu –

Within the sea of flames, tiny red bubbles of fire popped out, revealing golden skeletons that came crawling out.

The soul fires that burned within their eyes were far more powerful than those of the golden skeletons that Lin Ming had encountered before. Red light shot out from them, making the heart race.

The color was also far deeper than that of ordinary golden skeletons, and the aura they released was far more dreadful.

Lin Ming scanned his eyes around. There were around 400-500 golden skeletons that had appeared so far, and more and more were slowly crawling out from the sea of flames.

“Undying Inferno!” Someone gasped, panic-stricken as they stared at the fire phoenix composed of pure flames within the sea of fire.

As if it were aroused by this cry, the Undying Inferno that was resting with the roiling flames suddenly opened its eyes.

It was like a sun exploding, a supernova…

Bang –

Two terrifying masses of fire shot out, seeming as if they could penetrate through the world as they hurtled towards the person that had shouted just then!

These flames were incredibly quick. They directly pierced through Sheng Mei’s freezing ice domain and rushed towards that person!

Sheng Mei’s eyebrows pressed together. The attacked speed of the Undying Inferno was far too fast, not giving her enough time to save him. Moreover, she hadn’t laid down the battle array yet so she couldn’t rescue him if she wanted to!

With a light crackling sound, the person’s flesh and blood began to boil and burn, their entire body being scorched away. With a miserable scream, even the earth beneath their feet began to melt into a metallic magma due to the extreme heat.

Rah - !

Suddenly, a golden skeleton rushed out from the husk of the dead martial artist. Its body crackled and it raised its fiery fists as it rushed towards the group.

Then, a person’s figure flashed. It was Dragonscar. He grasped his heavy sword and rushed out. His heavy sword weighed as much as a mountain and in two strikes, the golden skeleton’s soul fires that burned in its eyes were extinguished.

Seeing this flaming golden skeleton on the ground, some people sucked in a cold breath, unable to restrain a feeling of grief in their hearts. Just a moment ago, this person had fought by their side. He seemed to have been a genius of some ancient clan…

If one was killed by the flames of the Undying Inferno they would turn into a golden skeleton. Although Soul Empress Sheng Mei had already informed them of this, with the bloody truth placed in front of them it still left them terrified.

Within her freezing ice domain, a rare earnest expression appeared on Sheng Mei’s face. The ribbon that wrapped around her body began to shimmer with giant runes. Every time these runes shimmered, they would release an indescribably profound aura of Ice Laws.

The aura of these Ice Laws rippled out, spreading through the void for 10,000 feet. Some of these ripples even neared the range of the Undying Inferno.

The freezing cold air directly collided with the strange flames, releasing horrifying energy fluctuations that detonated again and again.

Sheng Mei’s entire body released a peculiar icy aura as her delicate hands repeatedly moved in the air. Unbelievably beautiful wisps of essence energy scattered out all over, floating down like snowflakes.

Then, twining together with the power of Laws released by the strange ribbon, countless seals appeared as Sheng Mei formed an exquisite array formation with her as the center.

Within this array formation, everyone, including Lin Ming, felt the power of ice begin to condense around their bodies, forming a type of armor.

Although the armor had the power of mystic cold within it, its defensive capabilities were extremely high. Those people that were feeling suffocated from the burning heat just now suddenly returned to their normal states.

“This is the Extreme Cold Battle Array that I’ve laid down. Within this array formation, the might of the Undying Inferno’s flames will be greatly weakened. Everyone follow my lead and do not leave this battle array!”

Sheng Mei’s voice was deep and awe-inspiring, ringing out in the hearts of everyone present.

Everyone felt a chill crawl up their backs. None of them dared to neglect her orders – they had already learned from the mistake of that youth who had been scorched into a golden skeleton.

The fire phoenix-shaped Undying Inferno felt the freezing cold energy in the air and seemed to be stimulated by it. Overwhelming flames filled the skies as the Undying Inferno flew in circles. All of space for a million miles turned into a sea of flames, limitless and boundless.

On the ground, massive mountain ranges began to crack apart and disintegrate. Tongues of flame fell down from the void, transforming everything into molten lava flows.

The world was filled with fire and death, as if it were the eve of the apocalypse.

“You dare to anger me!? All of you will die!!”

The Undying Inferno raised its head, a contemptuous look in its eyes.

Its voice crashed into everyone’s minds like a peal of thunder. Then, the Undying Inferno unfurled its wings. From space, a blaze of crimson flames appeared and came crashing down, like a rain of tiny meteors.

A violent storm appeared, racing towards the area where Lin Ming was.

At the same time, more and more golden skeletons shot out from the sea of flames, all of them rushing towards Lin Ming and the others.

However, even though they were extremely fast, as soon as they entered the Extreme Cold Battle Array their movements slowed down as if they were mired in a swamp, becoming extremely slow.

Even so, these golden skeletons were far stronger than the previous ones. Wanting to kill them wasn’t easy at all!

Moreover, there was also the threat of the Undying Inferno. The fiery meteors it released were crashing down from the skies. Although these meteors were wrapped in layers of Ice Laws and slowed down when they entered the Extreme Cold Battle Array, if everyone was forced to deal with these then they would be far too overstretched!

For a time, the trial challengers were caught in a brutal struggle. The battle with the golden skeletons also entered a stalemate!

Minus the youth that had just died, no one had yet been injured. But if this battle were to continue, they would inevitably suffer losses. Moreover, the Undying Inferno had yet to truly attack. As for them, they were constantly wasting a tremendous amount of energy in battle with the golden skeletons. If this were to continue then things would rapidly become more and more dangerous.

If they couldn’t withstand this siege of golden skeletons until the Undying Inferno turned into a phoenix egg, then they would fail. There was even a chance that all of them would be exterminated!

In this situation, Sheng Mei still hadn’t moved. She focused all of her attention on maintaining the Extreme Cold Battle Array as well as guarding against the Undying Inferno’s fatal strike!

“Damn it, these fellows are just endless!”

“Just how many are there? Can we ever finish killing them all…?”

Many trial challengers were in a critical situation. The previous levity and happy atmosphere as they cut down the first golden skeletons had disappeared, replaced by a deep seriousness and even a trace of fear and dread.

And as everyone had fallen into a brutal melee, some people discovered that Lin Ming had separated from the group and had flown ahead with the black-haired girl. They almost neared the edge of the Extreme Cold Battle Array as they floated in the air.

Pitch black mystical runes shot out from Lin Ming’s palm.

“What is he planning on doing?”

Someone asked, startled. But at this time, they couldn’t care about Lin Ming. What was important was saving their own lives.

Suddenly, a black light flashed out from Lin Ming’s fingertips, carrying with it the aura of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. This light shot into the air and rapidly expanded into a giant vortex. From within this vortex, all sorts of sad screams and wails spread out.

Faintly, one could even see the outlines and shadows of countless demons and ghosts, hideous and horrifying.

When this vortex appeared, even those near it felt as if their souls would be sucked in.

As this vortex grew larger and larger, the golden skeletons that slowly moved within the Extreme Cold Battle Array began to stir, becoming restless. They all looked up into the air, their ghostly red fire eyes looking at the air in puzzlement.

Bang –

The giant vortex suddenly descended, wrapping all of the hundreds of golden skeletons within. Then, a golden skeleton roared out loud as the strange fires in its eyes flew out and began to stream towards the black vortex.

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel excelled in suppressing ghosts, spirits, demons, and souls of dead martial artists. Facing these golden skeletons, summoning the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel to extinguish the soul fires in their eyes was the best possible method!

As for the terrifying defensive power of the golden skeletons, that was all useless before the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

For a time, the burning flames within the golden skeletons’ eyes were swept up like candles in a raging storm, crazily inhaled by the black vortex!

Hu hu hu!

As the soul fires within these golden skeletons’ eyes were extinguished, their bodies fell down like waste wood, shattering as they struck the ground.

In an instant, a massive tract of golden skeletons had fallen down, as if they were nothing but stalks of wheat being reaped.

Seeing this scene, many people felt a cold sweat drip down their back. This Lin Ming, just what sort of abnormal cultivation method did he use to kill them? This was just too fast!

“A little bit of suction and they all died. Just what is that black wheel!?”

“How horrifying. Let alone that wheel destroying those golden skeletons, I even felt as if my soul would be sucked in!” A spiritas martial artist said with trepidation. As a spiritas he was highly sensitive to things of the soul.

The trial challengers present originally believed that Lin Ming’s cultivation time was limited and he was far too young, so in terms of Laws and cultivation methods he would be at a disadvantage. But, they never imagined that this single move Lin Ming displayed would leave them all in the dust!

This difference wasn’t minor at all. As they all remembered their thoughts that they would be able to obtain a tiny advantage due to their age, they realized they had been far too naïve.

Because of Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel suddenly reducing the pressure on everyone, they were all able to conserve more of their energy.

From a distance, Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming, a strange light shining in her eyes. Indeed, Lin Ming had not disappointed her. Like this, she could save more of her strength so that she would be able to pour more power into piercing through the phoenix egg that the Undying Inferno would leave behind.

Chapter 1721 – Victory or Defeat?

Sheng Mei’s complexion changed. She immediately thought of a possibility.

In an instant, the Undying Inferno sparkled with dazzling flames as it immediately arrived in front of the Extreme Cold Battle Array like a bolt of lightning.

This was true refined source strength of the Undying Inferno – it was enough to crush a planet!

Everyone was inexorably horrified. The Undying Inferno had arrived too fast, so fast that none of them were able to react!

Boundless burning power of fire combined with a tyrannical and overwhelming power. The Extreme Cold Battle Array began to tremble once more.

Some of the shattered runes fell away, allowing the majestic fire power to enter.

Wherever the power of fire went, it would turn everything into liquid flame sludge.

One after another, the runes of the Extreme Cold Battle Array began to break apart.

Everyone felt their hearts sink into despair.

This empowered Extreme Cold Battle Array wasn’t able to resist the core mystic strength of the Undying Inferno, let alone their mortal bodies!

At this time, Sheng Mei’s pupils began to swirl, becoming deep and dark like fathomless pools. A six-petal snow flower design began to appear within her eyes as a cold light emitted from them – this was her vital soul force!

As her soul force shot out into the Extreme Cold Battle Array, the shattered runes and soon-to-break Extreme Cold Battle Array were immediately revitalized, once more shining with a dazzling light.

Each rune glowed with an icy white atmosphere. Spirit power burst out, blinding the eyes. Even the power of fire in the air froze and was forcefully extinguished.

Bang!

The luminescent Extreme Cold Battle Array collided with the Undying Inferno’s life essence.

Each strike of the Undying Inferno was able to shatter a planet.

But no matter how much it tried, all of its attacks were blocked by Sheng Mei’s vital soul force-empowered Extreme Cold Battle Array.

Every collision would cause numerous runes to dim down and fade away. But with Sheng Mei’s support, more and more runes were born, rapidly glistening in the air…

An intense energy storm swelled forth in all directions, tearing apart space and ripping open the earth, destroying all things in its path. It was truly terrifying.

Flame swept up in tornados. More and more ice runes were destroyed!

Under this dreadful assault, Sheng Mei began to drip crystalline beads of sweat.

At this time, her concentration was utterly focused. The six-petal snow flower design in her pupils had turned icy blue in color. These pupils were similar to Dragon Fang’s Three Lives Pupils; they were different methods that brought out equally wonderful results. By using a secret technique, the shape of her pupils changed, allowing Sheng Mei to erupt with an even greater strength!

Seeing Sheng Mei in such a state, Lin Ming’s complexion was earnest. This Undying Inferno had surpassed his imagination. Sheng Mei was using up far too much strength!

Even if they persisted until the Undying Inferno became an egg, the following attack would still have to rely on Sheng Mei.

After all, against a fire phoenix egg, only attacking it with the power of ice could result in the greatest lethality.

As for Lin Ming, his cultivation methods were biased towards thunder and fire. Using fire to attack a fire phoenix egg was an exercise in futility.

Dragonscar also saw beads of sweat drip down Soul Empress Sheng Mei’s face. He gripped his fists, unable to stop his heart from racing with anxiousness.

“The Fire Phoenix hasn’t died yet! How could it be so tenacious!”

Dragonscar howled in his heart.

And at this time, through the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, Lin Ming could feel the strength of the Undying Inferno rapidly weakening!

“Mm? The Undying Inferno is dying…”

A happy expression crossed Lin Ming’s face. If this continued then the Undying Inferno wouldn’t be able to attack more than five times.

Soon, the other people also discovered that the impact strength behind the Undying Inferno’s strikes was weakening.

The Fire Phoenix’s flame body started to become increasingly dim in the air. The flames around its body shrank to dim strands that fluttered about.

However, it was still as wild and crazy as before, attacking the Extreme Cold Battle Array until it died!

Finally, as the Undying Inferno attacked the great vaulted barrier of the Extreme Cold Battle Array once more, the flame energy within its body was actually frozen by the Extreme Cold Battle Array, causing it to rapidly fade.

“Yes!”

“This Undying Inferno will be extinguished soon, haha!”

A breathless youth said, wild with joy as he saw the flames around the Undying Inferno beginning to extinguish.

But at this time, as the central force of the battlefield, Sheng Mei had yet to speak a single word. Even uttering a single syllable could release the energy within her, causing her strength to collapse.

Then, from the area where the Undying Inferno had just been extinguished, strange changes began to slowly occur in the midst of the dim flames.

Within the glow of flames, strange and mysterious lines of the Great Dao began to appear.

Hu – hu – hu –

Terrifying waves of energy swept out. The earth shook once more. Alarming cracks spread through the ground like an endless spider web, and from these cracks, blazing flames shot up, soaring to the heavens!

These flames howled in the air, all of them rushing towards the area where the Undying Inferno had been extinguished!

Rumble rumble rumble!

Horrifying flame explosions rang through the air, reverberating through space like a supernova was occurring right before their eyes! A terrifying heat swept over them. Even a planet would be instantly turned to be molten lava by this degree of burning heat!

The Extreme Cold Battle Array fiercely shook. Millions of runes extinguished as they tried to withstand this dreadful firestorm.

And at this time, in the center of the flames, all of the fire energy became increasingly dense. It was gathering into a massive egg the size of a mountain!

Thump! Thump! Thump!

Loud heartbeats rang out from the thick egg shell, like the steady beat of a great drum, showing off the exuberant life force within.

And this beating sound seemed to pass into the hearts of everyone present, making it feel as if their very beings were sympathetically resonating with it. There was an unspeakable discomfort that percolated within their chests.

The Undying Inferno was being reborn in a bath of flames!

At this moment, Sheng Mei’s fingers began rapidly twisting as she shot out numerous Ice Law runes. The strange ribbon that wrapped around her floated in front of her, glowing with an icy cold light!

This ribbon was the lucky chance that Sheng Mei had obtained on the fourth level. Although it wasn’t an offensive magic tool, it could actually enhance Sheng Mei’s power of ice.

At this time, Sheng Mei’s jade-smooth complexion dripped with little beads of crystalline sweat, revealing a faint trace of stubbornness.

Victory or defeat, everything would be decided in one strike!

Ka ka ka!

Strange explosive sounds crackled all around Sheng Mei. The sea of fire vanished, replaced by limitless freezing ice.

This everlasting ice even froze the void and shattered it to pieces. And from the cracks of the frozen void, an ancient glacier began to flow out!

A resonant and mournful Ice Phoenix cry spread out from within Sheng Mei’s body. Then, an Ice Phoenix emerged from her inner world!

This was not a phoenix phantom but a true God Beast. It was Sheng Mei’s mount, a royal Ice Phoenix!

Before, regardless of what attack she had to face from the Undying Inferno, Sheng Mei had not summoned her Ice Phoenix. This was because she needed the Ice Phoenix to conserve its strength, all to aid her in this final strike!

“Royal Ice Phoenix!”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. Sheng Mei was actually able to possess an Ice Phoenix of royal lineage as her contract beast.

However, beneath the peculiar Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, even Sheng Mei’s Ice Phoenix had its cultivation suppressed to the early Holy Lord realm!

The Ice Phoenix cried out. A dreadful icy wind howled about it. It dove into the ancient glacier, fusing together with it. Then, the massive glacier suddenly rose into the air. The enormous glacier began to fall like a river of white stars, crashing into the mountain-sized egg!

Everyone watched with bated breath.

Even after experiencing dozens of attacks from the Undying Inferno and having consumed a great deal of her strength, Sheng Mei was still able to use her Ice Phoenix as support and display such a terrifying striking power!

Where the titanic glacier went, space froze and cracked open like glass. With an overbearing momentum it crashed into the giant egg!

Ka ka ka ka!

A sound of shattering ice spread out with enough power behind it to freeze the souls of powerhouses. Waves of mystic Ice Law runes gushed out onto the fiery giant egg, covering it with a thick layer of frost.

With the extreme cold everfrozen glacier to attack the fiery giant egg, all of that horrifying cold energy reckless seeped into the egg, wildly attacking it!

In that moment, a crack appeared in the surface of the giant egg!

As this crack appeared, it began to widen a little bit at a time. Everyone was stunned, their eyes widening. Had they succeeded?

The great egg shell began to slowly split apart. A cold air fell down to the earth, as if it came from the highest frozen mountains.

Time seemed to come to a standstill. Everyone watched as the massive egg was frozen by the freezing glacier, becoming a giant block of ice. Above this block of ice, tiny cracks appeared and one could see faint traces of the Great Dao Fire Laws swirling about. Then, the heartbeat of the great egg also began to slowly die down…

Everyone kept their eyes locked onto the great egg, watching for any changes. They had no idea just what the result was.

After a moment of silence, the surface of the great egg released a crackling sound as a pillar of flame shot up into the skies, breaking through the cage of freezing ice and shooting into the horizon.

Everyone was on edge, their minds alert. This was a critical stage; they all thought that the Undying Inferno might rush out at any moment.

However, just an instant later, the entire great egg shattered, turning into a mass of flame that fused underground.

They did it?

No one was able to determine just what happened. Even Sheng Mei pressed her eyebrows together in thought. She had already swallowed down a transcendent divine pill, rapidly restoring her origin energy even as she kept watching against any sudden changes and dangers.

Lin Ming spread out his sense, trying to use the Asura Laws to investigate the situation of the Undying Inferno.

For a time, there was only absolute silence.

The sea of fire receded and the flowing lava solidified. The violent fire origin energy that flooded the world began to rapidly dissipate.

“We really did it!”

Seeing the dark wasteland that was immersed in the sea of fire begin to reveal itself once more, many martial artists relaxed, joy starting to appear on their faces.

“Yes!”

Dragonscar vigorously gripped his fists together, overjoyed from the depths of his heart.

These changes rapidly continued until they swept through the entire fifth level. The sea of fire had really vanished, disappearing until there was nothing left.

“Can we really enter the sixth level?”

“That’s right, haha, even if I cannot pass the sixth level no matter what, I am more than satisfied with taking a look at it!”

“Indeed! We will leave behind a legend! A legend that hasn’t appeared for a billion years!”

As many trial challengers were excitedly speaking, they all looked at Sheng Mei. Without a doubt, Sheng Mei was the pillar of their group.

But at this time, Sheng Mei’s complexion was still dignified. She hadn’t relaxed at all.

Sheng Mei’s expression caused Dragonscar’s mind to chill. “Empress, what is it…?”

Sheng Mei frowned. She gloomily said, “Haven’t you discovered that since the sea of fire receded, the temperature has already become lower than normal. In fact, it is dropping even more…”

“What?”

Hearing Sheng Mei’s words, everyone was panic-stricken. Indeed, as she had said, without them knowing the temperature had dropped below freezing and it was continuing to drop!

Chapter 1722 – Completion Percent

Originally, because of the Undying Inferno and the terrifying sea of fire, the temperature in the fifth level was enough to melt rock. Even though Sheng Mei continuously activated the Extreme Cold Ice Array and even crushed apart the fire phoenix egg with her everfrost glacier, she still wasn’t able to cause the temperature to fall.

But now, after the Undying Inferno dissipated, the temperature began to plummet at an alarming rate.

Soon, from the molten temperatures, this became a land of arctic ice!

A cold and dark wind wildly howled about and even the moisture in the air instantly froze, turning into ice crystals. A thick layer of frost began to cover the ground.

The rivers of lava turned into frozen rivers. Cold energy sank into the body, making everyone feel as if their souls would freeze here!

“This… this is…”

Dragonscar had already realized a single terrifying possibility. But, he wanted with all his heart to believe that this wasn’t true. He turned to Sheng Mei, “Empress, is this because of your everfrost glacier? I think that…”

Sheng Mei lightly sighed. She interrupted Dragonscar and shook her head.

“Em… Empress…”

“We’ve lost… the Undying Inferno has become the Undying Polar Ice…” Sheng Mei whispered.

“What!?”

Although the trial challengers could feel that something was wrong, Sheng Mei’s sudden words shocked all of them.

Before this they had already consumed a tremendous amount of their strength to struggle through a brutal battle. Even Sheng Mei had released that unrivalled attack. But even so, they still hadn’t been able to kill the Undying Inferno.

This Undying Inferno was far too ridiculous!

Such a powerful fifth level Overlord, how could anyone possibly pass?

“Even that powerful everfrost glacier wasn’t able to kill the Undying Inferno?”

“This… this Undying Inferno truly lives up to its name… it cannot die!”

“T-t-then what do we do?”

Some trial challengers sputtered out, at a loss of how to deal with the current situation.

Sheng Mei shook her head and said, “We have already lost so we can only return to the fourth level. It seems I underestimated the strength of the Undying Inferno.”

Ultimately, the last time that Sheng Mei had arrived at the fifth level, after her cataclysmic battle with the Undying Inferno she had only thought up a possible method to defeat it. Today was her trying out that method, but she had no idea whether it would succeed or fail.

Sheng Mei soon regained her composure. All of the years of preparation had been destroyed, but she didn’t lose faith. Currently she was only in the sixth revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art, and there was still the seventh, eighth, and ninth revolutions – sooner or later she would pass the fifth level.

It seemed that her hopes of passing the fifth level at the sixth revolution had been too naïve. After all, the vision of the Asura Road Master was far too high, so it was normal for her not to pass even at the sixth revolution.

“Return?”

Hearing Sheng Mei say this word, the martial artists looked at each other in dismay, at a loss for words. They thought that they could leave behind their own legends and be recorded in the historical texts of every major sect in the Asura Road, but now, all of those dreams had been popped.

“That’s our only choice. We’ve used up too much energy. If we don’t leave now then we won’t have another chance.”

As people were speaking, their misty breath instantly turned to ice crystals. The temperature had fallen to a point where even heaven and earth origin energy was being frozen.

But still, some people weren’t willing, “There might be a mistake. Since the Undying Inferno hasn’t died… how come we don’t see the phoenix egg?”

Lin Ming said, “There is no need for the phoenix egg to form; the entire fifth level is the breeding ground for the Undying Polar Ice. When the cold energy in this world has risen to the extreme, it will naturally gather together and reform into an Ice Phoenix.

After comprehending the Asura Heavenly Dao, Lin Ming could foretell what was soon about to happen.

Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming with surprise. This young man’s insight was truly keen for him to realize the situation in the fifth level.

And at this time, information appeared in everyone’s minds. This information told them their completion percentage!

Everyone felt their hearts shake. Most of them had over 60% with an extremely small number over 70%.

When they completed the Gate of Laws their completion percentage had been over 30%, after the fourth level it was around 50%, and then after the Divine Seal Altar and the battle with the Undying Inferno, the final number had settled around 65-70%.

This number left them depressed and frustrated. Let alone the legendary 80%, most of them didn’t even reach 70%.

But at this time, Sheng Mei also received a message – 86%. Compared to the last time she was here, it was a mere 3% higher.

Although it was only 3%, after reaching 80%, increasing the score by a single percent was incomparably difficult!

Her score had surpassed 85%. As the Divine Void Soul Emperor had said, there was no one that would be able to match her in in the past or future!

However, Sheng Mei was still unsatisfied with this percentage. She couldn’t help but glance at Lin Ming, “Lin Ming, your completion percentage… what is it?”

As Sheng Mei spoke, everyone looked over to Lin Ming. They also wanted to know.

This freak of nature had passed the Asura level Gate of Laws.

His completion percentage…

Just how high had been able to go?

Lin Ming thought for a moment and then said, “85.”

Although this completion percentage didn’t seem like much to Lin Ming, as this number fell into everyone's ears they sucked in a breath of cold air. 85%! That already broke past Sheng Mei’s past record. But this time, Sheng Mei was likely to have created a new record.

Lin Ming was also curious about Sheng Mei’s completion percentage. He asked her, “And the Soul Empress?”

Everyone waited with bated breath as they turned back to Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei was silent for a moment and then clearly said, “86%.”

Sheng Mei was even higher!

Everyone looked at each other with surprise. Some people were stunned speechless. They were already shocked enough when Lin Ming had perfectly crossed the Asura level Gate of Laws and thought he would have the highest completion percentage, but now their thoughts had been completely reversed.

“The Soul Empress is fierce… I thought Lin Ming would be slightly higher…”

“This is just on par for normal! Lin Ming probably had around 5% more than the Soul Empress after the Gate of Laws, but in the fifth level we had to face the Undying Inferno and it was the Soul Empress who led the way. It is impossible for anyone to compare with her heaven-defying comprehension of Laws. Rather, Lin Ming dropped a little… after all, he is too young, so this is a handicap he cannot overcome.”

After Lin Ming had completed the Gate of Laws his completion percentage reached 45. This was proven when he was able to step into the planet-sized immortal palace.

After crossing the fourth level and killing so many monsters, his completion rate had risen to 60%.

Then, after climbing up the 33 steps of the Divine Seal Altar, his score had risen to 75%. Up until then, his score had been perfect.

But on the fifth level the one leading the force and also the one with the greatest role had been Sheng Mei. Facing the Undying Inferno, whether it was defending or attacking, it was almost Sheng Mei alone. No matter how much everyone tried to support her, they were just that – supporting actors. Thus, Lin Ming obtained another 10% but Sheng Mei’s score rose by 16%. After combining everything, Lin Ming was slightly worse.

Although Lin Ming’s completion percentage was lower than Sheng Mei’s, it was enough to bewilder all the trial challengers present.

“How terrifying, if Lin Ming comes again and his skeletal age rises a little more, he might be able to obtain 88% or 89%!”

A trial challenger said. But, his words were immediately refuted by someone else.

“Don’t be silly, do you think completing the final trial is so simple? And you even thought of 89%! Do you know what sort of concept that is? Even someone who will become a True Divinity might not be able to achieve such a higher score! After reaching 80%, every single point more is incomparably difficult!”

“In the future, after several hundred more years pass and Lin Ming’s comprehension of Laws becomes higher, if he enters the final trial again then he might be able to obtain an 87% completion rate. That is the limit, but that is already more than high enough…”

As everyone was speaking, Xiao Moxian smirked, thinking otherwise.

Beside Lin Ming, Mo Brightmoon and Suya also tried to comfort Lin Ming. After all, Lin Ming was still young. Once his comprehension of Laws rose then he could always come again. And with Lin Ming’s future status it wouldn’t be hard to obtain the complete sets of god runes needed to enter.

At this time, Dragonscar said, “We must go now. The Undying Polar Ice will emerge soon. If we delay then we won’t be able to leave.”

Hearing Dragonscar’s words, many people felt disappointed.

To return back to the fourth level also meant that their journey into the final trial would end here.

Although the trial challengers had only been in the final trial for several months, they had experienced countless slaughter fests and perilous dangers here, and it felt as if they had spent several years here instead. Even after all of that their completion percentage was still low. Thinking that they had to return now, everyone was at a bit of a loss.

However, remaining was also impossible. They were just not a match for the Undying Polar Ice. Some people had already turned around and were ready to leave. But at this time, an icy voice rang out, especially clear in the chilling winds…

“Everyone, please wait a moment…”

“Mm?”

Everyone was startled. They stopped their steps and turned around to see a black-clothed Lin Ming standing not too far away from them. Standing right beside him was the black-clothed Xiao Moxian.

The one who spoke just now was Lin Ming.

“What is it?”

Everyone looked at Lin Ming with a puzzled expression. They didn’t know why Lin Ming had stopped them.

Lin Ming paused for a moment and then said, “The Undying Polar Ice… we can try to battle it.”

His slow and calm words passed through the cold wind, causing everyone to shiver!

“What!?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, the martial artists were stunned. They glanced at each other, aghast.

The Undying Inferno couldn’t be killed, and that was with Sheng Mei using her ice-attribute cultivation methods that restrained it. In this situation, how could they fight with the Undying Polar Ice?

“Lin Ming, stop joking around. The Undying Polar Ice is likely as strong as the Undying Inferno, just that the attributes are different. We were only able to rely on the Soul Empress to attack, and that is also because the Soul Empress trains in ice-attribute cultivation methods so cracking open a heated rock isn’t too difficult for her. But to freeze open a rock of ice, that is impossible.”

Some martial artists frowned, thinking that Lin Ming was playing with them.

“It's getting colder and colder here. Let’s not talk any nonsense. We have to hurry back to the fourth level. If the Undying Polar Ice emerges then we might not even have a chance to escape.”

Seeing the surrounding ice energy begin to permeate into their inner worlds, a trial challenger spoke out in a flustered panic. If the Undying Polar Ice were to attack them, that wouldn’t be funny at all.

Chapter 1724 – Umbral Heaven Ice Array

“Let’s hurry and get out of here!”

“Leave them behind to deal with the Undying Polar Ice! We’ve got to make it to a safe area!”

The eight trial challengers leaving were shocked and filled with dread as they witnessed the earth-shaking scene of the Undying Polar Ice being born. But from that initial shock and fear, it slowly became a gloating schadenfreude.

No matter how powerful the Undying Polar Ice was, it was Lin Ming that would have to withstand it; it had nothing to do with them.

The eight people all launched their movement techniques and used their energies to break past the massive ice crystals floating in the air, shuttling through the wild and frenzied cold winds.

Because the Divine Seal Altar’s transmission channel had closed, they were temporarily unable to leave the fifth level. But as long as they were far away from the Undying Polar Ice they shouldn’t suffer any major disasters. After all, when they first arrived at the fifth level they were quite a distance from the Undying Inferno and hadn’t suffered any attacks.

As the eight people flew away, terrifying snow gales and ice storms blew through the world. Massive chunks of ice fell on the ground, immediately covering the ground in thick glaciers.

Lin Ming and the others soared into the air. Sheng Mei once again created the Extreme Cold Ice Array around her, enveloping everyone.

Immediately, everyone felt the pressure on them be reduced. Lin Ming looked towards Sheng Mei and couldn’t help but admire her strength. He could tell that a dreadful amount of energy was required to maintain this Extreme Cold Combat Array, and a normal Holy Lord would only be able to keep it up for half an incense stick of time before being completely drained.

Yet not only was Sheng Mei able to persist for such a long time, but she also managed to control the Extreme Cold Battle Array to a profound degree that was able to withstand the strikes of the Undying Inferno and Undying Polar Ice. The reason she was able to accomplish this was because she had an incredibly deep understanding of the Ice Laws and could utilize her origin energy to its full potential. She was even able to absorb the power of ice from the world and minimize the use of her soul force.

But, even though Sheng Mei was able to perfectly accomplish all of this, it still placed a tremendous pressure on her to face the Undying Polar Ice in continuous battle.

“Empress…”

Seeing the heavy burden of defense fall on Sheng Mei’s thin and delicate shoulders, Dragonscar felt inexplicable pain in his heart.

“Focus your heart on the battle before you!”

Sheng Mei icily said as she saw Dragonscar be distracted. Dragonscar grit his teeth and turned his head towards that horrifying snowstorm that was breeding in the air.

As he turned back he also maliciously stared at Lin Ming, warning him that he better not be playing tricks here or he would never forgive him.

Lin Ming didn’t bother arguing. At this time, words had become meaningless. This battle would be his only way of proving his words.

“Take these…”

Lin Ming took out thick stacks of divine runic symbols and passed them to Suya, Mo Brightmoon, Fanny Fafa, and the others.

These were divine runic symbols that Lin Ming had drawn up in Tragic Death Valley, all in order to prepare himself for the final battle. Taking them out now when they were all standing on the blade’s edge was the perfect time to do so.

The greatest advantage of a divine runic symbol was that its strength wasn’t too related to the user’s strength. Even if Lin Ming didn’t use them, the strength wouldn’t be much weaker.

Suya and the others received the divine runic symbols, feeling their heavy weight in their hands.

“Use them freely. Don’t bother saving any.” Lin Ming warned.

Suya, Mo Brightmoon, and the others all looked at each other, speechless. Every single one of these divine runic symbols was priceless. To recklessly use them was the same as burning money. But, Lin Ming was extremely rich and also a divine runic master so he had the capital to burn as much as he wanted.

“This boy…”

Dragonscar’s pupils shrank. He was someone that could instantly judge the quality of treasures and he could see that these divine runic symbols were extraordinary!

Rumble rumble rumble!

The ice storm became increasingly intense. The wild winds reverberating in the air were like volcanic eruptions and endless thunderclaps!

The glaciers on the ground were cut open by the ice storm, causing massive fissures to open up. Giant chunks of ice flew into the air. It was like a divine being was using saber light to carve down mountains and open rivers. If a mortal’s body were sucked up into such an ice storm they would instantly perish without even their bones left!

And in this ice storm, the ice energy that was emitting strange and mystical Ice Laws suddenly began to condense together, forming an ice essence soul.

This ice essence soul contained an incomparably terrifying cold energy. All around it, even the void began to freeze and shatter!

Ka ka ka!

As the cold energy condensed to the extreme, cracks appeared in the ice essence soul. Pure freezing ice energy gushed out from the cracks, forming a giant ice blue phoenix in the air!

This ice phoenix looked up towards the heavens and released a shrill cry. Icy cold energy shot up into the air, causing the entirety of the boundless skies to freeze into limitless ice crystals.

Then, its icy eyes that emitted a horrifying aura suddenly locked onto Lin Ming and the others within the Extreme Cold Battle Array.

“Undying Polar Ice!” Xiao Moxian slightly shook as she felt a great pressure push down on her. She was originally of the fire-attribute Dark Phoenix lineage and this Undying Polar Ice was her natural inborn nemesis.

Everyone’s complexion turned solemn. This was a critical situation!

“I have returned from the earth and yet you remain here to offend my invincible divine might. There are no words to excuse your crimes, only death!” The Undying Polar Ice’s dreadful voice rumbled in everyone’s hearts. It was like an invisible mountain was pressing down on them, horrible to the extreme.

For a time, Ice Law runes began to shimmer all over the body of the Undying Polar Ice. It opened its boundless wings and countless white lines spread through the world, carrying with them the endless freezing aura of the Ice Laws that rapidly proliferated like weeds.

Wherever it went, there would be crackling freezing sounds as even space began to rupture apart.

As the white lines collided with Sheng Mei’s Extreme Cold Battle Array, the glass-like battle array emitted the sound of metal striking metal. The entire Extreme Cold Battle Array shivered, clearly withstanding a tremendous pressure.

However, the millions and millions of runes that formed the Extreme Cold Battle Array began to shine with incandescent light. The ancient freezing cold energy began to absorb the aura of the Ice Laws contained in the white lines.

As it was, even though the runes of the Extreme Cold Battle Array were being constantly destroyed, they could simultaneously absorb the aura of the Ice Laws to restore themselves.

“Sheng Mei’s Ice Laws… are above those of the Undying Polar Ice. Far, far above!”

Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. Sheng Mei was indeed Sheng Mei. Even though her strength was suppressed to the Holy Lord realm and she was weaker than the Undying Polar Ice, in terms of Laws she actually suppressed it instead!

“Interesting. Then, let me see just how long you can last!”

The Undying Polar Ice cried out and unraveled its wings to their full extent, wide enough to blot out the skies.

Countless pillars of ice shot out, tearing through the void as they hurtled down onto the people within the Extreme Cold Battle Array.

Dang! Dang! Dang!

The Extreme Cold Battle Array emitted more heavy striking sounds as massive runes shattered again and again, crushed as easily as glass. Many sections broke down, seeming as if the entire array would collapse at any moment.

The Undying Polar Ice wanted to use its absolute strength to trample over Sheng Mei’s Laws.

Sheng Mei’s complexion changed. From her two pupils that resembled six concentric ice crystals, a dark light began to shoot out.

This black light was twined together with runes; it was threatening and suppressive.

Her two pupils seemed to become black vortexes, as deep as the fathomless abyss. A mystic strength constantly revolved within as more and more black light shot out.

This was another variation of pupil-type cultivation methods. The eyes were the windows to the soul and the eye techniques of the spiritas could mean soul attacks, illusions, or a nearly endless number of other attack methods. Many soul cultivation methods used the eyes as the medium to channel soul force. However, compared to Dragon Fang’s Three Lives Pupils, Sheng Mei’s pupil techniques had the flavor of shattering all existence and swallowing it up.

As Sheng Mei’s pupils changed, all of the runes around the Extreme Cold Battle Array began to change with them. They started to dazzle with black ice energy.

In the blink of an eye, the Extreme Cold Battle Array became as dark as ink. Still, faint traces of black freezing energy rose up like countless pieces of frozen ice, covering everyone within.

“Primal Chaos Law Eyes and the Umbral Heaven Ice Array… Empress! You…!”

Dragonscar cried out, his voice shaking. The Primal Chaos Law Eyes and Umbral Heaven Ice Array were higher evolutions of the state of her Laws. If she still had her Empyrean realm strength then using these two secret techniques wouldn’t be difficult at all. But now, Sheng Mei was only at the early Holy Lord realm; she would just barely be able to use these two techniques and she might even have to use up her source soul force!

“Focus on yourself!”

Sheng Mei’s voice was frosty, her expression as calm as ice. Just looking into her eyes that seemed like an endless abyss was enough to make one’s hands and feet go cold. Dragonscar didn’t dare to say another word.

He knew that speaking any more would just disturb her mentality. He could only grit his teeth and focus on his own battle.

The ice pillars that the Undying Polar Ice shot out emitted terrifying sonic booms as they smashed into the Umbral Heaven Ice Array.

The Umbral Heaven Ice Array was different from the Extreme Cold Battle Array. It was far colder and far darker, and the inside rippled with mystical strength. The freezing black darkness formed by the array formation suddenly shot out like the quills of a porcupine to meet those innumerable ice pillars.

With each collision, two types of Ice Laws smashed into each other, tearing apart large tracts of space. But even as space tore open it would be directly frozen shut; it was an extremely unusual sight.

At first glance, it was like the sky was filled with countless snow-white patches.

However, this array formation withstood the endless attacks of the Undying Polar Ice, resisting and weakening them a great deal.

The surrounding earth, even if it were struck by shards of the Ice Laws, would be torn open with wounds as great as rivers and large as mountains. The might of this collision was astonishing.

Seeing this, Lin Ming was shocked.

“Sheng Mei is indeed terrifying! It’s unimaginable that she could display this kind of combat strength at the Holy Lord realm. Not just that, but the power of her Laws seems to be infinitely varied. Each time she uses one of her Laws it is extremely formidable!”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, his eyes touched upon Sheng Mei’s proud and focused face. He discovered that crystal beads of sweat were dripping down her nose and then turning into ice crystals that fell down like pearls.

Without knowing why, Lin Ming was touched by this scene, as if he pitied her and couldn’t endure seeing it.

He could imagine just what sort of pressure Sheng Mei was facing. One only needed to look at Dragonscar’s visibly shaken response to understand it. In this battle he could only succeed, he could not fail!

Taking a deep breath, Lin Ming’s eyes became calm and tranquil. He shut his eyes and closed off his senses, allowing his mind to enter into an ethereal state.

Behind Lin Ming, an auspicious light began to glow. Faint petals fell around him and the sweet trickling murmur of spirit springs filled the air. In this environment of spiritual springs and falling leaves, the phantom of an old tree appeared.

This old tree’s bark was withered and its leaves had mostly fallen off. But, the tree trunk and roots were powerful and vigorous, like the claws of a dragon. The few leaves that remained shined and glittered as if they were carved from the purest green jade.

This was the Bodhi Tree. When Lin Ming was at Mount Potala, he had meditated under a Bodhi Tree and fused the Samsara, ethereal, and Primordius martial intents together. Now, Lin Ming summoned this fused martial intent, forming a pure land of ultimate bliss around him.

No matter what crazy storms raged outside, whatever attacks came crashing down, nothing could disturb him. He had already completely handed over the task of defense to Sheng Mei. As for him, he wholeheartedly invested his focus into adjusting his condition, preparing for the final fatal strike!

Chapter 1725 – The Cold Plum Blossom Resists the Snow And Wind

“Attack together!”

Dragonscar bellowed. He fiercely grit his teeth and all-consuming golden light appeared around him. This soul force flowed down into his hands, turning into a pair of golden soul force swords. As these golden swords were placed together, their golden light was blinding.

His feet touched the ground and then he shot into the skies, hurtling towards the ice pillars!

After Dragonscar, everyone else began to take action. The Divine Mist Divine Kingdom’s Moonpond and Soulsky were the next to move. Soulsky took out a long sword and slashed out 10,000 sword lights. As for Moonpond, her actions were far more unusual. Her slim body became dim in the snowstorm as if she were disappearing. Then, a faintly translucent light appeared around her like a halo; this was an extremely strange variation soul force.

This soul force then unexpectedly fused into the pitch black Umbral Heaven Ice Array.

The entire Umbral Heaven Ice Array began to suddenly shine with a strange light. The runes became increasingly bright and dazzling and the defensive strength of it increased even more.

“Mm? Support-type soul force?” Dragonscar was surprised. He gave Moonpond a deeper look. In his eyes, Moonpond’s talent wasn’t too outstanding, but her support-type soul force was exceedingly rare. Those with a support-type soul force usually didn’t possess much combat strength on their own, but they could use their soul force to support the attacks and defenses of others.

If the one she assisted was weak then her use would be small. But if the one she assisted was strong, then her own use would be several times greater than anything she could accomplish herself. For instance, if Moonpond were to lend her soul force to Sheng Mei, then with Sheng Mei’s comprehension of the Laws, she could use this soul force ten times more effectively!

This would greatly lighten the burden on Sheng Mei.

For a moment, Sheng Mei also opened her eyes, a brilliant light shining in them as she looked at Moonpond.

Rumble rumble rumble!

The space for a thousand miles was torn to shreds by the violent collisions, with countless holes riddled in the void. However, the invisible power of ice forcefully froze and solidified this ruined space immediately.

Besides the area that Sheng Mei’s Umbral Heave Ice Array covered, the vast earth was suffering an apocalyptic disaster. Dreadful shockwaves rang out, smashing into the ground and creating fathomless pits and deep ravines.

In this violent combat, Lin Ming’s divine runic symbols played a considerable role.

Out of the ten people that remained, Suya, Mo Brightmoon, Fanny Fafa, and Thousand Slaughter were the weakest of the bunch. Compared to Sheng Mei, although their added combat strength wasn’t negligible, they could still only play a limited role.

But with Lin Ming’s divine runic symbols in their hands, everything was different. These divine runic symbols could be used several times each. Once activated, they could withstand the impact of an ice pillar and greatly reduce the burden on Sheng Mei.

Hu – hu – hu – !

The blazing light of Heavenly Fire Symbols and Heretical God Symbols lit up the heavens. The blazing flames burned bright. As the ice pillars shot into the seas of fire they began to rapidly melt away.

“Haha, Brother Lin’s divine runic symbols are too fierce!”

Fanny Fafa happily laughed. He grasped the divine runic symbols and shuttled through the ice storm, his entire body wreathed in burning hot flames so that the freezing storm couldn’t harm him. This method of combat was truly admirable.

After a long bombardment of attacks, the Undying Polar Ice in the skies suddenly went quiet.

But at this moment, everyone within the Umbral Heaven Ice Array held their breath. They could feel a dreadful rage brewing.

This was the rage of the Undying Polar Ice.

Billions upon billions of motes of gray ice energy shimmered with ice runes. Then, in the air, they formed ice phoenix claws that were as large as a mountain.

Shua!

These sharp claws carried with them the dreadful anger and will of the Undying Polar Ice. They tore through the air, raising up giant storms and endless waves as they came falling onto the Umbral Heaven Ice Array.

The strength was titanic, like a star exploding.

This momentous impact caused an eye-piercing white radiance to spread out.

Finally, the two different Ice Laws entangled and were destroyed together.

The entire Umbral Heaven Ice Array was torn apart. It was like some great monster had taken a large chunk out of it; it was truly terrifying.

Puff!

Moonpond suddenly shook. She had poured her soul force into the Umbral Heaven Ice Array and had been supporting Sheng Mei this entire time. Now, she trembled and blood shot out from her mouth, ears, nose, eyes, and she nearly fell unconscious where she was.

Because she had fused her own soul force into the Umbral Heaven Ice Array, once the array was damaged, Moonpond and Sheng Mei would naturally bear the brunt of the attack.

And in terms of endurance, Moonpond was far worse than Sheng Mei.

“Junior-apprentice Sister!”

Seeing Moonpond severely wounded, Soulsky was extremely worried and anxious.

Even Sheng Mei paled by several points. She waved her right hand and summoned a moon-white light that covered the severely wounded Moonpond. She said to Soulsky, “She’s fine, there’s just been some damage to her spiritual sea.”

As Sheng Mei spoke, a vast chunk of the Umbral Heaven Ice Array had broken apart and the cold energy from outside was beginning to pour in.

Chi chi chi!

A terrifying cold wind fell upon everyone. Even though they were wearing ice armor which blocked out most of the cold energy, they still felt their bodies chill and their souls nearly freeze over.

Suya And Mo Brightmoon quickly ignited a group defensive divine runic symbol to reduce the pressure for everyone. At the same time, they also protected Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian who were both within Lin Ming’s fused martial intent pure lands.

“This Undying Polar Ice is horrifying!”

Everyone looked up at the seemingly limitless Undying Polar Ice in the skies, their complexions grim and dignified.

“Lin Ming, are you alright?”

Suya asked with concern. However, Lin Ming didn’t respond. He only quietly remained beneath the Bodhi Tree, surrounded in the pure lands of ultimate bliss. All around him, faint Asura runes shimmered in and out like stars in the night sky. It was as if he was already separated from the world.

From far, far away, the eight trial challengers that had run away were watching everything happen within the Umbral Heaven Ice Array.

Seeing that Moonpond was wounded to the point of vomiting blood and yet Lin Ming was still meditating beneath an old tree, all of them were left speechless.

“That woman called Moonpond has already spat out blood but he’s still meditating. It seems he’s really good at sitting.”

“How crafty of him. Even now he hasn’t helped once. And Lin Ming’s woman, she hasn’t done anything either…”

The woman these people referred to was Xiao Moxian. From the start until now, Xiao Moxian had joined together with Lin Ming in his Bodhi Tree pure lands, her mind also entering an ethereal state.

Originally, there were just ten people available. Without Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, that meant there were only eight people left to defend.

The last time there were still 18 people that could defend against the Undying Inferno. Now, there were only eight people. In terms of numbers, they were over half down. In particular, without the unusually strong Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian, it wasn’t strange that the pressure placed on the ones defending was much higher than it should be!

“Lin Ming, that arrogant brat, he said it didn’t matter if we stayed or not! Very well, then let’s stand here and see just what happens to them!”

The eight people that retreated were all of the mindset to watch a good play at the expense of others. They were all looking forwards to Lin Ming and the others falling into peril. This was a normal psychological mindset for these people. Since they weren’t participating in the battle, they naturally didn’t hope that the battle would begin to veer towards a good outcome. In fact, the eight people thought that a good result would be if Lin Ming and his group were all beaten to a pulp, and the best result would be if several of them died.

At the same time, contradictorily they also hoped that nothing would happen to Soul Empress Sheng Mei. Although Sheng Mei came from the 33 Heavens, her etherealness, her perfection, her power, all of that quickly made her into the goddess of all the spiritas in the Asura Road. This was especially true for the eight trial challengers since they were mostly men. Towards Sheng Mei, they held nothing but infatuated admiration.

And at this time, the Undying Polar Ice started its attack once more!

Its massive form soared up into the skies and it began to recklessly absorb all the ice energy between the heavens and earth!

Massive glaciers that were miles wide were shattered into chunks, turned into countless shards of crushed ice that were sucked into the Undying Polar Ice’s body. This momentum alone was already panic-inducing!

“That’s scary…”

“They’re all going to die…”

Many people’s eyes were focused on this manic frenzy that was condensing in the world.

Whether it was human, saint, spiritas, or anything that possessed intelligence, everything would feel an instinctual fear upon facing such a world-shaking momentum!

After brewing for ten breaths of time, a pair of terrifying phoenix claws fell down from the world storm like falling mountains, carrying with them the strength of an unstoppable barrage!

Waves upon waves of icy storms set off massive tides of ice that were tens of thousands of feet high. They were like giant ancient beasts that wanted to swallow the Umbral Heaven Ice Array whole!

“Miss Mo! Mister Fanny! Thousand Slaughter!”

Suya cried out. But in truth, there was no need for her to shout. Mo Brightmoon and the others, including even Soulsky, were rapidly shooting out divine runic symbols as if they weren’t worth money at all.

For a time, the Heretical God Symbol, Heavenly Flame Symbol, all sorts of tyrannical energies wildly galloped through the skies, wreaking havoc where they went, sweeping through the world!

Peng!

In just a moment, all of the blazing flames were swallowed up by the raging waves of ice!

The improved divine runic symbols that Lin Ming drew up were extraordinarily strong. After the raging tsunamis of ice swallowed the fires of the divine runic symbols, they visibly slowed. However, that was only slowed. The momentum, the unparalleled momentum that seemed all-powerful, still impacting towards them as before!

Chapter 1728 – Ice Egg

“They blocked it, they really blocked it!”

Seeing the freezing blue beam of light scatter into sparkling motes in the sky, everyone within the Umbral Heaven Ice Array was excited. They felt as if they had just taken a round trip through the gates of hell.

Even though none of them had much strength left over, they were burning with incomparable joy in their hearts.

“Great! Awesome!”

Dragonscar gripped his fists together. Even though his entire body was soaked in blood, there was a stupidly happy smile on his face.

He was certainly happy. This was because even until the end, Sheng Mei hadn’t burnt any of her soul force. She only used up some origin energy and would be able to fully recover after some rest, not suffering any side effects at all. There wasn’t anything more important than this.

“This Lin Ming is really terrifying!”

Dragonscar looked up at Lin Ming in the sky. At this time, he had opened two Dao Palaces and the power of thunder and fire was twined around his entire body – he gave off a noble and striking momentum.

He originally thought that Lin Ming wouldn’t help in defending, but at the very end it was because of Lin Ming that they were able to cross this most difficult pass.

It wasn’t just Dragonscar that was thinking this, but many others had this thought. Far away, the eight trial challengers were also staring at each other in blank dismay. They had all fled from danger because they didn’t believe this battle could be won.

They didn’t believe that Lin Ming would be able to crush the ice egg and they thought it was unlikely that Sheng Mei would be able to block the Undying Polar Ice’s attacks. Rather, it should be said that even if Sheng Mei was able to block the Undying Polar Ice’s attacks, there was still a high chance they could die here.

In this sort of situation, it was a completely reasonable decision for them to leave. But now, they never imagined that the ten individuals would be able to withstand the attack of the Undying Polar Ice without any deaths.

Hu hu hu –

Cold air recklessly howled. 100,000 feet high in the skies, although the Undying Polar Ice’s final strike had consumed most of its strength, it still hadn’t faded from the world. It continued to maintain its Ice Phoenix form, but its body was extremely blurry.

“You stupid ants, you have truly provoked my anger! Originally I didn’t want to kill you, but now I have changed my mind! All of you can die here!”

The Undying Polar ice roared, its terrifying voice resounding through the world, horrifying!

Bang!

With a loud explosion, the Undying Polar Ice’s ice energy poured into the earth. The glaciers covering the ground began to thicken at an alarming rate!

“What? How can the Undying Polar Ice still have such terrifying strength left?”

Everyone was shocked. They had no idea just what the Undying Polar Ice was doing.

And at this time, the continually quiet Sheng Mei’s complexion changed. She finally understood what the Undying Polar Ice was doing. It had indeed consumed too much energy so it was impossible for it to send out another wave of attacks, but it was still able to use the last dregs of its strength to freeze the space node connecting the fourth and fifth levels!

She said, startled, “Be careful, it is sealing up the space channel to return to the fourth level!”

Sheng Mei’s words shocked everyone present. The Undying Polar Ice wanted to cage them in here!

The fifth level had a multiple space node. If a trial challenger gave up on killing the fifth level’s Overlord, they could retreat to the entrance. After a period of time, the space node would atomically expand and open, forming the channel from the fifth level to the fourth level.

Otherwise, if a trial challenger was able to strike down the fifth level’s Overlord then another spatial node would open, forming the channel from the fifth level to the sixth level.

The Undying Polar Ice used its power to freeze the space node, thus postponing the opening of it. And, in a mere half incense stick of time, the Undying Polar Ice would complete its second nirvana and reform into the Undying Inferno!

Once this happened, it would be impossible for the exhausted group to block its attacks once more!

“Damnit!”

“This beast wants to lock us in here!”

Mo Brightmoon, Moonpond, Dragonscar, and the others with them remained calm. As for the eight trial challengers that had withdrawn to the entrance, they felt their hands and feet turn numb. Once the Undying Polar Ice completed its nirvana, the consequences could be imagined.

And at this time, Sheng Mei was tranquilly sitting in the void, her eyes still emitting a mystic light. A black vortex appeared above her head, absorbing and condensing heaven and earth origin energy so that it wildly merged into her body.

At this time, she was incomparably calm. No matter what happened, she had to restore her strength as soon as possible. Only then would she be able to deal with the ever-shifting situation.

The Undying Polar Ice’s cold eyes focused on Lin Ming. It could clearly feel the killing intent on Lin Ming; this human would surely attack him.

“Hahaha! Human, you want to kill me?

“Interesting! How interesting! Then let me see what methods you have to kill me! You can either forcefully withstand my nine nirvanas or you can pierce through my nirvanic egg. But, in my nirvana state as the Undying Polar Ice, my shell’s defense is even greater than it is as the Undying Inferno! I will wait for you, hahahaha!”

The Undying Polar Ice recklessly laughed. Its body grew smaller and smaller as energy dissipated from it.

Lin Ming’s eyes were icy cold. His aura erupted. The terrifying strength unsealed from the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone still roiled within his body, wanting to break free from him.

He sunk his energy into his inner world. A large tree began to rapidly bloom behind Lin Ming – this was the Heretical God Tree.

But this time, it didn’t seem like a phantom of the Heretical God Tree at all, but a true and sublimely supreme divine tree!

This divine tree was covered with ancient marks, as if an Azure Dragon had forcefully grasped onto the bark. The branches and leaves that decorated the crown were lush and verdant, each one showing off a differently styled leaf.

Some leaves billowed with flames, emitting the source Fire Laws of Heavenly Tribulation.

On other leaves lingered arcs of crackling thunder, roaring and crackling.

This was the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation that lived in harmony above the Heretical God Tree. These two powers of heavenly tribulation emitted an inexplicably powerful pressure, causing the surrounding space to distort as if it would collapse at any moment.

The Heretical God Tree had appeared in its true form and the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation also displayed its true meaning. Faintly, plumes of enchanting flames mixed together with arcs of lightning, like dragons of thunder and fire twining together. This was the peak manifestation of Lin Ming’s understanding of the Heretical God Force.

The powers manifested once more and rose. Within the heavenly tribulation flames, there even seemed to be fire phoenixes crying out and stretching their wings. Within each flame there was a phoenix phantom dancing about like a captivating dream.

The Undying Polar Ice stared at the Heretical God Tree behind Lin Ming, a sneer forming on its face. Finally, its energy was completely exhausted. The endless power of Ice Laws between the heavens and earth collapsed and the blue light swirling in the world also dimmed.

In the next moment, the cold energy within the world seemed to be summoned by something. It wildly rushed towards the Undying Polar Ice, as all the power of Ice Laws retracted into the body of the Undying Polar Ice.

Hum –

Ripples of cold energy crazily circled in the air, forming a giant blue vortex. At the center of this vortex, all of the cold energy gathered together, becoming increasingly thick and tangible as it formed a massive ice egg!

This ice egg was like an oval-shaped ice mountain. All around it, runes shimmered like stars as a mystical bright luster emitted from it.

Lin Ming against the ice egg!

Dark strong winds howled. Lin Ming’s black clothes flapped in the endless ice storm, his hair dancing wildly around him.

Everyone held their breath. In their field of vision, it was like the only image left was Lin Ming’s figure!

This was the final strike. No matter how magnificent or wondrous the previous battle had been, if this final strike were to fail then everything would have been for naught. Everyone here would die…

Then, a spear appeared in Lin Ming’s hand.

This spear appeared so abruptly that no one noticed where it had come from; it was like it had always been in Lin Ming’s hands.

The spear was pitch black without the slightest sheen to it. The spear tip was cold and sharp, bringing with it a primal and boundless aura. The fierce aura seemed as if it were a dragon itself being born within it.

“What spear is that?”

Everyone was shocked. Even from far away they could still feel the horrifying aura on the spear, rendering them unable to move.

They could intuitively feel that this spear was peerless. It certainly must have cut down countless powerhouses during its existence, many of them characters that were unimaginably fearful!

Lin Ming took a deep breath and closed his eyes, feeling the murderous intent within the Black Dragon Spear. With his current strength, he was unable to incite the full power of the spear.

Just attacking once with the Black Dragon Spear would use up the majority of Lin Ming’s strength, so this wasn’t a weapon he could bring out whenever he wanted. For him to bring out this Black Dragon Spear now indicated that he was ready to engage in a final life or death struggle!

With another deep breath, Lin Ming’s body seemed to darken. A thick smell of blood gushed out from within Lin Ming’s body, as if an ancient death god were being born from within him.

His entire figure emitted a strange blood red mist, thick and dense. Dragon scales emerged from beneath Lin Ming’s skin, wrapping around his entire body.

His hair lengthened, growing long. His black hair seemed to become dyed with fresh blood, becoming a vivid bright red.

Pa pa pa!

His joints crackled and popped. His body rose, becoming taller.

Red flames seemed to cover his face, condensing into a blood red mask of curse seals. A mystic power of thunder lingered around his body, turning darker until it became a pitch black armor of thunder that constantly flashed around him.

Lin Ming had awoken the Asura blood within his body, undergoing a body metamorphosis to become an Asura death god!

“What kind of power is this!?”

As everyone looked at Lin Ming who had body metamorphosized into an Asura, and also feeling that overwhelming killing intent that poured forth from his body, even those that were standing far away felt their breath catch in their throats.

The Asura blood contained billions of years of essence of the Asura Road Master. Now that Lin Ming stimulated it, his blood vitality roared to the limit of extreme. To all martial artists, this aura aroused an instinctual fear from within them.

Lin Ming stepped forwards. The void seemed to turn into firm ground beneath his feet, even cracking apart.

Dong. Dong. Dong.

Step by step, Lin Ming became increasingly fast as he hurtled towards the ice egg.

The thunder and fire heavenly tribulation atop the Heretical God Tree was galvanized. It flowed into the Black Dragon Spear, causing countless star-motes of thunder and fire to swirl above it.

Chapter 1729 – Exterminating the Undying Polar Ice

As Lin Ming rushed towards the ice egg, a sharp phoenix cry split through the endless skies.

A blazing flame phoenix rushed out from the crowd of people, flying straight towards Lin Ming.

“That is…!”

Everyone was shocked.

“That is Xiao Moxian!”

Some people recognized Xiao Moxian, but they didn’t dare to believe it was her. At this time, even Xiao Moxian had undergone a body metamorphosis into a Dark Phoenix, just like Sheng Mei’s Ice Phoenix contract beast.

Both of these two phoenixes were of royal lineage!

However, Sheng Mei’s was an Ice Phoenix that was covered with ice whereas Xiao Moxian was a Dark Phoenix, her entire body burning with brilliant flames!

Xiao Moxian cried out, her call echoing in the heavens. Pitch black flames shot out from her body, rolling up into the sky. After completing two nirvanas, she had gained the ability to transform her body into that of a True Phoenix!

Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian flew through the air together, their speed becoming faster and faster, their two figures nearly fusing into one!

Annihilating nirvanic flames completely poured into Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear.

The Black Dragon Spear’s spear light spread a thousand feet further. The tip of the spear point burned with nirvanic flames, perfectly melting together with the power of thunder and fire heavenly tribulation as it tore through space.

Lin Ming gathered all of his potential for this strike. He opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, bringing with him billions and billions of jins of strength. In addition to the Asura blood having been awakened within him, his body felt as if it contained the strength of infinite dragons. Even if a star were to stand in front of Lin Ming, it would be shattered all the same!

Such terrifying strength all rested within the dim Black Dragon Spear. As if the spear itself sensed Lin Ming’s monstrous killing intent, it began to hum with excitement.

Ka ka ka!

It was like a black dragon soaring through the world. The thick mist around the ice egg was constantly torn apart by the Black Dragon Spear. The power of Ice Laws that gushed out was able to freeze anything, but even that was forcefully obliterated by the billowing power of thunder and fire!

The Black Dragon Spear itself weighed more than 10 billion jins. Under such a high speed impact, its destructive might could be imagined! Moreover, the power of thunder and fire that twisted around the shaft was able to suppress the Ice Laws to the limit. With Lin Ming’s powerful mortal bodily strength added on as well as the blood-drenched mystic strength of the Asura blood, the power behind this strike had reached the pinnacle!

Endless power of Fire Laws, endless power of Thunder Laws, Lin Ming’s strike was like a bombardment of endless blood red meteors and falling bolts of thunder.

Rumble rumble rumble!

At this time, Lin Ming’s entire body roiled with inexhaustible power. His entire body had become a blazing meteor, carrying with it an indescribable momentum. Finally, he smashed into the ice egg!

In one potent strike, reckless heavenly tribulation fire, nirvanic flames, destructive thunder tribulation, all of it attacked every inch of the ice egg! The entire ice egg was instantly surrounded by burning flames and raging thunder!

Thunder and fire collided. Each collision could turn endless mountains and rivers to ashes, could evaporate entire seas!

Underneath this strength, the seemingly inexhaustible Ice Law runes atop the ice egg began to tremble and break down!

Ka ka ka!

With a frightening sound, atop the ice egg that possessed incredible defensive powers, a crack appeared!

The Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that Lin Ming practiced gave him an unbelievably sharp insight. Even through the savage and tyrannical onslaught of energy, he was still able to instantly deduce the location of this almost imperceptible crack!

The Ice Laws lingered around this crack, wanting to fuse the crack back together.

But, how could Lin Ming give it such a chance?

In that moment, a sharp light burst out from Lin Ming’s eyes. The Black Dragon Spear seemed to become a flaming black dragon, directly crashing into that singular point on the ice egg!

Kacha!

With a loud explosion, the crack was torn open!

Lin Ming grit his teeth, suppressing the severe pain in his arms and brought the Black Dragon Spear crashing down again and again!

This Black Dragon Spear was over 10 billion jins heavy. Just by wielding it, the inertia alone would cause a massive pressure to rip through Lin Ming’s body. No matter how powerful Lin Ming’s body was, he still couldn’t withstand the burden and his muscles constantly tore.

Blood rained down, gas to the flames.

Lin Ming’s eyes were blood red. Spear after spear, the crack grew longer and longer beneath this unprecedented barrage.

“This… this…”

Those trial challengers looking far off from the distance were shocked. Even Sheng Mei had stopped restoring her wounds, her bright eyes staring straight at Lin Ming, unblinking.

This high intensity barrage continued unabated. Every strike could easily slaughter a World King.

It was hard to imagine that this was the attack of a junior.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Within the horrifying explosions of energy, wild dragon roars and resounding phoenix cries wove together!

The ice egg cracked apart more and more. And at this time, Lin Ming could already feel the cruel soul sealed within the ice egg howl at him in warning.

This was the Overlord of the fifth level – the soul of the Undying Polar Ice!

Lin Ming diabolically grinned. He had already become an incarnation of an Asura, his killing intent blotting out the world like a demon. This cold and gloomy soul aura was only able to arouse his killing desires!

You want to run away?

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He could feel the soul trying to escape deep into the earth!

He certainly remembered what happened when Sheng Mei attacked the Undying Inferno’s egg. Although the egg shell had cracked, the soul had fled underground where it slowly bred into the Undying Polar Ice.

How could Lin Ming allow the same mistake to occur twice?

One difference between him and Sheng Mei was that he thoroughly understood the Asura Laws. He had long been prepared for this.

In an instant, countless Asura runes shot out from Lin Ming’s body, locking in the space for 1000 feet and blocking every possible escape direction of the Undying Polar Ice’s soul.

In the final trial, no matter where, the Asura Laws were the supreme Laws, the ultimate adjudicator; it was a simple task for him to imprison the Undying Polar Ice’s soul that had lost all strength.

“Human, you are seeking death!”

The Undying Polar Ice was enraged. Its cruel and oppressive aura spread into Lin Ming’s mind, but Lin Ming only sneered, “The one seeking death is you!”

Lin Ming burnt 20% of his blood essence with the Gate of Life. Then, his strength erupted once more. With his bloodstained arms, he moved the Black Dragon Spear and stabbed it into the ice egg’s crack, thrusting straight ahead.

“Die!”

Lin Ming’s voice was cold and his expression was ferocious and callous. In that moment, dragons of fire and thunder burst out from the Black Dragon Spear, rumbling into the ice egg!

Bang – Bang – Bang –

The power of thunder and fire detonated. The inside of the ice egg was turned into a cataclysm of flames. The Undying Polar Ice’s soul was caught up in this explosion. It sent out heart-tearing screams as it was burned and refined by these flames!

“Human, you and I cannot live under the same skies!”

“Then I’ll suppress you and take away your chance!” The Asura-metamorphosized Lin Ming wildly laughed. He shot out the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, locking onto the Undying Polar Ice’s soul within the ice egg.

At the same time, the ice egg was unable to withstand the series of explosions occurring within it, and it began to blast open. The massive ice egg started to collapse!

Crash! Bang! Bang!

Endless sheets of ice fell down, covering the ice and even submerging Lin Ming.

In that moment, the Undying Polar Ice had been killed by Lin Ming!

Chapter 1730 – Souls of Ice and Fire

After the ice egg shattered, the scattered pieces of crushed ice were swallowed up by the power of thunder and fire.

Bang!

With a loud blast, the heap of ice exploded, sending countless chunks of ice flying everywhere!

Lin Ming raised the Black Dragon Spear and rushed out from the ice debris. His entire body was covered with blood that was nearly frozen over.

There were countless wounds on his body and muscles all over him were torn. His blood vessels had burst apart in many areas. These wounds weren’t caused by just the Undying Polar Ice, but from the fact that his body couldn’t withstand the burden of the Black Dragon Spear.

The Black Dragon Spear was simply far too heavy. Moreover, the energy needed to move it was mind-boggling. For Lin Ming to destroy the ice egg in a short time, he was forced to overdraw his energy.

At this time, the power from the Asura blood had yet to leave him. He was still in his Asura body metamorphosis state, looking like a death god that crawled out from the blood ponds of hell.

Bang! Crash!

Behind Lin Ming, as the Undying Polar Ice died, massive glaciers began to split apart, melting in raging floods and waterfalls that flooded the land.

Crazy waves soared into the sky. But because there was an invisible force field around Lin Ming, none of the water was able to approach him. It simply swept away from his side.

Seeing this scene, all of the trial challengers held their breath, unable to summon any words.

After Lin Ming activated the Asura blood, his aura was far too powerful. That invisible force field surrounding him gave off a deeply oppressive feeling!

Besides Sheng Mei, even Dragonscar, Soulsky, and the others also felt themselves panting for breath as they faced Lin Ming’s Asura slaughter energy.

As for those eight trial challengers in the distance that had fled earlier, they were even more despondent.

When the ice egg exploded, their chins nearly hit the ground. They couldn’t believe that the fifth level Overlord, the existence that even Sheng Mei couldn’t kill, had been slain by Lin Ming!

How could this have happened?

“The Undying Polar Ice died like this?”

Although the truth was before them, the eight of them still found this reality hard to accept.

This was because they had run away earlier.

Even if the Undying Polar Ice was slain, it had nothing to do with them!

“Maybe… maybe it hasn’t died… Sheng Mei also destroyed the Undying Inferno’s phoenix egg, although she didn’t do it so thoroughly like Lin Ming did. Even so, the Undying Inferno was reborn later. Perhaps the Undying Polar Ice has temporarily gone underground… and it hasn’t died…”

A trial challenger said with unwillingness in his voice. He didn’t want to think that after he had wavered and left earlier, this junior Lin Ming that was far younger than him had completed the seemingly impossible trial, and he had nothing to do with it!

If he couldn’t obtain something, he definitely didn’t want others to.

But at this time, the eight people suddenly shook. A message had popped up in their minds, informing them that the fifth level trial had been completed.

The fifth level Overlord had really died!

And their completion percentage hadn’t increased at all.

“It’s over. We…”

The eight trial challengers stood there in a daze, their eyes losing focus.

The requirement to enter the sixth level was to participate in striking down the fifth level Overlord. But as for them, they had withdrawn in the final stage and had excluded themselves from the trial. In other words, their journey in the final trial had come to an end.

They had missed out on entering the sixth level!

As they realized this, they regretted it to the point of their intestines turning green.

This was the final trial’s sixth level!

The sixth level – just what sort of concept was that?

It was a billion year legend. In all that time, no one had set foot in it!

If they could have stepped foot in the sixth level and returned to their sect then the honor they would have received, the glory, the worship of countless young disciples…

They would also have received the rewards and lucky chances of crossing the fifth level. It might even have changed their lives and affected their future achievements…

Thinking of this, not only did their livers hurt, but their hearts hurt, their balls hurt, and they felt sick as their intestines twisted into knots.

The eight of them stared at each other in dismay, wanting to smack themselves with both hands…

Because of their fear, they had missed out on a once in a lifetime opportunity!

At this time, Sheng Mei, Dragonscar, Brightmoon, and the others had all landed from the sky and were running towards Lin Ming.

They had also received the message from the final trial. Although they had confirmed that the Undying Polar Ice had died, Dragonscar, Fanny Fafa, and the others still weren’t able to regain their composure yet.

Although the Undying Polar Ice had been killed because they all worked together, the truth was that besides Sheng Mei, Lin Ming, and Xiao Moxian, the others only played a limited role in the battle.

In particular Lin Ming – his performance was far too spectacular!

Dragonscar watched as Lin Ming’s body metamorphosis gradually faded away, his scales vanishing into his body. He was at a loss for words. When he first saw Lin Ming he had despised him due to a sense of superiority. But now, he gulped and obediently stood behind Sheng Mei, not daring to say anything.

Originally Lin Ming was supposed to manage offense while Sheng Mei managed defense. But in the end, Sheng Mei had overdrawn her own soul force, causing her to leak blood from her lips, and even during this time Lin Ming was still sitting in meditation, adjusting his condition. Dragonscar had certainly seen this and he felt that all of the advantages were taken by Lin Ming and the price Sheng Mei had to pay was far too high.

But during the Undying Polar Ice’s final attack, the originally meditating Lin Ming suddenly woke up and played an important role in defending against the strike. If it weren’t for Lin Ming then Sheng Mei would have burnt her source soul force and the others might have died.

What Dragonscar felt most unbelievable was that even after Lin Ming moved to help Sheng Mei defend, he still managed to kill the Undying Polar Ice. Such a heaven-defying method truly left Dragonscar no choice but to deeply admire him.

No matter which race it was in the 33 Heavens, all of them admired powerhouses. Dragonscar’s superiority originally came from Sheng Mei. He didn’t believe that there was anyone in existence that could compare to her. At just the sixth revolution, there was nearly no one that could rival her talent beneath the True Divinity realm. As for the seventh, eighth, and ninth revolution, it was even more difficult to imagine.

But now, Lin Ming’s appearance had far surpassed Sheng Mei. The natural feeling of superiority in Dragonscar’s heart was also destroyed.

In the future, Lin Ming would rise to heights that were hard to imagine. It was simply impossible to judge with Dragonscar’s current experiences.

“Lin Ming…”

Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming and took a deep breath. Her voice was faint and ghostly, “I originally thought that humanity’s destiny had come to an end… but I never imagined that after 3.6 billion years, someone like you would appear. Perhaps… you are humanity’s good fortune…”

Sheng Mei’s word seemed like high praise towards Lin Ming, but Lin Ming heard something else. A light shined in his eyes. He asked, “Is humanity’s destiny already exhausted?”

Sheng Mei’s words concealed a hidden meaning. That was that she believed humanity would likely perish in the great world calamity!

“Empress, are you saying that humanity will perish underneath the saints?”

Lin Ming pressed the question.

3.6 billion years ago, another great calamity descended. The barriers separating the 33 Heavens weakened, vanished, allowing alien races to invade. During this great calamity, humanity’s destiny became increasingly weak. True Divinities died, geniuses were on the wane, and compared to the saints and spiritas, humanity became far, far weaker.

Now, if humanity couldn’t overcome this great calamity, it was likely that they would perish.

Sheng Mei didn’t directly respond. Instead, she vaguely said, “Within birth there is death, the cycle of samsara turns again and again. Nothing is permanent. The Heavenly Dao can change… even stars can burn out, much less lives and races. 10 billion years ago, the ancient races were magnificent beyond compare, but even they vanished without a trace… in the river of time, the destruction of humanity isn’t strange at all…”

Sheng Mei seemed as if she was speaking of eternal truths, but within her words, Lin Ming could hear a little regret and unwillingness. Sheng Mei, was she really willing to enter samsara and die?

Inexplicably, Lin Ming thought of the Spiritas Holy Scripture and the Stone of Eternal Life recorded within it…

Eternal Life. To a martial artist, these two words were an irresistible temptation…

“The destruction of humanity isn’t strange at all…?” Lin Ming silently mumbled to himself. He didn’t have an answer to Sheng Mei.

He would not allow humanity to be destroyed in this great calamity. The human race was his roots. Without the roots, how could the leaves survive?

As Sheng Mei and Lin Ming were speaking, the cold energy that the Undying Polar Ice gathered had already dissipated. The entire fifth level had been restored to the state it was at during the beginning. The glaciers melted, turning into lakes. Even the temperature turned back to normal.

And above the largest lake, a gray wheel was slowly floating. Atop this wheel, the phantoms of countless demons appeared. It looked evil to the extreme.

The gazes of all trial challengers were focused on this wheel. This was Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

And within the center of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, there were two masses of soul fire. One soul fire was flame red and emitted a terrifying heat. The other was ice blue and exuded a chilling cold.

Extreme heat and extreme cold, these two masses of soul fire were sealed within the center of the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, peacefully coexisting with each other.

Without needing to think, one could tell that these two masses of soul fire were left behind by the fifth level’s Overlord. The flame red soul fire was the Undying Inferno and the ice blue soul fire was the Undying Polar Ice!

These two masses of soul fire were rare treasures of the fifth level Overlord!

For a time, everyone looked at Lin Ming. As the one who had finally struck down the fifth level Overlord, they would have to ask Lin Ming how he wanted to distribute these two soul fires.

Lin Ming reached out his hand. The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel flew back to him, spinning above his palm.

Seeing the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, Sheng Mei’s hands slightly moved. She could feel that this Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel contained all sorts of mysterious changes, and she was unable to see through any of them for a time.

This cultivation method was obviously extraordinary.

Lin Ming gently touched the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, guiding the ice blue soul fire to fly out. As the ice blue soul fire flew through the air, it left behind a path of frost, even freezing the void around it.

From far away, the trial challengers could feel a cruel and evil aura from this mass of ice blue flames. This was the Undying Polar Ice’s tyrannical soul! Although its body had been destroyed, its soul hadn’t died!

Lin Ming looked at Sheng Mei. With a flick of his fingers, this soul fire flew towards her.

“Soul Empress, the polar ice soul fire that the fifth level Overlord left behind will be handed over to you. The remnant will of the Undying Polar Ice is still within and it won’t be easy to absorb, but I don’t think this can stop the Soul Empress…”

During this trial, Soul Empress Sheng Mei’s role was without doubt; she accounted for nearly half the effort. By all reasonable principles, half of the treasures that the fifth level Overlord left should be given to her.

In particular, the Undying Polar Ice was a treasure of the extreme cold attribute. It was inestimably useful to Sheng Mei and could be considered a great lucky chance.

As for the others, it was impossible for them to absorb it.

Chapter 1731 – Lin Ming’s Completion Percent

Sheng Mei stretched out her pure white hands and cradled the Undying Polar Ice’s soul fire.

She cultivated the Ice Laws and had an extremely keen insight into the power of ice. She could feel that the Undying Polar Ice’s soul fire in her hands possessed an incredibly pure and potent essence of ice. Although she had attainments in the Ice Laws and had absorbed many ice-attribute heavenly materials, none of those heavenly materials were able to compare to the current soul fire in her hands.

The rewards that the Asura Road Master left behind were truly extraordinary!

Taking a deep breath, Sheng Mei received the Undying Polar Ice’s soul fire. She truly did need this. With this soul fire, she had hopes that her strength would be able to rise in a short period of time. This would create a much better foundation for when she had to step into the Grand Reincarnation Art’s seventh revolution.

And at this time, within Lin Ming’s hands, there was still one more soul fire. This soul fire originated from the Undying Inferno and was the polar opposite of the Undying Polar Ice. The heat emanating from this soul fire was astonishing, strong enough that it seemed as if it would melt down the void.

Lin Ming’s fingers moved and he formed runes of the Asura Heavenly Dao to completely seal the Undying Inferno’s soul fire. Then, he flicked his fingers and this soul fire flew towards Xiao Moxian.

“Xian’er, this soul fire is for you.”

The ball of flames fluttered through the air and into Xiao Moxian’s hands.

Xiao Moxian’s pitch black eyes shined as she stared at the soul fire in front of her. She could sense a strong attraction from it, as if its attributes were simply tailor-made for her.

Xiao Moxian’s God Beast bloodline originated from the Dark Phoenix. The Dark Phoenix originally represented the idea of destruction, and this Undying Inferno’s soul fire also contained the attribute of destruction!

As long as she absorbed this soul fire then she could complete her third nirvana in a short period of time, allowing her strength to further increase and break into the Holy Lord realm.

However, Xiao Moxian looked at Lin Ming and hesitated for a moment. “Big Brother Lin, you also cultivate the Fire Laws. If your heavenly tribulation fire absorbs this soul fire it will likely evolve once more. If you give this to me then there’s nothing left for you.

“Moreover… you have to open the third Dao Palace soon. If I remember correctly, the third Dao Palace is the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, and you need to form the foundation of the Dao Palace with the source energies within you. Big Brother Lin’s two source energies should be fire and thunder, but in order to continue you will need a top grade Thunder Source and top grade Fire Elemental to form the foundation of the third Dao Palace. This Undying Inferno’s soul fire is just perfect for that.”

As Xiao Moxian spoke, Lin Ming shook his head, “When I form the foundation for the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, it’s enough for me to use an Empyrean level Fire Elemental and Thunder Source. As for the Undying Inferno’s soul fire, the truth is that it isn’t a Fire Elemental at all, and its characteristics are too strong. Trying to use it to form the foundation for the Extreme Polar Dao Palace is far too wasteful. Moreover, I would need to find a Thunder Source on the same level which would be nearly impossible.”

Currently, the soul fire in Xiao Moxian’s palm could be considered peak True Divinity in grade.

If Lin Ming used such precious flames to form a part of the third Dao Palace’s foundation, that was simply wasting the treasures of heaven.

Moreover, Lin Ming dual cultivated fire and thunder. If his attributes were imbalanced then that wouldn’t be good for him at all.

Rather, if he were to leave it to Xiao Moxian, someone who only cultivated the Fire Laws, then she would be able to display the peak potential of this soul fire!

And… the more powerful Xiao Moxian was, the more advantages Lin Ming would have when they dual cultivated.

As Lin Ming said this, Xiao Moxian didn’t decline any more. She carefully took the sealed soul fire and put it away. As for the Fire Elemental that Lin Ming needed for the third Dao Palace, Xiao Moxian also seemed to have some possible ideas…

At this time, Lin Ming turned to everyone else. He said, “I’m sorry… the fifth level Overlord only left behind two treasures. After dividing them, there isn’t anything left for you all… if I find some precious spirit treasures or materials from the next level, I will offer them to you all first. What do you think?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s apologetic tone, Fanny Fafa chuckled. “Brother Lin, where do those words come from? In truth, from start to finish we haven’t been able to help much at all, especially me. Even if I did help several times, what I used were Brother Lin’s divine runic symbols. At the end, we all had to depend on Brother Lin, the Soul Empress, and Miss Xian’er in order to bring down the fifth level Overlord. Basically, all of us have already benefited far more than we put in. Not only did our completion percentage increase considerably but we also have a chance of experiencing the legendary sixth level. If any of us were to think of divvying up your treasures at this time then our facial skin would be far too thick.”

Everyone approved of Fanny Fafa’s words. In the battle, they had only been able to play a limited role. It was fine for Lin Ming to be polite to them, but it went against all their morals to take advantage of the situation and demand treasures.

To be able to obtain more completion percentage was something they were more than satisfied with. As for those eight trial challengers that had withdrawn earlier and thus didn’t participate in bringing down the Undying Polar Ice, all of them had despondent expressions and were sick with regret.

As everyone was discussing rewards, another piece of information appeared in their minds. And, this information was their current completion percentage after striking down the fifth level Overlord!

Immediately, everyone held their breath, their minds alert.

If everything went as expected, this completion percentage would be their final result. None of them thought they would be able to pass the sixth level.

Lin Ming also focused his mind and carefully listened to his own completion percentage. He didn’t know what his performance in the fifth level was like. The final trial was just far too difficult; he didn’t have any hopes that he would be able to perfectly complete it.

Lin Ming looked up and subconsciously glanced at Sheng Mei. He saw that Sheng Mei was also looking at him.

Two pairs of eyes met. Sheng Mei faintly smiled and didn’t speak. It was clear that they were both curious as to what the other’s result was.

The results were soon confirmed. Everyone glanced at each other, a happy expression on their faces.

“What are all your completion percentages?”

Someone couldn’t help but ask.

“I am 71%. That’s far better than what I was thinking!”

Fanny Fafa was the first to speak. As long as one could obtain at least 70%, that was an extremely good result.

If Bigflame and the Divine Void Crown Prince hadn’t been massacred by Lin Ming on the fourth level, their final completion percentage might be around 75.

Only an unrivalled genius of an entire race would be able to surpass 80%.

“Mine is 72%...”

“Mine is 70%...”

Mo Brightmoon and Suya each said. When they passed through the Gate of Laws, their completion percentage was in the thirties. After passing through the fourth level and the Divine Seal Altar, their completion percentage grew by another 26-27%. As for the fifth level, they obtained less than 10% for defeating the Undying Inferno and Undying Polar Ice. This was because their contributions to the battle weren’t too much.

Even so, they were more than satisfied. Their completion percentage from the fifth floor was like a free reward. If it weren’t for Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, they wouldn’t have received anything at all.

Everyone looked at Moonpond and Soulsky. The two of them seemed to have an amazing background and their talent was superb. Their completion percentage should be relatively high.

“77%.”

“Mine is 78%.”

The two people spoke. Moonpond’s completion percentage was a point higher than Soulsky’s. This was because Moonpond’s supportive cultivation method had played a significant role in defending against the Undying Polar Ice.

Then, there was Dragonscar.

His completion percentage was 79, just shy of reaching 80.

“What a pity…”

Someone said.

Dragonscar shook his head. “It’s not a pity at all. If Lin Ming didn’t kill the Undying Polar Ice then my score would have been at most 76%...”

As Dragonscar spoke, he turned Lin Ming. What he was interested in the most was what Lin Ming, Sheng Mei, and Xiao Moxian’s final scores were.

Without a doubt, all three of them should surpass 85%.

In fact, when the Undying Inferno transformed into the Undying Polar Ice, Lin Ming’s completion percentage was already 85. As for Sheng Mei, she was just a tad over Lin Ming, with 86%!

This time, it was hard to imagine how high their completion percentage would go… would it possibly be at 90%?

This incredulous thought immediately flashed through many people’s minds.

Everyone held their breath and there was even a bit of awe as they looked at Lin Ming. 90%, that was truly a myth! It could be said someone who was bound to become a True Divinity would reach around 85, 87, or 88%.

It was also because of this that they all faintly felt that wanting to reach 90% was just impossible.

“Xian’er, what did you get?” Lin Ming looked at Xiao Moxian.

“87…” Xiao Moxian smoothed out her hair and chuckled, revealing two cute canines as she smiled at Lin Ming.

This number left everyone sucking in a breath of cold air.

87%. Without a doubt, that was truly at the level to become a True Divinity. In other words, the young black-clothed girl that stood beside Lin Ming would become a True Divinity in the future!

Although no one was surprised by this result, to have the final trial approve and recognize this result, everyone still found it hard to accept.

This was because in their original impression, this black-clothed girl was only Lin Ming’s woman. And if his woman was so powerful, how could there still be any justice left in the world!

“Soul Empress?”

Lin Ming looked at Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei thought for a moment and then calmly said, “I have two points more than Miss Xian’er.”

“89%!?”

Someone cried out in shock. This number was just one point from reaching 90%!

“Too great!” Dragonscar couldn’t help but grip his fists behind Sheng Mei, excited from his heart. It had to be known that Sheng Mei was only in her sixth revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art. At this pace, she would be able to break past 90% during her seventh revolution.

As for the eighth and ninth revolution, that would be even higher!

Sheng Mei could clearly see Dragonscar’s thoughts. She shook her head, saying, “You’re overthinking this. Even during my seventh revolution it will be impossible for me to break this record. During the seventh revolution, if I come alone it will be impossible for me to kill the fifth level Overlord. And if I ask someone to help, our completion percentage will inevitably be divided, thus 89% is already my limit. The only exception is if… I can perfectly pass the Asura level Gate of Laws…”

As Sheng Mei spoke, everyone was left flabbergasted. Sheng Mei said she was stuck at 89%. Although this was only a single percent from 90, the truth was that this single percent was a massive gap!

Thus it could be seen just how great the disparity was from a completion percentage in the eighties and one at 90.

As everyone was thinking this, they recalled Sheng Mei’s words and seemed to remember something. They all looked towards Lin Ming.

When Sheng Mei said that she would need to perfectly pass the Asura level Gate of Laws to reach 90%... hadn’t Lin Ming passed through that!?

If so…

“Sir Lin, your completion percentage…”

Suya’s voice trembled as she asked this.

Lin Ming took a light breath and then said, “My completion percentage is… 92%.”

Chapter 1734 – Emperor Jade

Pressing his hands over the lid of the ancient bronze coffin, Lin Ming released the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. Strength erupted within his body, rising to tens of billions of jins. With a loud rumbling sound, the dustless lid that had lain over the ancient bronze coffin for billions of years was pushed open by Lin Ming!

And as Lin Ming pushed open the cover, the entire sixth level began to shake, as if some ancient great beast was awakening here!

Ka ka ka!

The ground shook and everything began to collapse in massive tracts, revealing a pitch black abyss. And from this abyss, a massive black divine stone slowly rose out.

This is…

Lin Ming’s mind shook. Unconsciously, his hands stopped pushing open the ancient coffin’s lid. His eyes looked down and fixed upon that massive black divine stone. This black divine stone was clearly a sculpture, and one that he had seen before! This sculpture was the same as the giant stone sculpture in the Asura level Gate of Laws. It was a sculpture of an Asura war god!

This Asura war god grasped a black dragon spear and wore a suit of battle armor. His body was covered in dragon scales and his hair was wild and free, his momentum awe-inspiring!

Standing in front of this Asura sculpture, Lin Ming could feel a rich slaughter energy rolling off of it, making it difficult to breathe. Even his heart was flooded with tyrannical, archaic, and unbelievably cruel emotions, making one almost lose their sense of self.

In the sixth level, this Asura war god sculpture had reappeared after opening the ancient bronze coffin. Just what was this sculpture made from?

Lin Ming was somewhat startled. If the sixth level contained such a mechanic, there had to be some special significance to it.

Lin Ming’s first guess was that the soul avatar that the Asura Road Master forged might be sealed within this Asura war god sculpture. But, he soon rejected this idea.

This was because after pushing open the ancient bronze coffin, he was able to sense a vast soul aura coming from within it. It was clear that the soul avatar was slumbering within the coffin.

Then this Asura sculpture…

Lin Ming pondered for a moment and walked towards the sculpture. As he carefully probed it, he faintly discovered that there was an extremely potent power of Space Laws contained within it. All of the power of space within the sixth level seemed to be attracted by the sculpture and was slowly converging towards it.

“This is… a space node?”

Lin Ming thought. There was a space node contained within the Asura sculpture!

And in the final trial, this sort of space node undoubtedly represented the entrance to the next level.

The seventh level!?

Lin Ming took a deep breath. If the sixth level was only for rewards, then going by previous experiences his completion percentage wouldn’t increase here. The truly difficult to pass test would be the seventh level!

And this level would inevitably be far more difficult than the fifth level. Even Lin Ming didn’t believe he had the slightest chance of passing the level. He could try to go as far as he could in the seventh level with the mindset of obtaining as much completion percentage as possible.

“The space node to enter the seventh level is actually sealed in the Asura sculpture… I wonder what the meaning behind it is? Is there something special about this sculpture?”

Lin Ming thought it was strange. It would be reasonable for the entrance to the seventh level to directly open, but the entrance was actually sealed within the Asura sculpture. Lin Ming’s first thought was that this Asura sculpture might be related to some test.

In the final trial, from the second to third level he had to pass through the Gate of Laws and from the fourth level to fifth level he had to ascend the Divine Seal Altar. These two passages between levels hadn’t been easy to pass at all.

Thus, if this Asura sculpture was some sort of test then it wouldn’t be surprising at all.

As Lin Ming was thinking this, a strange image suddenly caught his attention.

He discovered that atop the Asura sculpture’s war armor, there were three grooves lying side-by-side, and Lin Ming had seen the shape of these grooves before!

Near these grooves, there were also several lines of characters carved into the stone. These words were in the same language as the Asura Sutra.

What they said was –

“33 Heavens, Asura inheritance, passed down to the unrivalled genius, passed down to the one with great destiny, passed down to the fated one!”

“The word of Fate, to be predestined or not, if you are fated then even through the endless universes you will still find my inheritance, but if you are not fated then even if your talent is unrivalled you shall never enter the gate.”

“I left behind three emperor jades of essence, energy, and divine. The emperor jades have spiritual powers, and if you are fated then they shall fall into your hands. If you lack fate then no matter how much hardship you undergo to find them you shall never succeed. Bring the three emperor jades to this land and open wide the gates to the seventh level.”

Lin Ming was startled after reading these carved words beside the grooves.

The final inheritance of the Asura Road. In order to receive it, one needed to be an unrivalled existence, possess a great destiny, and also be the fated one. A trial challenger required all three of these characteristics in order to obtain the approval of the inheritance.

The first several levels of the final trial, including the entire test that was the Asura Road itself, could be considered repeated verifications of a trial challenger’s talent and destiny. But in order to go from the sixth level to the seventh level, one needed ‘fate’.

The manifestation of the symbol of fate was to possess the three token emperor jades of ‘essence, energy, and divine’!

Only by simultaneously possessing all three emperor jades could one enter the seventh level.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and retrieved two jade pendants from his spatial ring. Rather, it was more accurate to say that there was one complete jade pendant and one fragment.

This complete jade pendant had been obtained by Lin Ming in the Hunter game. Because of this jade pendant, Lin Ming had been able to enter God Burying Ridge, fall into Tragic Death Valley, and escape from there and continually pass through absolute killing zones. Utilizing those killing zones, Lin Ming had brought down three top masters: Mister Zhou, Mister Ash Murder, and Tian Mingzi.

It could be said that Lin Ming’s life was saved because of this emperor jade.

As for the emperor jade fragment, Lin Ming had bought that from Old Xue’s stall at the Divine Runic Masters Guild.

Old Xue didn’t know what this emperor jade fragment was, but his intuition told him it was unusual. Yet no matter how much he studied it over the years, he had never been able to discern its secrets. Finally, he thought it was some Empyrean spirit treasure fragment and sold it to Lin Ming.

Because this emperor jade fragment had too many flaws in the Asura dao patterns within it, it wasn’t too valuable. Even so, Lin Ming kept it in his spatial ring.

Now, taking out these two emperor jades, they just happened to match with the shape of the grooves.

Without a doubt, he would have to collect all three emperor jades and then place them in the grooves to open the portal to the seventh level.

If he couldn’t, then he could only stare helplessly on at the entrance to the seventh level, but without the ability to enter.

“This sort of rule…”

Lin Ming was speechless.

According to any common logic, in the massive Asura Road, to find three tiny emperor jades was as difficult as searching for a needle in the endless ocean. It could even be called an impossible mission.

But, according to that Asura Road Master’s viewpoint, these three emperor jades were extraordinary. They were emperor jades of ‘fate’, and possessed strange and incredible Laws. As long as one’s fate reached a certain point, one wouldn’t even need to look for these emperor jades, but they would take the initiative to seek out the person instead.

If one couldn’t collect all three emperor jades, then one could only say that their fate was lacking.

“My fate is lacking…”

Lin Ming looked at the whole emperor jade and the emperor jade fragment in his hands, bitterly smiling. He thought that his lucky chances were enormous to be able to obtain two emperor jades so far, but after entering the sixth level he realized that his fate was insufficient. In order to enter the seventh level he needed to obtain all three emperor jades.

Moreover… the second emperor jade in his hands was already fragmented. If it was a token left behind by the Asura Road Master, how could it break apart so easily?

This question flashed through Lin Ming’s mind. He felt that this didn’t make sense at all.

He tarried in front of the sculpture for some time. Then, after some hesitation, he tried to place the two emperor jades into their respective grooves.

These three grooves were in different shapes. Lin Ming first put in the complete emperor jade; the shape fit in perfectly.

Then, Lin Ming tried to fit in the emperor jade fragment into another groove.

At this time, something startling occurred.

When the broken emperor jade was placed into the groove, it suddenly began to emit a dim light. Countless motes of light gathered into the emperor jade, and in the next moment the emperor jade melted into liquid light that covered the entire groove.

“Mm? This is…”

Lin Ming’s eyes widened. After several breaths of time the liquid slowly solidified, forming the complete emperor jade that perfectly fit into the groove.

“The emperor jades can repair themselves?”

Lin Ming mumbled, dumbfounded.

If so, then even if the emperor jade was shattered into several fragments it would be fine as long as he could obtain one. To him, this could just reluctantly be called good news.

But… he simply had no clues about the whereabouts of the third emperor jade. Where would he be able to find it?

Chapter 1735 – Soul Spring Divine Embryo

The appearance of the emperor jades also announced that Lin Ming’s adventure through the final trial had come to an end. No matter what, it was impossible for him to find the third emperor jade any time soon.

With this, his final trial completion percentage was 92.

The truth was that in the trial of the fifth level, Lin Ming hadn’t been able to perfectly complete it. In the end, he was simply too young and his comprehension of Laws was lacking. After he became a World King or Empyrean and then returned to the final trial once more, he might be able to perfectly complete the fifth level.

As these thoughts raced through his mind, Lin Ming stepped in front of the ancient bronze coffin. He placed his hand on the coffin lid, his body straining as it bent like a bow.

His muscles tensed and strength surged from his feet. Lin Ming pushed open the ancient coffin’s lid once more, thoroughly opening it.

The moment that the ancient coffin was opened, Lin Ming took a deep breath and drew backwards. The Phoenix Blood Spear had already leapt into his hands.

A raging strength surged in Lin Ming’s meridians. He looked at the ancient coffin with his guard up in order to prevent any possible dangers.

The heavy ancient coffin quietly lay on the invisible land of the sixth level. After being opened by Lin Ming, there was no movement from within.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment. All he saw was a pitch black aura, shimmering with glittering runes, gushing over the edges of the ancient coffin. It was impossible to see what was inside.

However, those waves of black aura caused his heart to sway. It was like there was an endless abyss contained within, bringing with it a mystical strength that seemed as if it could swallow his consciousness.

“This… what a vigorous and pure soul force!”

Lin Ming was shocked. He suddenly realized that the pitch black aura that was overflowing from the coffin like a waterfall was actually soul force so dense that it had substantialized. Even though his soul force had been tempered harder than diamonds, it was still seriously influenced. He could feel an inexplicable danger.

As if there was something dangerous lying dormant beneath that black fog.

“Open!”

After rushing all the way to the sixth level, Lin Ming’s will and decisiveness were incomparably solid. Although this black fog soul force was terrifying, it only served to stimulate his curiosity even more.

The Phoenix Blood Spear had been through countless slaughters and had been tempered numerous times by Lin Ming. Thrusting out the spear, it was like a blood phoenix flew forth. Endless mystic strength shined and even runes seemed to fall like large glowing stars.

Bang!

In a moment, hundreds of millions of spear lights were shot out at once. The fog of soul force that seemed as if it came from nether springs emitted a crackling sound. The soul force suddenly scattered as it was forcefully shaken out.

Rah!

With a sudden loud roar, a demonic energy filled with cruelty rushed out from the ancient coffin.

A pitch black demonic energy formed into a giant demon hand. It sparkled with dark metallic light and clashed with the Phoenix Blood Spear.

Lin Ming was forced backwards several steps, each step pressing down with 10 billion jins of force. Every step he took cracked open the void and his blood vitality tumbled. He suddenly found his steps unsteady.

As for that demon hand, it faded after colliding with the Phoenix Blood Spear.

Then, the contents of the ancient coffin were revealed to Lin Ming.

As he clearly saw what was inside, his pupils shrank.

“This is…”

Within the coffin, a massive body appeared, one over 50 feet high that exuded the boundless pressure of a king. This body wore a black crown emblazoned with purple and gold designs as well as a black nine dragon robe.

This black purple-gold crown was covered with strings of pearls, each pearl as large as a person’s skull. Each one was formed from a demon king, each of them roaring and howling and releasing a fierce and sinister aura.

The entire purple-gold crown had countless strings of pearls covering it. In other words, there were countless demons struggling atop it.

As for the black nine dragon robe, it was flowing with nine True Dragons that were brimming with death energy. They winded about the robe, carrying an indescribably massive soul force. Occasionally, the head of a dragon would drill out of the robe, its crimson greed-filled eyes staring at Lin Ming.

“This is the divine soul avatar refined by the Asura Road Master!?” Lin Ming’s eyes widened, staring unblinkingly at the nine dragon imperial robe.

Suddenly, he could feel a rush of heat within his body. The suppressed Asura blood in his body surged and Lin Ming was able to catch a glimpse of something unusual.

In the space of the final trial, the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws were ubiquitous, pervading every inch of this land.

As the Asura blood throbbed, Lin Ming was able to discover that this demon king’s demonic energy body was not a true material body, but one that was created from resentment and violence-filled soul force.

And deeper within, there was an even darker and vaster soul force.

That mass of soul force was as vast as the ocean. As the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws that Lin Ming sent in to probe touched this soul force, they were immediately swallowed clean.

“This is the Nether Springs Divine Embryo… in the past when I fought the ancient races, cutting down countless rulers, the souls of these sovereigns were used by me, tempered in the Great Dao of the 33 Heavens and cast into this Nether Springs Divine Embryo.

“This Nether Springs Divine Embryo is the spirit essence avatar of the Asura Sutra’s second volume. This avatar has a potent inborn soul force and its potential is limitless. It can seize the good fortune of the world and arouse the jealousy of the Great Dao… this avatar can hold life essence and follow the thoughts of the main body…”

Suddenly, a deep and mysterious voice transmitted from the deepest depths of the dark, sounding out in Lin Ming’s consciousness.

Lin Ming immediately understood that this was a wisp of thought that the Asura Road Master had left behind in this space. Even after billions of years it hadn’t been extinguished.

“…A portion of these ancient sovereigns’ resentment has yet to be melted away… if you wish to completely obtain this divine soul avatar, you must defeat the remaining resentment of these ancient sovereigns…”

As the voice spoke to here, it scattered away.

He had to wipe out the remaining power of resentment?

Lin Ming’s eyes began to shine with a fighting spirit. Every ancient sovereign had experienced hundreds of millions of years of war and slaughter. Through the endless years, they remained until now, not extinguishing even in this vast space. Just how terrifying had they been?

Facing this demon king body that wore a black purple-gold crown in front of him, Lin Ming realized it was formed from the resentment of these ancient sovereigns.

Even though it was only a tiny portion of resentment left behind by the remnant souls of these ancient sovereigns, and even though 10 billion years of weakening had passed, they absolutely had to be extremely terrifying existences.

However, if he wanted to obtain the acknowledgement of the Asura Road Master as well as this divine soul avatar, this was what he would have to do. Lin Ming’s eyes blazed with a zealous fighting spirit as he hurtled himself towards that demon king body.

Bang!

The demon king body’s endless demonic energy suddenly rushed into Lin Ming’s body!

Lin Ming’s eyes turned vacant. Countless black curse seals appeared over his body, as if dark earthworms were wriggling all over him.

His two pupils had already become black vortexes, slowly spinning around.

Lin Ming’s demonic energy soared to the heavens. His body remained motionless. His fists stayed in the center of the divine soul avatar’s black fog, like he had turned to stone.

But in his mind, Lin Ming had fallen into a strange demonic illusion world.

In front of him was an endlessly bleak world, like an eternal twilight was laid out before him.

Countless skeletons spread out beneath his feet, each skeleton as large as a mountain.

This entire space was filled with a fierce and cruel hostility, thick to the point that one could choke on it.

Nine black dragons of different shapes loomed on the horizon, their bodies like mountain ranges, the outline of their figures like gray clouds.

Dozens of fierce ancient sovereigns floated in front of Lin Ming, all of them exuding the pressure of a king.

Each one had a terrifying aura, able to summon wind and thunder by raising their hands or taking a step. Faint arcs of electricity shimmered in their eyes.

Without a word, the nine black dragons on the horizon as well as the dozens of ancient demon kings all hurtled towards Lin Ming.

Lin Ming knew that the significance of this battle was monumental. His chest began to burn with a fervid fighting intent.

Roar!

An Azure Dragon burst out from Lin Ming’s body, rising to the skies.

With a phoenix cry, a Fire Phoenix roiling with flames shot out from Lin Ming’s body.

One dragon, one phoenix, they were the True Dragon bloodline and Fire Phoenix bloodline within Lin Ming’s body. At this time, in the battle within his consciousness, they manifested into their source spirits.

At the same time, the Phoenix Blood Spear in Lin Ming’s hand also cried out. Endless raging flames melted onto his body, contouring onto him and forming a suit of flame armor, giving him the feeling of infinite strength. This Phoenix Blood Spear was not the true Phoenix Blood Spear, but the manifestation of the Phoenix Blood Spear’s artifact spirit that had yet to truly awaken.

Meanwhile, behind Lin Ming, the Heretical God Tree appeared, its boughs growing into the heavens.

This giant tree seemed as if it could tear down the world, emitting the inexhaustible power of the Heretical God Force. On every leaf, there were tiny fire phoenixes and thunder dragons flying about.

This was the spirit of the Heretical God Tree as well as the auras of heaven and thunder heavenly tribulation within Lin Ming’s body.

As more and more Laws appeared like overlapping waves, the momentum of Lin Ming’s soul force began to rise without end.

As the threatening ancient sovereigns rushed forth, the void split in half and two incomparably massive stars appeared.

A palace shimmered atop each of these stars, radiating a mystical power.

These were the Purple Temple Dao Palace and Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace that Lin Ming had broken through.

These two Dao Palaces, although they couldn’t manifest in the outer world, they had always existed in Lin Ming’s sea of consciousness, exuding a vast aura of the Heavenly Dao.

In this sort of soul force collision, the function of the two Dao Palaces to strengthen Lin Ming’s body wasn’t useful at all.

However, these two Dao Palaces represented the Heavenly Dao Laws and were more than enough to clash with the residual resentment of these ancient sovereigns.

Bang! Bang!

The two titanic stars gushed with endless starlight, bringing with them the two Dao Palaces as they came crashing down. Two of the mountain range-like black dragons rushed towards Lin Ming’s body that was formed from soul force, but were crushed to nothing by these two Dao Palaces.

Bang –

The two stars fell onto the earth along with the ruined bodies of those black dragons.

Just how immense was the impact of this soul force? Even the dozens of ancient sovereigns, formed by resentment-filled soul force, were struck by the shockwaves. The entire world began to collapse.

The world transformed. Lin Ming felt endless waves of soul force swell towards him from all directions, entering his body.

A golden sea tumbled beneath him. They had unexpectedly arrived at his sea of consciousness.

A battle of soul force was highly risky, as well as incredibly strange.

After arriving at his own sea of consciousness, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. His body began to grow, his head reaching higher than the clouds as he became even larger than the remnant souls of these ancient sovereigns.

He formed fists with his hands and smashed out at one of the ancient sovereigns.

The Heretical God Tree behind Lin Ming also began to move. Every branch emitted strange Laws that drilled into the void, sweeping towards those ancient sovereigns.

Infinite heavenly tribulation fire gushed out into space, followed by miniature thunder dragons that wove together, forming a mystic thunderfire in space.

In that moment, Lin Ming’s soul force surged. He began to engage the group of ancient sovereigns in a brutal melee, mercilessly striking them!

Chapter 1737 – Three Years

Lin Ming had already decided his plans. Until the time within the final trial came to an end, he would stay in the sixth level and study the Asura Sutra.

In any case, this was the sixth level reward space. No matter who was at the sixth level they would have their own lucky chance. Lin Ming wouldn’t be able to find Xiao Moxian for some time nor was he worried for her because the sixth level simply didn’t have any dangers.

As for the seventh level, if he couldn’t go there then it was definitely impossible for others.

Lin Ming focused all of his attention on the ancient bronze book. As his thoughts moved, his entire being floated up until he was a mere 10 feet away from the bronze book. He could feel the powerful soul aura emanating from the words.

As his mind was immersed in the Asura Sutra, Lin Ming could feel the words filled with a thick demonic energy rush towards him, as if each word was an imposing demon god.

Seemingly because he had refined his second avatar, when Lin Ming looked through the ancient bronze book again, he seemed to have even more insights into it. Within his sea of consciousness, the world shook as if giant demon gods had appeared. The skies roiled as all sorts of mystical runes formed Law lines around these illusory demon gods…

Then, giant golden swords appeared, slicing through the demonic energy that rolled off of these demon phantoms.

Like this, Lin Ming floated in front of the ancient bronze book. Every time he looked at a word he would have to suppress the soul force emanating from it, and then carefully ponder the endless true meanings contained within.

Years passed without sense of time.

On the words of the ancient bronze book, every divine soul aura was gradually suppressed by Lin Ming.

Each pitch black character formed a star that floated high above his sea of consciousness.

In the end, the soul force that shimmered above the ancient bronze book turned gloomy.

The entire Asura Sutra Second Volume appeared in Lin Ming’s sea of consciousness.

This second volume spoke about cultivating one’s soul force. Compared to the soul force cultivation method passed down by Empyrean Divine Mist, it contained far more unique and incomprehensible mysteries.

Lin Ming had already assiduously cultivated the first volume of the Asura Sutra and had formed a foundation through doing so. Now, it was twice as easy for him to cultivate the second volume while spending half the effort. The true meaning of every word, every rune’s Law lines, all of them danced in the air, allowing him to gradually comprehend the essence of their mysteries.

Slowly, every mysterious word of the Asura Sutra Volume Two dazzled with strange soul force as they slowly danced around Lin Ming…

Lin Ming’s mind was immersed within the boundless text. He simply didn’t feel the passing of time.

At the same time, at another space within the sixth level –

A pitch black flame lotus bloomed. The flame lotus was a thousand feet wide and long and shot blazing conflagrations straight into the skies.

All of the space within a hundred miles was filled with a vast destructive fire energy.

And in the center of the black lotus, Xiao Moxian’s entire body floated naked. Her black hair cascaded down her body like an inky waterfall, gently covering her perfect figure.

In the space between her eyebrows, there was a little flame spirit that seemed as if it was melting the void around it. This little flame spirit was breaking down as it constantly fused into Xiao Moxian’s body.

The little flame spirit was the Undying Inferno’s spirit.

Just how terrifying was the Undying Inferno? Even this tiny piece of its spirit cost Xiao Moxian over a year of time before she was able to adapt to it and start swallowing it.

As this life spirit fused into Xiao Moxian’s body, runes that represented the source of fire began to appear over her skin like curse seals.

Slowly, her entire body started to project beams of pitch black light. Rippling feathers containing the aura of the Great Dao began to drill out from her body.

These black feathers shined with mystical fire runes. They began to wrap around Xiao Moxian as she slowly absorbed the Undying Inferno’s life spirit.

Over time, a dark and massive egg appeared in the void, exuding a vast power of fire.

Xiao Moxian was infinitely close to her third nirvana. There was a long road separating the second and third nirvana. Of course, because she had just completed her second nirvana not too long ago, it would be impossible to finish everything at once without accumulating over time.

Before her third nirvana, she had to draw support from the Great Dao Laws of a Phoenix’s nirvana, and then fuse together the Undying Inferno’s life spirit with her own, concentrating them together. Then, through unending struggle, she could comprehensively master the power of fire and allow it all to become a part of herself…

Meanwhile, at another space in the sixth level.

A similar event was occurring.

However, as opposed to the incandescent sea of fire that Xiao Moxian was bathing in, in this space the entire earth had been frozen to the hardest of extremes for a thousand miles.

Soul Empress Sheng Mei was also naked, her entire body wrapped in deep blue freezing ice. Her exquisite body was curled up like a baby, her arms wrapped around her knees and her two eyes shut tight. Because of the refraction of light, it was impossible to see her sublime curves through the ice.

Vast waves of the power of ice, sparkling source Ice Laws, all of it gathered around Sheng Mei’s body in flowing waves.

Between Sheng Mei’s eyebrows, a tiny ice phoenix mark appeared, shining with the most source power of ice, echoing and resonating with Sheng Mei’s body.

This ice phoenix mark was the remaining spirit mark left over after Sheng Mei completely refined the spirit of the Undying Polar Ice.

Tiny rivulets of black blood essence emitted from Sheng Mei’s snow white skin, emanating a terrifying power as if a star was dissipating.

As it dissipated, even space itself seemed to be squeezed and shattered by the massive force.

At this moment, Sheng Mei was reaching perfection of her sixth reincarnation!

When she entered the sixth level, she already had massive accumulations and an unfathomable background. Now, with the spirit of the Undying Polar Ice that Lin Ming had given her, this gave her even more confidence to reach perfection of her sixth reincarnation.

Thus, in this incomparably safe sixth level, Sheng Mei had chosen to push herself to perfection of the sixth revolution, enhancing her bodily strength and soul force to the peak of the sixth reincarnation.

As long as she completed all of this, she could finally begin to wholeheartedly prepare for the seventh reincarnation.

In the Grand Reincarnation Art, the seventh, eighth, and ninth revolutions were the most difficult. Even Sheng Mei still lacked the confidence to face the last three revolutions.

She didn’t fear that she couldn’t complete the last three reincarnations, but was afraid that her accumulations would be lacking, leading to her reincarnations not reaching perfection. If this happened, this it would have a permanent negative influence on her road of martial arts and place a limit on her future achievements. But, with the Undying Polar Ice’s spirit, this gave Sheng Mei far more confidence.

……….

Without the three emperor jades, no one could open the final trial’s seventh level.

The seventh level was also likely the final level…

When Fanny Fafa and the others entered the space of the sixth level, they all tried to find a passage to the seventh level. But, all of them failed. Thus, unanimously, they all decided to stay in the sixth level and digest the massive harvests they had gained.

However, compared to Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian, and Sheng Mei, their harvests were far less.

A completion percentage of the early seventies was simply far too different from the high eighties and low nineties.

What Fanny Fafa, Mo Brightmoon, and the others obtained were all cultivation methods of the Laws of the 33 Heavens that perfectly suited them.

……..

Time passed and the third year arrived. It was nearly time for the end of the final trial.

Lin Ming floated in front of the ancient bronze book, deep in meditation. The pitch black soul force around him had become increasingly light and blurry.

Within his mind, the words of the Asura Sutra Second Volume shimmered like black stars.

The Asura Sutra was the condensed essence of martial arts that the Asura Road Master had gained throughout his lifetime, and thus filled with infinite secrets. Although Lin Ming had read and comprehended as much as he could, all he understood was an extremely tiny part.

He wasn’t able to understand the majority; he would need time to slowly and thoroughly study it.

However, the parts of the Asura Sutra that he didn’t understand were all forcefully recorded in his sea of consciousness with soul force; he wouldn’t forget them.

When the last word of the Asura Sutra Volume Two was recorded in his mind, Lin Ming slowly opened his eyes.

With a light flick of his sleeves, black light rippled out from him.

At this time, Lin Ming’s eyes appeared exceptionally bright.

“It seems… it’s almost time to leave.” Lin Ming realized. After wholeheartedly cultivating the Asura Sutra Volume Two for over two years, he slowly discovered that it was much easier for him to understand the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws within the final trial, as if everything was in perfect harmony with himself.

He could faintly feel that this space was emitting a mystic strength that was repelling him.

Once this mystic strength gathered to a certain point, it would directly teleport him out. In other words, the time at which the final trial ended was rapidly approaching.

Chapter 1738 – The Final Reward

As time passed, Lin Ming could feel the repelling force of the Asura Heavenly Dao become increasingly intense. At the rate this force was accumulating, Lin Ming guessed he would be transmitted out from the final trial in around a day.

“I wonder how Xian’er and Mo Brightmoon are doing…” Lin Ming couldn’t help but wonder. In the sixth level, everyone would have their own respective lucky chances. He had no idea what Xiao Moxian had obtained here or how much her strength increased.

As the power of space was brewing and the exit of the final trial was about to open, Lin Ming saw that in front of the ancient bronze book, countless Law lines gathered, gradually forming into a square array diagram.

This square array diagram was similar to the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel but there were many other things included. Within it shimmered countless magnificent and phantasmal lines and numerous ice crystals.

Although these lines seemed dense and incomparably complicated, Lin Ming could make out many clues from just a single glance.

His heart began to beat faster. These lines were similar to the Asura Heavenly Dao Law lines that appeared when drawing up a divine runic symbol…

Looking more carefully, the astonishment in Lin Ming’s eyes became increasingly bright.

“This array diagram is not just the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, but an array diagram formed from the union of all three volumes of the Asura Sutra. Moreover, these beautiful lines are similar to those that appear when I’m drawing up a divine runic symbol…”

If he were only a divine runic master then he might be confused about seeing these crystalline lines. After all, these lines seemed extremely messy, and besides seeing some enchanting figures, everything else looked strange.

But Lin Ming’s grasp of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws had reached an unbelievable degree. He quickly looked at these chaotic crystalline lines and was able to dismantle the infinitely powerful divine runic symbol refinement process.

With how each line overlapped and crossed, they were able to produce trillions and trillions of geometric changes.

Besides being materials that hadn’t been refined into divine runic symbols, the divine runic symbol refinement lines recorded on these ice crystals could be called perfect.

“These ice crystals must be divine runic symbol wisdom in crystallized form that the Asura Road Master personally refined in the past!”

Realizing this, an ancient voice suddenly sounded out in Lin Ming’s mind.

“Ten of nine, the peak of numbers, may inherit the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram. This array diagram is formed from the three forces of grandmist energy, genesis energy, and spirit source. Take the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram and fuse it into the flesh and blood, growing a microcosm of the Asura Road within the body. Sunder the Great Dao of the 33 Heavens and wander through the 33 Heavens with the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws unhindered.”

As this information flowed into Lin Ming’s mind, he was immediately overjoyed.

He suddenly recalled that after someone was able to obtain the approval of the final trial, the most important reward a trial challenger could obtain was the ability to bring the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws back with them to the 33 Heavens.

If this Asura Heavenly Array Diagram was buried within the body, it was the same as having a mini Asura Road world within oneself. He would be able to use the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws, and even the many Laws within divine runic symbols could be used in the 33 Heavens.

The divine runic arts were different from the inscription technique of the 33 Heavens. The difference lay in the fusion of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws and god runes within the inscription symbol itself.

The reason that the divine runic arts were useless outside of the Asura Road world was because the 33 Heavens’ Great Dao pushed back and repelled the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws. Generally speaking, a martial artist wouldn’t have the incalculably mighty ability of the Asura Road Master to defy the will of the heavens and establish their own Heavenly Dao. Thus, they couldn’t use the Asura Laws.

But with this Asura Heavenly Array Diagram, Lin Ming had no need to fear the 33 Heavens’ Great Dao!

Realizing this, Lin Ming no longer hesitated. His body flashed as he rushed into the center of the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram.

The moment that Lin Ming rushed in, the endless runes of the array formation swept towards him like a whirlpool, sinking into his body and rapidly shrinking within him until they completely fused into his body and blood essence.

The array diagram was formed from highly compacted source strengths of essence, energy, and divine; the impact of this fusion was astonishing.

It was like countless stars were breaking into his body. Even though Lin Ming’s body had been tempered to an incredible degree, it still caused his blood vitality to tumble and seethe. Two hours later, Lin Ming had slowly absorbed all of the Laws. Within his inner world, the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram had formed, slowly revolving.

Whorl –

Runes emitted the mystic source strength of a universe, flooding Lin Ming’s inner world. Because of this, even the boundaries of his inner world began to develop and expand outwards.

In that moment, Lin Ming felt his cultivation come infinitely close to reaching the Holy Lord realm. As long as he wanted to, he could break through at any time.

And at this moment –

The complete Asura Heavenly Array Diagram took root in Lin Ming’s body, completely integrating with his flesh and blood, becoming a part of him.

The vast power of the Asura Dao Laws within the final trial surged up, roaring out into the outer world.

……….

Inner Asura Road, Asura Sea –

In the broad Asura Sea, waves crashed up in smoky clouds, limitless and without end. Some people had once tried to find the end of the Asura Sea, but even if they rode top quality spirit ships and sped to the depths of the Asura Sea, they still weren’t able to find its limits. As for trying to use great void shifts to traverse long distances, this sort of travel would cause one to be easily lost in the chaotic fluctuations of space and time, unable to find the exit afterwards.

It was like the Asura Sea itself represented the end of the Asura Road world. And this end blurred in with the chaotic power of space. The space here was perilous and filled with cruel dangers; there was no one able to truly arrive at its end.

Not only was the Asura Sea infinitely broad, it was also unfathomably deep.

Even a star could be submerged within its great waters. Beneath the surface, ancient sea beasts lived, approaching colossal, incomprehensibly large sizes. Among these sea beasts, there were even many God Beast level existences.

Although it was said that there were many buried treasures hidden in the Asura Sea, because the water was too deep and there were too many dangers, it was nearly impossible to find them; one would only find life-threatening emergencies. Thus, very few people came to the Asura Sea.

But on this day, deep in the Asura Sea, there were over a hundred thousand people gathered.

These people were all outstanding individuals from different influences. There were senior supreme elders and also extraordinary young elites. All of them floated above the sea waters with overwhelming momentum, many of them riding opulent spirit boats and spirit ships.

This scene was truly magnificent.

The reason for this was that recently in the skies above the Asura Sea, space storms constantly flashed as if there was something horrifying brewing there. And according to previous experiences, this meant that the exit to the Asura Road’s final trial was about to open at last!

The final trial that had gone on for several years was finally coming to an end!

To the many influences of the Asura Road, this was an incredibly significant event!

If there were influences who had sent disciples to attend the final trial, there was no need to mention just how important the opening of the final trial’s exit was to them.

Even influences who hadn’t sent any disciples to participate still came to the Asura Sea to see what outcomes others had.

They all wanted to see what the completion percentage of other geniuses from large influences were like. This completion percentage would reflect to a great degree the future achievements that martial artist would be able to reach. If there was a sect who had a trial challenger that reached 77-78%, this would meant that in the future they would reach the half-step Empyrean realm, and there was even a considerable chance they would become an Empyrean!

The birth of an Empyrean. In an Empyrean level influence, there was no need to mention how important this was. They would unhesitatingly spend every resource possible to chase after such a goal!

In truth, the birth of an Empyrean was an event worth great celebration even in a True Divinity level influence, one for which heroes from all over the world would be invited. For instance, the Divine Void Divine Kingdom. If one ignored Soul Emperor Divine Void, then Divine Void Divine Kingdom only had seven Empyreans.

So, any influence that could produce a trial challenger with 77-78% completion would absolutely draw enormous attention.

As for a completion percentage of 79, that was even more exaggerated. Such a character had an extremely high possibility of becoming an Empyrean and perhaps even a powerhouse amongst Empyreans.

A step higher than that was 80% completion! That was a mythical score. Although there was only a single percent between 80% and 79%, the truth was that it was as far as the heavens and earth. In the last 100 million years, there were several such people who had appeared with this score, and nearly all of them had become Empyreans, with many close to becoming True Divinities!

However, there were no influences that dared to hope for this completion percentage. In this round of the final trial, only Sheng Mei had a chance to uphold this legend. But, Sheng Mei was someone from the 33 Heavens and had nothing to do with the Asura Road.

In the Asura Sea, the various great influences set themselves up according to their strengths.

There were dozens of large and small sea platforms. The central platforms, the seats of honor, naturally belonged to those of Divine Void Divine Kingdom and Heaven Union Divine Kingdom.

At this time, whether it was Divine Void Divine Kingdom or Heaven Union Divine Kingdom, they both had core disciples attending the final trial. The Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s Third Crown Prince and Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s Bigflame had both entered, and they were destined to be the most brilliant and dazzling characters of the final trial. They had also made a bet beforehand, causing everyone to anticipate their confrontation even more.

In a sense, the results of the final trial were also a competition between the futures of the Heaven Union Divine Kingdom and Divine Void Divine Kingdom. Both sides had attached great importance to the final trial.

The group leader of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s team here was a direct disciple of Divine Emperor Heaven Union – High Prince White Feather, a half-step Empyrean.

As for the Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s side, their team was led by the Third Imperial Scholar of the Divine Void Divine Kingdom, Imperial Scholar Sun. He was also a half-step Empyrean.

The two platforms that these two great influences stood upon were less than 200 feet apart. As they glared at each other from across the sea, they both stood in sharp opposition.

High Prince White Feather comfortably reclined on his kirin throne, a smile dangling on his face. To one side, a beautiful maid was holding up a screen for him and on his other side, another beautiful maid was hand feeding him rare and precious spirit fruits. This sort of pose was similar to that of an emperor of the mortal world enjoying himself; he looked extremely relaxed.

High Prince White Feather also had a look of confidence. He looked at Imperial Scholar Sun, who had a table next to him with a jar of celebratory wine. He smiled and said, “Imperial Scholar Sun, you even have the celebratory wine prepared? It seems you’ve prepared it for the Third Crown Prince? Imperial Scholar Sun seems to have already assumed that the Third Crown Prince will return in glory, but it seems you prepared the festivities too early… you might need to be careful of accidentally slapping yourself…”

High Prince White Feather taunted. Heaven Union Divine Kingdom and Divine Void Divine Kingdom were both respective leaders of the saints and spiritas in the Asura Road. They were both hostile to each other to begin with, and now that they were sitting near each other it was normal for them to engage in verbal battles in their boredom.

Chapter 1739 – The Exit Opens

Facing High Prince White Feather’s taunting words, Imperial Scholar Sun cackled. His fingers rhythmically tapped on the armrest as he leisurely said, “There is no need to speak so arrogantly, otherwise the one who will have to leave from shame might be you.”

Whether it was Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s Bigflame or Divine Void Divine Kingdom’s Third Crown Prince, both were amongst the most outstanding young disciples of their generation. In the future it was likely they would become Empyreans.

In this final trial, except for the anomaly known as Sheng Mei, everything was theirs for the taking. Whether it was High Prince White Feather or Imperial Scholar Sun, they both had absolute confidence in their influence’s disciples.

“Hahaha!” High Prince White Feather laughed. “Very good! Then, let us take a good look at whether the Third Crown Prince or Bigflame has a higher completion percentage! However, I only fear that your joy will turn to sorrow. If there is anything that might have happened to your precious disciples… hehe!”

“That is what I am cautioning you about. Since ancient times, it has been common for peak disciples to perish in the final trial. If Nephew Bigflame were to recklessly try to show off his power and have some accident befall him, that would truly be regretful.”

The barbs between Imperial Scholar Sun and High Prince White Feather became increasingly cruel and sinister. At this time, winds and clouds began to surge. The power of space rapidly converged above the sea.

The final trial’s exit was about to open.

Everyone’s minds tightened. The originally boisterous scene suddenly quieted down. Everyone waited in complete concentration for the exit path to open!

In the final trial, the truth was that there was more than one exit path. Besides the largest one, there were many small exits and the trial challengers would be transmitted to random locations. It wasn’t necessarily true they would be transported out to this location. Thus, many people had already prepared sound transmitting talismans and signal flares to call out to their disciples as soon as possible.

As everyone was preparing to receive and greet their disciples, at this time, monstrous waves formed atop the sea. From the distant horizon, a majestic golden mountain came flying towards them, bursting out with flashes of golden brilliance.

This divine mountain had just appeared on the horizon but in the blink of an eye it had arrived in front of everyone, as if it had appeared out of thin air. This mountain was incredibly high, and the peak was buried deep in the clouds, unable to be seen. Wherever the mountain went, gargantuan waves would rise up and the earth would quake.

“Boundless Divine Mountain! Soul Emperor Divine Void’s personal transportation!”

Just the appearance of Boundless Divine Mountain wasn’t worthy of surprise. This was because Soul Emperor Divine Void didn’t necessarily need to be on Boundless Divine Mountain; many times it was used as a spirit ship. But, what shocked everyone was that there was a faintly terrifying pressure emitting from Boundless Divine Mountain, as if there were a spiritual god at the summit of this divine mountain!

This sort of pressure made one feel awe from the depths of their heart. It even caused their soul to shiver!

From such a great distance atop the divine mountain, this existence could actually cause the hundred thousand plus people to have their minds quake in fear, and even cause World Kings to tremble. This was a pressure that only a True Divinity could possess!

“This… how can this be… Soul Emperor Divine Void, he came here personally?”

“This is only a trial for juniors, it shouldn’t be enough to alarm him…”

Just what sort of status did Soul Emperor Divine Void have? No matter how significant the final trial was, Soul Emperor Divine Void still wouldn’t come to greet the disciples. In ordinary times only a half-step Empyrean would be sent out to manage these matters.

But the current situation was different and that was because Soul Empress Sheng Mei was also participating in the final trial. Her status almost stood on par with Soul Emperor Divine Void’s. And, the most important factor was that Sheng Mei was a woman who Soul Emperor Divine Void admired from the depths of his heart.

Sheng Mei had already been in the final trial for several years. Moreover, this final trial was extremely important to Sheng Mei and concerned whether or not her sixth reincarnation would be able to reach perfection. This was why Soul Emperor Divine Void personally came out to greet her.

The appearance of Soul Emperor Divine Void caused all the martial artists present to hold their breath. No one dared to needlessly speak; they simply quietly waited for the exit paths of the final trial to open.

As for Boundless Divine Mountain, it remained peacefully floating above everyone’s heads, waiting for the exit to open.

A few hours passed. Slowly, dusty pink clouds rose like smoke, condensing in the skies above the Asura Sea. Multicolored heaven and earth origin energy gathered from all directions, condensing into a thick mist that was incomparably gorgeous.

Chi chi chi!

In this mist, thunder and fire sparked.

The wild waves became increasingly turbulent. At this moment, a thousand mile long vortex began to form.

As this vortex appeared, the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy became increasingly violent. A massive space gate appeared, like the maw of a giant beast that was ready to swallow the world.

The final trial that had lasted for over three years had finally ended!

The appearance of the space gate also meant that the trial challengers would be transmitted outside soon.

“We can finally find out the results!”

“I wonder how many trial challengers perished this time, and what are the results of the survivors?”

“It’s certain that Sheng Mei will be number one, but I don’t know if she managed to create a new record or not. And, we need to find out whether the Divine Void Crown Prince or Bigflame did better.”

Everyone began to wildly discuss. Even Divine Rune City’s Old Xue and Old Su were mixed up in the crowd. In their old age, the chances of making another breakthrough were slim to none. Thus, they spent their days idly enjoying themselves. If they weren’t out taking strolls then they were setting up their stalls. As for such a grand occasion as this, they certainly wouldn’t miss out on it.

Moreover, there was a junior that they were paying particular attention to – that was Lin Ming.

“I wonder how that brat Lin Ming did? I really cannot understand him. In the last several years he’s given me many pleasant surprises in the divine runic arts for my eyes to enjoy, and now all of a sudden he became a talented martial artist. I have no idea when he managed to collect the necessary sets of god runes to earn the qualifications to enter the final trial…”

“Let’s wait and take a look. Although I’ve never seen this boy fight before, he’s always managed to surprise me. In terms of combat, he should definitely have some talent. I don’t think his results will be bad.”

As Old Su and Old Xue were speaking, a trial challenger had already appeared from the portal.

He appeared several hundred miles away from the group, but to these martial artists this distance wasn’t anything at all. He was soon received by the people from his sect.

As he appeared, more and more disciples were transmitted out. They were all transmitted in a scope of tens of thousands of miles in the Asura Sea. Every sect used their own unique sound transmitting talismans to call out to their disciples.

“What’s your completion percentage?”

“How far did you go?”

“What rewards did you obtain?”

As the trial challengers returned to the welcome embrace of their sects they were rapidly peppered with questions.

Trial challengers with a high completion percentage naturally replied with pride. As for those with a low completion percentage, they hung their heads and answered in shame.

Many of them had poor results and had withdrawn from the final trial midway, forced to wait the three years until they were transmitted out of the final trial.

Seeing the trial challengers all emerge in droves, Heaven Union Divine Kingdom’s High Prince White Feather had a confident expression on at all times. His maid stood by his side, feeding him a peeled spirit fruit.

At this time, from beside High Prince White Feather, a disciple suddenly said, “High Prince Your Highness, some of our disciples have returned!”

“Oh?”

High Prince White Feather’s eyes brightened. Focusing his eyes, he could see that on the distant horizon there were five disciples rapidly flying towards him. They all wore star crowns and had similar sect clothing on. They were disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom.

As the disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom appeared, they immediately attracted the attention of many people. Out of all the influences present, Heaven Union Divine Kingdom was one of the leads. It was impossible not to notice them.

They all wanted to take a look and see what the results of the chosen prides of heaven from Heaven Union Divine Kingdom were like.

High Prince White Feather stood up. He glanced at Imperial Scholar Sun with a hint of mocking superiority. Then, he turned to the arriving disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom and welcomingly laughed.

“Good! Very good! In this final trial, you have all returned with merits. When you return to the sect in the future you will definitely be vigorously cultivated. Your futures will be wonderful!”

High Prince White Feather boisterously praised. As he spoke, the five disciples gulped, as if they were afraid of something.

High Prince White Feather noticed this but didn’t care much. He was only speaking polite words just now. In truth, he didn’t care about the results of these disciples at all; he only cared for Bigflame.

“Bigflame? How come he isn’t with you all?”

As High Prince White Feather asked this question, the ears of many nearby martial artists pricked up. As Imperial Scholar Sun heard this, he also carefully listened even as he continued rapping his fingers. He similarly cared about Bigflame’s completion percentage.

However, the complexions of the five disciples had turned ugly.

“Mm? What is it?” High Prince White Feather frowned.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Bigflame, he… he… hasn’t… come out yet?” These disciples asked with fear in their voices. They looked in all directions, holding onto some hope that Bigflame was here.

However, even as more and more trial challengers arrived, they didn’t discover Bigflame’s shadow at all.

The response of these disciples caused High Prince White Feather’s face to darken. “What are you all hesitating for? If there’s something to say then spit it out!”

The disciples awkwardly looked at each other and then said, “Reporting to Your Highness the High Prince… this disciple didn’t see Senior-apprentice Brother Bigflame in the fourth level. Even when the channel to the fifth level opened, Senior-apprentice Brother Bigflame still didn’t appear and we didn’t see him afterwards either. We thought that perhaps… Senior-apprentice Brother Bigflame was stranded somewhere on the fourth level…and when the final trial ended, he would be transmitted out…”

The disciples said, their voices weak and quivering. In truth, there was something that they didn’t say, and it was that in such a situation, the logical conclusion was that Bigflame had died in the final trial.

“What did you say!?”

As High Prince White Feather heard this he was immediately shocked.

Bigflame disappeared in the fourth level? If he didn’t come out even now, then it was likely something had happened to him!

How could this be possible!?!?

And at this time, Imperial Scholar Sun began to wildly cackle, “Unfortunate, unfortunate, far too unfortunate! I wonder what sort of accident befell Apprentice Nephew Bigflame? If he went missing in the fourth level and still hasn’t come out then… wouldn’t his fate likely have been more unfortunate than fortunate?”

Imperial Scholar Sun loudly and openly said, pouring as much salt as he could on High Prince White Feather’s wounds.

But seeing Imperial Scholar Sun’s appearance, the several Heaven Union Divine Kingdom disciples glanced at each other, a strange look on their faces. They suddenly said, “Senior is from Divine Void Divine Kingdom? Your Third Crown Prince also went missing with Senior-apprentice Brother Bigflame; has he come out yet?”

This sudden question caused Imperial Scholar Sun’s face to stiffen. His expression immediately became quite wonderful indeed.

Chapter 1740 – Legend

“What did you say?” Imperial Scholar Sun’s eyes widened as he glowered at the disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom.

“I said that the Divine Void Third Crown Prince has also gone missing and neither he nor our Senior-apprentice Brother Bigflame have been seen since the fourth level. From Senior’s response, it seems that the Third Crown Prince hasn’t appeared yet. If so… then… his fate is likely no better…”

A Heaven Union Divine Kingdom disciple said. But, his words had touched upon Imperial Scholar Sun’s reverse scale.

Imperial Scholar Sun hissed, “Stop speaking nonsense!”

Although his words were rough, a strong sense of unease had appeared in his mind. Even though the disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom were hostile towards the Divine Void Divine Kingdom, he didn’t think that they would speak recklessly about such things, because these types of matters were too easily seen through. If they were to speak lies then their words would eventually come back to haunt them.

The several disciples of Heaven Union Divine Kingdom had ‘believe it or not’ expressions on their faces and didn’t argue back. At this time, someone standing near Imperial Scholar Sun said, “Lord Imperial Scholar, Senior-apprentice Brother Yang has returned!”

Just as this voice spoke out, Imperial Scholar Sun grabbed onto it like a life-saving thread. He quickly turned and saw five people flying towards them from the far off horizon.

These people were the trial challengers that Divine Void Divine Kingdom had sent out. One of them was the one referred to as Senior-apprentice Brother Yang.

The first thing Imperial Scholar Sun did was try to search for the Third Crown Prince amongst the group. However, he didn’t see him.

This caused his heart to turn as cold as ice.

“Where is the Third Crown Prince!?”

He didn’t wait for the Divine Void disciples to steady themselves before he aggressively approached them and asked.

“The Crown Prince, he…”

After having Imperial Scholar Sun ask them this question right to their faces, the several disciples were dazed for a moment, not knowing how to respond.

“Where did he go!?”

Imperial Scholar Sun was breathless. Right now he didn’t care about the Third Crown Prince’s completion percentage; he just wanted to see the live person.

“Well…” The several Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciples looked at each other in dismay. Finally, Senior-apprentice Brother Yang said with fear in his voice, “Reporting to the Imperial Scholar, his Highness the Crown Prince… as well as Duke Fullmoon… disappeared on the fourth level and their whereabouts are unknown. We tried looking for them but… afterwards, there was a giant staircase of 33 steps leading from the fourth level to the fifth level, and after I climbed to the 31st step I entered the fifth level, and after that I didn’t see the Crown Prince.”

The Senior-apprentice Brother Yang was one of those people who had followed Lin Ming and the others to fifth level and helped confront of the Undying Inferno. But, he was also one of those that were afraid of the Undying Polar Ice that appeared afterwards and left the group at a critical moment.

“He’s missing…”

Imperial Scholar Sun mumbled to himself. He fell back into his wooden chair, a stunned expression on his face.

The Divine Void Third Crown Prince was of their Sun Family bloodline and was also the most outstanding disciple from their family. Because of this reason, Imperial Scholar Sun had been chosen to lead the delegation to greet the Third Crown Prince. But now, he discovered that the Crown Prince was missing and had likely suffered some fatal accident. This information was naturally a great attack to him.

For a time, Imperial Scholar Sun had no interest at all in bickering with High Prince White Feather.

At the same time, High Prince White Feather had no intention of kicking Imperial Scholar Sun while he was down. Right now, they could be called fellow sufferers grieving together. Because Bigflame was missing, he too had fallen into despondency.

Originally, the Divine Void Divine Kingdom and Heaven Union Divine Kingdom were the stars of the final trial. With their overly dramatic and tragic end, this caused more and more martial artists to notice them.

Everyone now realized that two of the most outstanding disciples from Divine Void Divine Kingdom and Heaven Union Divine Kingdom, Bigflame and the Third Crown Prince, had gone missing in the final trial and had likely suffered some tragic end!

The two of them had been the main leads of the final trial and they had even made a bet based on their results. But currently, the final trial’s exit had been open for some time already and seemed to be closing soon, and yet the two of them hadn’t appeared. The hopes of them showing up became more and more uncertain, and the surrounding people couldn’t help but start speaking in hushed whispers.

“Bigflame and the Third Crown Prince both perished?”

“Unbelievable… that two extremely talented individuals with chances of becoming Empyreans in the future would die here. The final trial is far too dangerous!”

“Indeed… although many people survived, the truth is that most of them don’t have a high completion percentage. Many of them had given up on the fourth level. If they really had to struggle for great lucky chances then that would have been extremely perilous for them. Before, I envied those people who found such great lucky chances but now that I see it, if we were to go it’s unknown whether we could come back out.”

As everyone was speaking, an enchanting blue light shot over their heads, followed by a faint cold wind.

As everyone was startled, they looked up to see a blue beam of light arcing across the endless skies and disappearing into Boundless Divine Mountain. The speed was so fast that some people even wondered whether or not that was an illusion just now.

The cold wind gradually dissipated, but a vague and ethereal pressure remained in the air, not fading for a long time.

“Soul Empress Sheng Mei!”

“Yes, she seems to have entered Boundless Divine Mountain…”

Everyone took a deep breath, their words filled with reverence.

For the last 100 million years, Soul Empress Sheng Mei had maintained the top final trial record of 83% completion, even suppressing the Good Fortune Saint Son and leaving behind a legend that would last for a hundred generations.

And this time, without a doubt, Soul Empress Sheng Mei had created an even higher record!

It was horrifying just thinking about it. Outstanding young elites like the Divine Void Third Crown Prince and Bigflame had likely perished in the final trial, yet Sheng Mei had not only easily returned, but created new records!

This difference was simply far too great.

“Soul Empress… what was her completion percentage?”

Someone couldn’t help but ask. They began looking towards the several Divine Void Divine Kingdom disciples that had returned from the final trial.

Of these disciples, some of them had joined with Sheng Mei in combatting the Undying Inferno. Because of their hesitancy and fear, they had been a single step away from entering the sixth level and becoming legends in their own right. Otherwise, they could have easily obtained a completion percentage in the seventies.

Hearing this question, Senior-apprentice Brother Yang replied, “The Soul Empress, she is likely at… 89%...”

On the fifth level, when Sheng Mei, Lin Ming, Xiao Moxian, Dragonscar, and the others had killed the Undying Polar Ice, the ones who had left weren’t too far away. With their extremely keen hearing, they were able to hear what was happening far away. Thus, when Sheng Mei, Lin Ming, and Xiao Moxian joined forces to create a miracle, they had faintly heard what Sheng Mei’s completion percentage was. To them, this hadn’t been too shocking, but had seemed perfectly normal.

But when this information fell into the ears of those present, it was like a bolt of lightning smashing down from nowhere.

“W-what… what!? 89%!? Are you joking with me?”

The one who asked was shocked. Let alone them, even Imperial Scholar Sun and High Prince White Feather suddenly regained their composure from their sorrow of losing their top disciples. They both looked towards the disciple who had been speaking with disbelief etched on their features.

This number was far too bewildering. For a time, all of them were unable to accept it.

“89%... are you sure?”

“It’s true…” Senior-apprentice Brother Yang gulped, a bitter smile on his face. He had been just a step away from leaving behind his own legend; how could he not be filled with regret?

“How can it be so high!? Do you know what sort of concept that number is? In the stories, even those who become True Divinities will only reach 85% or above! She… how… how can her score be so high?”

Imperial Scholar Sun muttered to himself again and again. He simply couldn’t regain his wits.

Senior-apprentice Brother Yang helplessly said, “It wasn’t so high to begin with, but because they killed the fifth level Overlord they were able to enter the sixth level and thus their score increased by several points. Originally, the Soul Empress’ completion percentage wasn’t so exaggerated…”

The more Senior-apprentice Brother Yang spoke, the more bitter he felt. Speaking these words was the same as picking at his scabs.

“Killing the fifth level Overlord and entering the sixth level?”

Imperial Scholar Sun and the others sucked in a breath of cold air. Although they didn’t know what the fifth level Overlord was, they did know that the sixth level was a legend. In the last billion years, there hadn’t been anyone who managed to accomplish the magnificent feat of entering that mysterious land.

“The Soul Empress is really fierce, she actually killed the fifth level Overlord…”

High Prince White Feather gulped. Even though the saints were hostile to Sheng Mei’s spiritas race, he couldn’t help but admire such a powerful woman.

However, these words caused a strange look to appear on Senior-apprentice Brother Yang’s face.

“This is…” Although he didn’t want to, he couldn’t help but say, “The one who killed the fifth level Overlord wasn’t the Soul Empress…”

“Mm?”

Everyone paused. They all looked towards this Senior-apprentice Brother Yang.

“If it wasn’t Sheng Mei then who was it?” High Prince White Feather asked, puzzlement on his face.

“It… it was that fellow called Lin Ming.”

Speaking Lin Ming’s name, Senior-apprentice Brother Yang couldn’t help but sigh in his heart. Really, this was what it meant to be inferior to others. Lin Ming’s horrifying performance on the fifth level had left him shocked and awed, and he knew he could never catch up to this Lin Ming no matter how hard he tried.

“Lin Ming? You’re speaking of…” Imperial Scholar Sun was stunned. He queerly said, “Are you telling me it’s that boy from the Divine Runic Masters Guild?”

Many people hadn’t heard Lin Ming’s name before. Although he could be called a celebrity within the Asura Road, the truth was that Lin Ming was only a big figure within the professional circles of divine runic masters, so it wasn’t strange if others didn’t know of him. But, when he entered the final trial, there had been a good number of people that recognized him.

Because a divine runic master invested so much time into studying the divine runic arts, their combat ability was normally nothing to mention at all. It was already fantastic for young divine runic masters to be able to follow the cultivation pace of their peers, let alone participate in the ruthless final trial.

Thus, when Lin Ming appeared many people had started to talk about him and so others knew of his existence.

And now they were being informed that Lin Ming had killed the fifth level Overlord. They couldn’t help but glance at each other, dumbfounded. What was the meaning of this?

“Do you need to use the divine runic arts to kill the fifth level Overlord?”

Some people couldn’t help but make this association. They didn’t believe that Lin Ming surpassed Sheng Mei in strength.

But these people were soon disappointed. Senior-apprentice Brother Yang shook his head and said, “No… in order to kill the fifth level Overlord what you need is strength. When the fifth level Overlord was in the state of the Undying Polar Ice, only Lin Ming had the ability to kill it. He really did have the true ability to kill the fifth level Overlord. Moreover… his completion percentage was even more exaggerated…”

As the disciple spoke to here, he slowly said, “…He had 92% completion.”

With this number, the entire audience of martial artists fell into a deep silence.

“…92%?”

Everyone held their breath, unable to believe this…

Chapter 1742 – To Settle All Ties

A short time after being transmitted from the final trial, Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian found each other. Then they contacted Mo Brightmoon and met up. Together, the three of them used the Asura Command to leave the Asura Sea. At this time, the people above the Asura Sea didn’t even know that Lin Ming had created a miracle of obtaining a 92% completion rate.

Lin Ming quietly left, not wanting to stand atop the waves of attention. When the exit passage of the final trial opened, influences from all over would gather and there would likely be some people intending to plot against him. He naturally didn’t want to be targeted by these people.

The final trial had already ended and now he planned to return to the Divine Realm in the near future. But before doing that, there was a matter he needed to finish.

This matter was only a matter of convenience for Lin Ming, but it could also give him decent benefits. To him, this could be considered his final mark in his adventures through the Asura Road.

One month later, Setting Sun City –

Setting Sun City was located in a remote area of the inner Asura Road. However, there were some nearby areas that were rich in spiritual energy, and thus this land was occupied by an Empyrean level influence – the Far East Family.

This also made Setting Sun City a bustling marketplace. As one of the inner Asura Road’s largest intelligence networks, Heaven’s Secret naturally wouldn’t miss out on such a large city. In Setting Sun City, there was also a branch division of Heaven’s Secret. Every day, many martial artists would come to this Heaven’s Secret branch division looking for information, and on this day, a common-looking black-clothed youth happened to visit.

This black-clothed youth was of medium height and carried a heavy sword on his back. His looks were ordinary and there were circular demon tattoos on his face, making him look a bit fierce.

He walked through the streets, a faint slaughter energy rolling off of him, causing people to unconsciously avoid him.

Like this, he walked to Heaven’s Secret.

“Mister, how do you do? What rank of news would you like to ask about?”

The doorman felt his heart jump as he saw this black-clothed youth. After waiting at the doors of Heaven’s Secret for so many years, he had naturally seen all sorts of characters. His intuition told him that this black-clothed youth in front of him wasn’t simple at all.

“I am looking for someone, a Great World King…”

The black-clothed youth lightly said. The doorman’s pupils shrank. Although this black-clothed youth didn’t seem too old, he actually searched for a Great World King. Of course, he wouldn’t ask this guest what his reasons were. He respectfully bowed and waved his hand in welcome, “Of course, please follow me to the sixth floor.”

The black-clothed youth nodded and followed the doorman into Heaven’s Secret Pavilion.

In the middle of a chamber on the sixth floor of Heaven’s Secret Pavilion, a blue-clothed old man was solemnly sitting behind a table.

The entire pavilion was filled with a fragrant smoke that resembled fog.

The doorman introduced the black-clothed youth to the chamber and then respectfully drew back, head bowed.

“I hear that this guest wishes to inquire into news about a Great World King. May I ask which Great World King this is?” The blue-clothed old man was tall and thin. His hands rested above a white jade cutting board and his voice was calm like a mountain.

The cutting board continued to shimmer with the strange power of runes, as if endless information was constantly surging atop it.

The blue-clothed old man’s eyes unwittingly swept over the black-clothed youth in front of him, as if he were trying to see through his origins.

This black-clothed youth emitted an extremely strange aura. The blue-clothed old man’s probing was immediately sensed.

Just looking at this black-clothed youth, besides the vigorous man-eating demonic aura that seemed to roll off him, he seemed to constantly fade in and out of the world, as if he could disappear at any time. It was an extremely strange feeling.

The old man looked for a long time but eventually gave up on discerning this young man’s origins.

The black-clothed youth thought for a moment and then calmly said, “Dark divine runic grandmaster, Shadow Overflow. I am looking for him about some matters.”

“Grandmaster Overflow?”

The blue-clothed old man’s eyebrows shot up. He gently traced his beard. When the average person asked about Shadow Overflow, it was usually to make deals that couldn’t be seen in the daylight. He guessed that this black-clothed youth was in a similar situation.

He didn’t ask much. He simply put forth the fee for the information and then drew several strange lines atop a jade slip.

After some time, the information within the jade slip started to rapidly reorganize itself, sparkling.

In the void, several brilliant characters began to appear.

“Darktide City, Tigerhunt Cave.”

Once he had carefully read the meaning behind these characters, the blue-clothed old man began to slowly answer.

After obtaining this answer, the black-clothed youth bowed. The demonic circles on his face emitted a faint black light; it was impossible to know what expression he was making.

Slowly standing up, the black-clothed youth left a nine sun jade on the table. Then, his figure flickered and he disappeared.

………….

“Darktide City, Tigerhunt Cave.”

The black-clothed youth chewed over the name of this area. As he flew through the skies he was like a black rainbow arching through the heavens.

And as he was flying, this black-clothed youth’s appearance gradually changed. The demonic tattoos on his face slowly hid themselves, he became taller, and the edges of his face became sharper and more contoured.

This person was Lin Ming.

The reason he had changed his appearance to go to Heaven’s Secret and ask about Shadow Overflow was to complete the last matter he wanted to seal in the Asura Road.

That was… killing Shadow Overflow.

Firstly, Shadow Overflow had a grudge against Lin Ming and Lin Ming could sense that this person was sinister and cruel, always taking revenge for the smallest slights. Although the chance that he would be able to harm Lin Ming in the future was extremely small, Lin Ming didn’t want to give him the tiniest chance to do so.

Many years ago, when Lin Ming was in the Seven Profound Valleys he had offended the Seven Profound Valleys’ Acacia Faction’s Ouyang Family. Because of that, Lin Ming had been taught a profound lesson. Due to his carelessness, Qin Xingxuan had nearly been killed by the Ouyang Family.

From that point on, Lin Ming had firmed his resolve. When it came to enemies that could harm him, his family, or his friends, he would treat them ruthlessly without the slightest bit of mercy, cutting down the problem at the roots as soon as possible. Sometimes, even the most common-seeming characters could come back to bite like a viper in the grass.

Also, there were other reasons Lin Ming wanted to kill Shadow Overflow.

Lin Ming had grasped the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram and now he could bring the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws back to the 33 Heavens. Before leaving the Asura Road, he wanted his divine runic arts to be even more perfect.

Shadow Overflow was a giant amongst all dark divine runic masters and had mastered the wide breadth of knowledge of the dark divine runic arts. He was highly adept at applying various Laws and principles to different situations.

Shadow Overflow’s memories of the dark divine runic arts were extremely tempting to Lin Ming.

These were memories he had to obtain.

They would allow him to save many years of work.

……..

The setting sun was like inky blood. A towering city stood in the midst of a howling sandstorm. The exposed city walls were rugged and simple, seeming as if they could collapse at any moment. The entire area was cold and desolate.

Several decayed sentry towers stood behind the city gates.

No one manned these sentry towers. There were only carrion vultures resting above them, sending out sharp cries.

“This is Darktide City?”

Lin Ming pulled down his black hood, biting his lips as he stood in the dusty sands and looked at the bleak sand-swept city in front of him.

According to the information he gathered, Darktide City was a well-known crime capital in the outer Asura Road. It was an extremely evil and malevolent city.

Here, rogues and thugs ran rampant.

Most of these thugs had committed a number of evil deeds. Darktide City just happened to be at the junction of many nearby Holy Lands and Divine Kingdoms. Thus, because it was under no one's jurisdiction, it had become a paradise for numerous criminals.

Lin Ming didn’t think that such a famous crime capital would be desolate in such a manner; it was really startling.

If he hadn’t obtained information from Heaven’s Secret, Lin Ming would never have thought that the famous dark divine runic grandmaster Shadow Overflow would live in such a grim place.

“Mm?”

Suddenly, Lin Ming became keenly aware that there were slight energy fluctuations in the skies.

These types of fluctuations were even weaker than fluctuations of light. However, because of the incredible sensitivity of Lin Ming’s senses, he was able to instantly lock onto the locus of changes in the air.

His lips curved up in a faint sneer.

Putting on an ignorant appearance, Lin Ming flipped his black hood back on and slowly walked towards the city entrance.

Behind him, a strong big fellow drilled out of the void, draped in translucent wings. This person carried a metal trident that shined with strange runes. He was impressively a member of the monster race.

“Human?” The monster fellow showed a greedy smile.

Then, this fellow saw a strange divine runic symbol slowly flutter down from the air.

The divine runic symbol had a clear word written upon it – Imprison!

This word exuded threads of mystic power. The wind rose and in the next moment a web of golden wires shot out, tightly wrapping around the monster fellow, tightly locking onto his flesh and blood!

“Ahhh!”

The monster fellow cried out in alarm. However, in the next moment, all his cries were sealed off, leaving him unable to cry. He wasn’t able to summon any monster essence from within his body, making him seem like a dead dog being hung in the air.

The monster fellow revealed a look full of panic and dread.

Lin Ming floated up, looking down at this robber with imposing contempt. A faint killing intent shined in his eyes, making this monster fellow’s heart shake and sweat drip down his back.

“Tell me, what is the situation of Tigerhunt Cave? Do you know someone called Shadow Overflow?” Lin Ming icily said to the monster fellow.

As Lin Ming spoke, his pupils changed color, becoming a deep dark abyss. If a common martial artist were to look at Lin Ming now, they would feel as if their soul was being sucked into his eyes.

This was an arcane skill of the Asura Sutra’s second volume. As the monster fellow met Lin Ming’s eyes, his body shook, his eyes glazed over and his expression turned blank. His sea of consciousness had been thoroughly muddled by Lin Ming’s soul force.

In the next moment, the monster fellow opened his mouth and spoke of everything he knew.

The monster fellow happened to be someone from Darktide City’s Tigerhunt Cave. From his mouth, Lin Ming had been able to learn a great deal of useful information.

Gently shaking his robes, Lin Ming’s figure began to dim among the yellow sands, disappearing into the void.

As for that monster fellow, he tumbled to the ground, his eyes still blank and his face pale like an idiot. His spiritual sea had suffered irreversible damage and from this point on he was ruined.

From the moment that Lin Ming entered this monster fellow’s mind, he had learned that he normally raped and pillaged, killing others to steal their possessions. Facing a villain like this who only committed evil deeds, Lin Ming would show no leniency. Removing one such person was the same as saving many lives.

Chapter 1743 – Killing Shadow Overflow

Although Darktide City was in name a city, the truth was that it encompassed a massive region. Within this region were innumerable gangs of murderers, robbers, various influences, and even dark divine runic masters.

Tigerhunt Cave was located beneath Sunflare Mountain at the very center of Darktide City.

When the last rays of blood red light struck Sunflare Mountain, waves of glorious light would emit from the base of the mountain.

As if daytime was rising where the light came from.

If one looked carefully, they would see that this brilliant daylight was composed of countless divine runic symbols.

This formed an extremely formidable tidal wave of defense.

The giant Tigerhunt Cave was carved into the mountainside. It was over 10,000 feet wide.

Magnificent structures towered into the skies, illuminated with candle-like lights all over. It was a beautiful and enchanting sight.

The massive structural complex had no guards. From within, one could only hear the laughs and frolicking screams of women.

A hundred meters from the periphery of Tigerhunt Cave, Lin Ming circled around a rocky peak.

Beneath the waves of light from the divine runic symbols, his figure constantly shimmered like an image on the rippling surface of a lake. It was hard to make out his appearance.

After emerging from the space of the final trial and obtaining the second volume of the Asura Sutra, Lin Ming had reached the pinnacle in attainments of soul forging Laws. This sort of understanding manifested in Lin Ming’s previously learned cultivation methods. By using a bit of soul force with the Divine Dream Law and combining it with the power of space, he was able to freely move and deceive the eyes of ordinary martial artists.

As he arrived in front of the defensive divine runic symbols, he narrowed his eyes. He scanned the palatial structures within Tigerhunt Cave, a trace of killing intent passing through his eyes.

One hand gently followed the trajectory of a nearby divine runic symbol, creating an energy line.

Lin Ming slowly perceived the energy structure. Then, after a moment, he forcefully opened up a gap within the supposedly impregnable divine runic symbols.

His form flickered as he passed inside.

Tigerhunt Cave.

There was a lustrous palace resplendent in gold and jade, covered in beams of shimmering energy. The palace rose high into the air.

Coming from within the central hall of this grand palace, there was the sound of lively chatter.

There was currently a banquet feast being held in the palace. The sounds of cheers and boisterous laughter lingered in the air.

At this banquet feast was a crowd of dark divine runic masters in long black robes.

Sitting at the highest seat of honor was the infamous Grandmaster Overflow, one of the top dark divine runic masters of the Asura Road.

The other dark divine runic masters surrounded Shadow Overflow like planets around a sun. Some of them were a little drunk and had flushed faces.

Beside them were beautiful young girls carrying platters of wine and meat, their bodies only covered by the thinnest layers of gauze. Their large chests and slender waists were clearly illuminated with each light step they took.

The entire feast was filled with the smell of wine and meat, mixed with the fragrance of a young girl’s flavors.

“Grandmaster Overflow, recently our business has become increasingly good. All of that is thanks to Grandmaster’s luck.” A middle-aged dark divine runic master said, raising a glass of wine as he flattered Shadow Overflow with a drunk smile.

“Haha, if things continue like this then in the future, all of the dark divine runic masters around Darktide City will have to work under the grandmaster.” Someone laughed out loud.

Facing these people’s flattery, Shadow Overflow only ominously smiled. His smile was a bit cold. As the present dark divine runic masters saw Shadow Overflow’s expression, they all shrunk their necks. They knew that Shadow Overflow was likely in an extremely poor mood.

If one had to think of a reason, it was all because of the results of the Asura Road’s final trial. There had been a certain individual who had created a miracle and obtained a 92% completion rate, and this person was none other than Shadow Overflow’s sworn enemy, Lin Ming.

This meant that Lin Ming possessed unimaginable talent. In the near future, he could kill Shadow Overflow as easily as stepping on an ant. In this sort of situation, Shadow Overflow felt as if a mountain was constantly pressing down on his chest, leaving him unable to take a single breath.

So in recent days, whenever someone mentioned Lin Ming’s name, Shadow Overflow would look as if he had taken a cup of poison.

With Lin Ming in the Asura Road, as long as he grew up, Shadow Overflow would never be able to publicly appear for the rest of his life. He would have to live like a little underground mouse.

The other dark divine runic masters had correctly guessed Shadow Overflow’s thoughts. One of them said, “Grandmaster Overflow, I’ve already contacted some intelligence networks and underworld influences to search for Lin Ming’s whereabouts. As long as there is any news found about him then we can release the information to those influences who have dark intentions towards Lin Ming. I’m sure they will be extremely interested…”

“That’s right, although it's difficult for us to take out Lin Ming, those evil influences are ruthless and cruel. They will definitely covet the secrets and lucky chances that Lin Ming has!”

Several dark divine runic masters grinned as they spoke. Hearing these words, Shadow Overflow was finally in a better mood. He said, “That little beast, this time he really did put himself in the limelight, but a tree outside of the forest will be blown down by the wind. Since he’s made himself so high profile, there are innumerable influences targeting him. I hope that those dark influences can kill him, but I guess we’ll have to wait to see the play.”

As Shadow Overflow spoke, hatred flashed in his eyes.

He threw back the blood red wine in his glass in a gulp. As long as he thought of Lin Ming being killed, his entire body would shiver with excitement.

“You little beast, just you wait. And that little witch that follows him, it's best if they are both ruined together.”

Thinking of the black-clothed girl that followed Lin Ming, Shadow Overflow suddenly fiendishly grinned. Without any indication he reached out and grabbed one of the beautiful maids nearby, ruthlessly kneading her milk-white breasts.

The maid paled. She bit her lips but she was only able to look at Shadow Overflow with a pleasing smile.

“Hehe…”

Shadow Overflow lasciviously chuckled several times. He grasped the maid by the waist and then turned to walk towards the back gardens.

In the darkness, an indifferent Lin Ming followed him like a god of death arriving in the midst of night.

The divine runic symbol traps arranged in the air or placed on the ground were nothing in front of him. He could skillfully bypass them all.

This was also because Lin Ming had cultivated the Asura Sutra Volume Two. With that, his understanding of the Laws of divine runic arts had gone even further. To him, these traps existed in name only.

Pah –

Another barrier of divine runic symbols was broken open by Lin Ming.

His clothing fluttered around him. Like an owl, he flew deep into the back gardens, blending in with the endless darkness.

…..

The thinly-clothed maid was tossed onto a bed. Staring at her creamy white body, a pleased grin appeared on Shadow Overflow’s face. To the current Shadow Overflow, beauty no longer had any temptation for him. What he liked was recklessly ruining and conquering nubile young maids in order to give vent to the sadness and feelings of suppression in his heart.

Just as he was about to throw himself onto the maid, he suddenly froze.

Although he had to spend a great deal of his time and energy on the divine runic arts, his strength and cultivation were still those of a Great World King. He had sharp senses and was able to detect a strange, thread-thin fluctuation of strength in the air. He slowly turned his head, looking towards a window lattice

There, hovering in the air, was a tall black-haired youth.

He wore a black robe and his entire body seemed wrapped in darkness. Strange circular demonic tattoos rippled along his neck, constantly moving without end. As he looked down from his commanding position, his stare was cold and ruthless, like a hawk staring at its prey.

“You… how did you get in?” Shadow Overflow felt his scalp tingle and all the hairs on his body rise up. He was a sixth level dark divine runic master and he had extremely deep attainments in the divine runic arts. Within Tigerhunt Cave, he had laid down layers upon layers of array formations and trap divine runic symbols. Because of this, he simply didn’t need any guards.

With such a solid and complex defense, how did this black-haired youth come in? His intuition was screaming to him that something was wrong here.

He didn’t know who this unexpected intruder was. This intruder’s face was covered by his strange dark demonic tattoos, making it impossible to clearly see his face.

Shadow Overflow didn’t know why, but this youth gave off a familiarly repugnant feeling, one that aroused his loathing.

“No matter who you are, since you dare to intrude upon my lair then die!”

Shadow Overflow coldly sneered. As a sixth level dark divine runic master, he had experienced and weathered countless storms before.

Towards this unknown visitor, although he was startled he wasn’t afraid. He didn’t think that this person’s cultivation was too high.

His hands wove lines in the void. The originally calm space began to bubble and explode with energy like raging lava.

The surrounding walls were all covered with colorful God Beast drawings. And now, they seemed to come alive, releasing a strange mystical power of fire.

At this time, Lin Ming could also clearly feel that Shadow Overflow’s chamber seemed to come alive. The glistening dyes used to draw the murals on the walls began to shine and emit a turbulent essence energy – they were clearly manufactured from wonderful fire-attribute heavenly materials.

In front of Shadow Overflow, a lifelike fire rune was drawn, one that looked like a snake formed from flame. The fire essence energy in the dyes on the murals started to be energized and drawn into the middle of the rune.

Everything was actually a mighty and massive divine runic symbol.

Lin Ming was startled. He didn’t think that Shadow Overflow had filled his entire chamber with materials used to draw a divine runic symbol and could instantly summon them to defend against enemies.

In a moment, a blazing hot divine runic symbol appeared, so hot that even the air began to bubble. The ground instantly cracked and melted away. Lin Ming was directly surrounded by these flames. The demonic tattoos on his body and the black energy around him began to burn, rapidly dissipating.

As the demonic energy dissipated, it also caused Lin Ming’s face to be revealed. Since he came to Shadow Overflow’s lair, he hadn’t changed his appearance.

Shadow Overflow was now able to clearly see Lin Ming’s face.

As Shadow Overflow saw this face that had haunted him like a nightmare, he suddenly felt as if he had fallen into an icy lake.

“It’s you! Lin Ming!?”

Shadow Overflow’s withered old eyes opened wide. He looked at Lin Ming with hate and fear, “You, you actually dared to enter my mansion!?”

No matter what, he never imagined that while the dark divine runic masters under his command were searching everywhere for information about Lin Ming’s whereabouts in order to share it with evil influences, Lin Ming would actually come to him on his own initiative and try to attack him.

But Lin Ming didn’t even have a Holy Lord cultivation. Was it possible he thought he could kill a Great World King?

Shadow Overflow certainly wouldn’t doubt Lin Ming’s talent, but for a half-step Holy Lord to kill a Great World King, Shadow Overflow didn’t believe Lin Ming had this ability!

Chapter 1744 – Leaving the Asura Road

Because of Shadow Overflow’s sudden attack, the entire chamber was turned burning hot. And when this energy burned through the demonic tattoos that covered Lin Ming’s body and was released from the control of Shadow Overflow’s soul force, it began to rapidly spread everywhere.

Flames spread all around, burning up the entire chamber, turning it into a conflagration of hell.

The young maid that had been tossed on Shadow Overflow’s bed cried out in alarm. Her clothes had caught fire and she would soon be swallowed up by the tongues of fire.

With her cultivation, it was naturally impossible for her to resist the shockwaves from the fires.

Seeing this, Lin Ming frowned. He flicked a finger and a rune came whistling out, covering the maid. After the rune absorbed all of the flames it transported her far outside.

Shadow Overflow saw all of this happen. A severe and mercilessly cold light flashed in his eyes, “You dare to divert your attention at such a time? Die!”

Shadow Overflow shouted out loud. He grasped three divine runic symbols from his spatial ring and threw them towards Lin Ming.

These three divine runic symbols all formed different shapes as they hurtled towards Lin Ming. They all possessed darkness-attributes. As they shot through the void, they covered space in endless chaos.

These were sixth grade divine runic symbols that Shadow Overflow kept on himself for self-defense. Facing Lin Ming, he cast them all out without a hint of hesitation!

Hu –

The entire room was swallowed by the energy of the divine runic symbols. Within a terrifying black vortex, the walls, furniture, bed, everything was twisted into ash and then even the ash disappeared. This sort of disappearance was not disintegration or tearing, but complete annihilation, leaving not even the tiniest bit of matter to prove that they existed in the world once.

This was the terror of the Concept of Darkness. Although Shadow Overflow’s combat strength wasn’t much, the divine runic symbols he drew up were considerably strong.

By the time the darkness scattered, the entire palace had been razed, everything disappearing without a trace.

This also included Lin Ming.

In the midst of the ruins, the only one left was Shadow Overflow. As he looked at the mess around him, he maintained absolute vigilance.

Although Lin Ming was only a half-step Holy Lord, Shadow Overflow didn’t have the slightest thought of underestimating him. In his opinion, this junior had countless methods to use and in addition to that he even obtained a 92% completion rate in the final trial. Shadow Overflow had no choice but to be careful.

“Did he die…?”

Shadow Overflowed gripped a divine runic symbol in one hand, his eyes cold. He didn’t think anything would be able to survive in that horrifying black vortex.

But at the same time, he also didn’t believe that someone like Lin Ming would die so easily.

At this time, Shadow Overflow’s pupils shrank and the greatest sense of crisis he had ever felt in his entire life washed over him. From not too far away, space tore open and a bright red spear thrust straight towards him.

What followed this spear was the vast and boundless grandmist force field. It covered all space in a thousand foot radius.

Lin Ming had hidden himself in a space distortion to avoid Shadow Overflow’s attack. Now as he thrust out his spear, there was grandmist energy that blocked all directions for Shadow Overflow to dodge in.

“This brat!”

Shadow Overflow’s face distorted grotesquely. From every pore on his body, black light shined out. Black energy surged, causing space itself to twist and surge.

This black energy instantly formed a 50 foot high demon soul with fiendish features and wearing pitch black armor.

Every scale of the armor had a howling ghost head stretching out of it.

The demon soul was filled with surging soul force that filled the air with evil and pestilent energy.

“Blood Pond Hell!”

Shadow Overflow shouted out loud. In that moment, the surroundings for a thousand feet all around turned into a suffocating hell, filled with a thick yin chill.

He took out a ghost banner from his inner world. This ghost banner had many demon souls sealed within. Then, all of these demon souls came rushing out, filling the world with the howls of ghosts and the cries of gods!

These demon souls had already substantialized into reality; this was the manifestation of an extremely potent soul force. The demon souls plunged towards Lin Ming, their claws stretched out as a massive space storm followed them.

As these ghosts rushed towards Lin Ming’s from all direction, they emitted sad and pained cries. The sound waves crashed against the mind, making one feel intense fear.

“Divine soul attack?”

Lin Ming’s eyebrows shot up. As a dark divine runic master and also a spiritas, Shadow Overflow possessed a number of soul attacks, all of them the kind that the spiritas were skilled in.

But to Lin Ming, this attack wasn’t anything at all.

Wu – Wu – Wu –

As the fierce ghosts cried out, Lin Ming’s spear light was swallowed up by them. Then, they all continued rushing towards Lin Ming.

Even within the grandmist space, Lin Ming could still feel a soul force wanting to sink into his body, making him turn cold.

“These ghosts aren’t bad!”

Spiritas martial artists excelled in raising fierce ghosts to swallow the souls of enemies. To many martial artists, dealing with these malicious spirits was the same as living a nightmare. But to Lin Ming, they were actually a tonic.

Lin Ming stretched out his hands. On his fingertips, faint traces of a strong aura of dead soul began to percolate. Black sparks appeared in his hand, slowly forming an ink black wheel that spun around.

Lin Ming cast out seal after seal, all of them impossibly complex. Then, behind him, the faint figure of an Asura appeared.

As this Asura martial god appeared, the wheel began to spin even faster.

The entire black wheel suddenly rose up, blocking out the skies. Dark purple Heavenly Dao runes began to spin along, like planets circling a star.

Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel!

Then, before any of the strong demon souls that leapt towards Lin Ming were able to reach him, all of them were pulled up and sucked into the endless vortex created by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

Wuwuwu - !

The ghosts howled in sorrow. One by one they were torn to pieces, turning into pure soul energy that was absorbed by Lin Ming.

“You…!”

Shadow Overflow’s eyes were blood red. Watching those demon souls blow up one at a time, he felt his heart drip blood. Those demon souls had been raised over tens of thousands of years and were fed countless lives to be produced. He had even fused a part of his own life spirit into them to refine them. Now they were being twisted into pieces and absorbed by Lin Ming; how could he not be angry?

He hurriedly wanted to take back those ghosts, but he discovered that the black wheel Lin Ming summoned was like an all-consuming black hole. Once a ghost fell into the traction range of that black hole, it couldn’t escape.

Even Shadow Overflow’s life spirit was swallowed up.

“Ahh!”

Shadow Overflow cried out miserably.

He felt a severe pain in his spiritual sea. Blood leaked out of his nose and mouth.

His life spirit being swallowed caused tremendous damage to him.

With a loud cracking sound, the ghost streamer he held was also twisted and broken by that endless black soul storm.

“This is… what sort of cultivation method is that!?”

Shadow Overflow was panic-stricken. He was heavily bleeding from all orifices on his head. His body swayed and his face was as pale as funeral paper.

Lin Ming couldn’t be bothered with speaking to Shadow Overflow. He turned his hand and the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel was received back into his body. These souls that Shadow Overflow raised were a considerably nourishing tonic to Lin Ming.

At this time, Lin Ming calmly stretched out his right hand. Motes of dark light condensed in his palm, shining with a mystic strength.

After several breaths of time, a dark gray cube appeared in his palm, brimming with an ancient and powerful aura.

Seeing this object appear, the already bleeding Shadow Overflow’s entire body turned cold. His body shivered as if he had seen the most terrifying demon to ever exist.

“What is that!?”

Shadow Overflow cried out in horror. As a spiritas powerhouse, he had an instinctual fear towards the Magic Cube. This was a suppression that came from the deepest depths of his soul.

“Die.”

Lin Ming didn’t wait for Shadow Overflow to respond. He flicked his fingers and the gray Magic Cube turned into a beam of light that shot into the space between Shadow Overflow’s eyebrows.

In that moment, Shadow Overflow felt his body shake. He trembled, clawing at his head, his old face crazily distorting. “You… what did you put in my spiritual sea!?”

As Shadow Overflow spoke, he felt a terrifying pain spread through him in agonizing waves, as if he would be torn apart at any moment.

Lin Ming’s expression was indifferent. He faced Shadow Overflow and reached out his hand.

Shadow Overflow felt a giant invisible hand catch him and bring him floating up into the air. His expression was that of absolute pain and his withered face was twisted into an unrecognizable mess. He pulled at his hair like he wanted to tear open his head.

At this time, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He turned his head and saw five black-robed men rushing towards his location in a panic.

“What’s going on! Who are you!?”

These five black-robed men were the dark divine runic masters that had been at Shadow Overflow’s banquet feast. They had originally been in their own rooms, ravishing the maids they had chosen. But when they felt horrifying energy fluctuations spread out they all quickly put on their clothes and rushed over to see the scene of Shadow Overflow being grasped in the air by Lin Ming.

“You… you are… Lin Ming!?”

Some of these dark divine runic masters had gone to the Divine Rune City Auction, thus they recognized Lin Ming.

Upon saying this, everyone’s complexion changed. They glanced over at Shadow Overflow who was being gripped by Lin Ming, then, a feeling of intense fear rose in their hearts. Without further thinking, they all turned tail and ran!

“None of you may leave.”

Lin Ming coldly said. Within Shadow Overflow’s spiritual sea, the Magic Cube began to release an even more dazzling black light!

An invisible black vortex started to revolve in Shadow Overflow’s spiritual sea, becoming increasingly large. The vortex completely swallowed Shadow Overflow and even those dark divine runic masters that tried to run were caught in the vortex, all of them twisted up by it. No matter how much they shouted out in anguish, all of them were sucked up into the vortex, none of them able to resist its terrifying strength as they were ripped to death.

A moment later, the black vortex disappeared, turning into a gray cube that flew back into Lin Ming’s body.

Shadow Overflow, as well as those several dark divine runic masters, had their souls torn to shreds and swallowed into the Magic Cube.

Beneath the unique corrosive ability of the Magic Cube, their souls turned into pure memory fragments that were sealed within the Magic Cube space.

After Lin Ming killed these people, he turned and flew up without hesitation, shooting straight into the horizon!

As he was flying, he waved his right hand and took out a plain command token from his spatial ring.

It was unknown what metal this command token was made from. On the front was written ‘Asura’, and on the back there was the carving of a demon.

This was the Asura Command that allowed one to freely pass in and out of the Asura Road.

With the Asura Command in hand, Lin Ming activated it.

In the next moment, the Asura Command released a dim bronze light that enveloped Lin Ming. Then his figure became increasingly dim. After half an incense stick of time, he completely vanished.

Like this, Lin Ming left the Asura Road. His 80 years of adventure in the Asura Road had finally come to an end…

Chapter 1747 – Xiao Moxian’s Worries

“What is wrong with me…?”

Sitting in meditation, Xiao Moxian opened her eyes. She found that she was wet with sweat and even her forehead was covered with beads of sweat.

This was not due to tiredness from meditation, but because of weakness!

Her body was weakening, causing her to sweat!

“What is happening?”

Xiao Moxian’s eyebrows pressed together. At such a critical moment how could she encounter such a strange occurrence?

With Xiao Moxian’s cultivation and strength, although she couldn’t fight Lin Ming in a head-on battle, that was only compared to him. Amongst others of her generation, Xiao Moxian was a crane amongst chickens; no one could hope to be her opponent.

Along with the pure yang energy she had absorbed from Lin Ming and her heaven-defying half-phoenix body, her blood vitality was extremely powerful. Let alone sitting in meditation for an entire day, she could easily handle fighting all day and all night.

But now, the more she sat in meditation, the more tired she became. All of the strength she gathered was slowly weakened.

“No, there’s something wrong with my body.”

As she recalled the dizziness she felt when she rode in the carriage, Xiao Moxian was increasingly confident that there was some problem with her body. One time could be called an accident, but it was impossible for repeated cases to be a coincidence. There was absolutely something wrong here.

She quickly investigated her body, probing her meridians, flesh and blood, organs, and even spiritual sea. There were no problems with any of them.

Only in her inner world were there some differences.

“This is…”

Xiao Moxian was surprised to find that within her inner world, there was a strange vortex slowly absorbing all of the origin energy within her.

Generally speaking, a martial artist’s inner world was a whole world, in other words a ‘seamless’ world. It was impossible for a leaking point to exist!

But now, it seemed as if there had been a hole poked within Xiao Moxian’s inner world.

A massive amount of origin energy was continually passing out from this hole.

And as this origin energy passed out, it didn’t completely disappear but stayed within her body. It didn’t affect her cultivation, only making it so that she couldn’t summon this strength.

“How could this be?”

Xiao Moxian panicked a little. She was not in the mood for such a joke to be played on her right now. Every bit of cultivation was important to her and she needed to use all of it to condense her primordial yin energy and suppress the pure yang energy within her.

If there was a problem with her cultivation, the chances of her being exposed were even greater.

“What is this vortex? Just how is it absorbing and confining my power? It is the aftermath of having absorbed the Undying Inferno?”

Xiao Moxian immediately thought, startled. If the Undying Inferno’s soul wasn’t extinguished, then perhaps it might be thinking of wresting away her strength and stealing her body. This was not a minor matter at all!

Thinking of this, Xiao Moxian raised her vigilance to the limit and immediately locked onto this ‘vortex’ within her mind, ready to engage the Undying Inferno in a brutal battle in her spiritual sea at any moment.

However, Xiao Moxian soon discovered that the situation was completely different from what she had thought.

The vortex had a gentle atmosphere, completely different from the tyrannical and cruel aura of the Undying Inferno. Faintly, Xiao Moxian could even feel something akin to her flesh and blood in this vortex, as if there was some small and weak soul calling out to her.

She had no idea why, but this feeling left Xiao Moxian moved. A deep sense of tender love began growing in her heart, as if this little soul in the vortex was more important than her life. This sort of feeling was beyond description, but was still ingrained into her very bones.

“This… this is…”

Xiao Moxian was stunned. On her bed, she wasn’t able to respond for a long, long time.

After confirming the situation several times and reexamining her body, verifying her acupoints, checking her bloodline and meridian channels, she finally understood what had happened...

This so-called ‘vortex’ was in truth a small and immature soul. And for such a soul to appear within her, there was only a single explanation. Her dual cultivation with Lin Ming had resulted in her pregnancy!

This vortex, the energy mass within it, was her and Lin Ming’s child!

“I actually… have a child…”

At this moment, an indescribable feeling filled Xiao Moxian’s heart. She felt as if all her thoughts were drowned in a fog, her entire mind turning blank.

Before this, Xiao Moxian had never made any preparations to ward against pregnancy. This was because the more powerful a race was, the more difficult it was for them to become pregnant. Moreover, Xiao Moxian was a half-phoenix and she was of a completely different race from Lin Ming.

If they wanted to produce a living crystallization of their love, that was something that might not happen even after countless hardships and attempts. It was possible that there might not be any children between them for the rest of their lives.

But she never imagined that after she left the Asura Road, she would find out she was pregnant.

This happiness had come far too suddenly. Originally, she had already mentally prepared herself to never have any children in her life. In the Asura Road, whenever she thought of this matter, she would feel pain in her heart. For a woman to not be able to have a child with the man she loved most, this sort of regret could be imagined.

To hold her and Lin Ming’s child in her arms, this was something that Xiao Moxian yearned for in her dreams. And now her dream had suddenly come true.

But what followed the arrival of this happiness was endless worry!

This child had come at the worst time possible.

Whether it was her or Lin Ming, both of them were too weak right now and neither had the ability to change the course of the world. It wasn’t even known if they could be together in the future.

Moreover, within this upcoming grand calamity, the birth of this child would involve the survival of many races. To this unborn child, such a heavy fate was far too cruel.

“How… how could this be…”

Xiao Moxian rubbed her stomach, a strange taste in her mouth.

Joy, happiness, sorrow, worry, all sorts of moods passed through her, making it impossible for her to feel at ease.

But what was without a doubt was that with her pregnancy, it would be far, far more difficult to conceal her affairs with Lin Ming.

Luckily, there was a single point to rejoice, and this was that the child within her was not ordinary at all. She wouldn’t have a pregnancy like a mortal would, gathering natal energy and giving birth after ten months. If that happened then she really would be seen through.

Xiao Moxian had a special physique and Lin Ming also had all sorts of strange bloodlines in his body. Not only did he have the blood of a phoenix and dragon within him but he also possessed a drop of Asura blood. Compared to the bloodlines of a dragon or phoenix, this sort of bloodline was incomparably more precious.

Whether it was Xiao Moxian or Lin Ming, they both possessed a heaven-defying talent and divine body. Currently, the child formed between them was only the purest group of blood essence. Its growth would be an extremely slow process that would continue for dozens of years. Even hundreds of years passing before birth wouldn’t be strange at all. But during this period, this child was already able to substantialize in the inner world of its parent and commune with the surrounding heaven and earth origin energy.

“It’s either good fortune or disaster… and if it’s disaster then it cannot be avoided…”

As Xiao Moxian said this, she clenched her teeth and sat back down in meditation, continuing to accumulate her primordial yin energy. With things having reached this step, she could only walk forwards one step at a time, taking things as they came.

Even though there was only the slimmest chance of making it through this, Xiao Moxian had to furiously struggle for it.

Right now, she absolutely could not honestly speak to Empyrean Demondawn about her and Lin Ming’s matters.

If she wasn’t pregnant, then if she frankly spoke of her relationship with Lin Ming to Empyrean Demondawn, the most he would have done was confine her to her room and cut off all communications she could have with Lin Ming. But now that she was pregnant, if Empyrean Demondawn or the monster race were to find out, it was hard to imagine what fate this child would suffer!

If this child suffered any accident, to Xiao Moxian, that would be the cruelest thing in the world. She would rather die than have anything happen to her child.

Thinking of this, Xiao Moxian couldn’t help but grip her chest. She found it difficult to breathe.

During this longevity feast, in front of all the great characters of the Divine Realm and possibly even representatives of the saints… if her pregnancy was to be revealed…

Xiao Moxian didn’t dare to imagine the consequences. Even her fingers began to shiver.

If such an occurrence were to truly occur, if the monster and demon races still chose to ally with the saints, then this child would become the shame of the monster and demon races.

They would definitely decide to kill it before it was born…

Drops of sweat began to run down Xiao Moxian’s fingertips.

She was afraid. She was truly, truly afraid.

A chill crossed her body and even her arms and legs felt ice cold.

But at this time, she could faintly feel the small life within her suddenly send out a call. This was a call that came from the soul. Inexplicably, this call warmed Xiao Moxian, as if at that moment courage had bloomed in her heart.

At the longevity feast, if she were indeed exposed, even if everyone within the Divine Realm were to ridicule and mock her, even if they all pointed at her, even if Empyrean Demondawn and the monster race were furious with her, Xiao Moxian wouldn’t care at all.

However, if someone dared to move against the child in her belly, if her grandfather didn’t care about their familial love, then she could only threaten them with her death!

As Xiao Moxian was filled with countless worries, Lin Ming had arrived at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

The phantasmal and ethereal Divine Dream Heavenly Palace remained unchanged from 60 years ago. Mo Brightmoon looked at the magnificent jade palace, finding it hard to remain calm. According to what Lin Ming had told her, her big sister was in this palace!

Chapter 1749 – Towards the Monster Race

“Oh? The fifth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art?”

Lin Ming asked, curious. Although he was confident in facing the Good Fortune Saint Son, it was always best to have a better understanding of the enemy.

“Yes, this Good Fortune Divine Art is a top cultivation method created by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. Its rank even surpasses that of a transcendent divine might. In other words, it is a True Divinity cultivation method. Even my Divine Dream Law is lacking!

“This cultivation method is incredibly difficult to learn and cultivate. Even if an Empyrean tried, they would suffer layers upon layers of troubles. But, the Good Fortune Saint Son was able to cultivate it to the fifth level. My guess is that the Grandmist Spirit Bead played a considerable role in this.”

Empyrean Divine Dream said, sighing. With the Grandmist Spirit Bead in his possession, whether it was the Good Fortune Saint Son’s cultivation ability or combat prowess, everything would be even more formidable. In addition to his originally heaven-defying talent, it would be far too difficult for a junior of humanity to surpass him. To the geniuses of the human race, this wasn’t a fair battle to begin with. Only Lin Ming had a chance of comparing to him, but unfortunately, Lin Ming was just far younger than the Good Fortune Saint Son was.

“40 years from now the day of your decisive battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son will arrive – you must be careful. This Good Fortune Divine Art can move the power of good fortune itself; its might is beyond imagination.” Empyrean Divine Dream cautioned.

Lin Ming nodded. “Yes, this junior understands.”

……..

Time passed. Soon, three months flew by.

The Monster Emperor’s longevity feast would start in just several days.

At this time, in the endless starry skies, a pitch black giant spirit ship slowly flew through the air.

This spirit ship was several hundred thousand feet long. As it flew through space, it resembled a massive ancient beast.

In this spirit ship, within a grand hall, Xiao Moxian stood behind a porthole. She was garbed in an elegant dress as she looked out, unspeaking.

At this time, she was going to the monster race to celebrate the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast!

“Xian’er, what are you thinking of?”

Behind Xiao Moxian, a low and deep voice rang out. And as soon as she heard this voice, Xiao Moxian’s thoughts froze and her fingers faintly shivered.

She let out a light breath and suppressed her racing heart. Slowly turning around, she put on a happy smile and said, “Grandfather.”

Behind Xiao Moxian stood a large middle-aged man. He was over a head taller than an average man and his shoulders were extremely wide and strong. His forehead was sharp, as if it had been carved by sabers.

He wore a black robe and cloak. As the hem of the cloak dragged along the ground, it exuded a mystic and dignified atmosphere.

This person was Empyrean Demondawn! Amongst Empyreans, he was a peak existence. Looking at the entire Divine Realm, the number of people who surpassed him in strength could be counted on one hand.

Facing Empyrean Demondawn, Xiao Moxian was certainly flustered!

Before this she had already been called to see Empyrean Demondawn several times. Xiao Moxian had to summon all of her will and martial arts skills in order to conceal what had happened.

This was thanks to the fact that Xiao Moxian had crossed two nirvanas and restored some of the primordial yin energy within her. In addition to her isolating her inner world, the changes didn’t seem too great.

After undergoing her two nirvanas, whether it was in terms of aura or the nirvanic flames within her, she was much stronger than before. Empyrean Demondawn would have been able to instantly see through all of this. But because Xiao Moxian was pregnant, it made it look as if her aura wasn’t powerful at all. Rather, it appeared as if she had weakened.

Thus even now, Empyrean Demondawn didn’t know that Xiao Moxian had undergone two nirvanas. Instead, he felt it was strange. After Xiao Moxian ventured through the Asura Road and her cultivation increased by a considerable amount, how come her foundation seemed ordinary and even sloppy?

It was because of this reason that Empyrean Demondawn had carefully and repeatedly urged Xiao Moxian to not increase her cultivation at the cost of her foundation.

“Xian’er, you… your aura seems to be a bit chaotic?”

Empyrean Demondawn had extremely sharp senses. He could faintly feel that there was something wrong with the origin energy flowing throughout Xiao Moxian.

“I’m fine Grandfather. I probably spent too much time in the Asura Road. The world Laws are different there and I had adapted to them. Now that I’ve come back to the Divine Realm, I’m not used to it so that caused some disorder in the heaven and earth origin energy within my inner world. I’ll be fine with some more time.”

Xiao Moxian lied, coming up with some excuse.

“Mm… the Laws of the Asura Road are truly different and the heaven and earth origin energy there is different from in the Divine Realm.” Empyrean Demondawn nodded, accepting Xiao Moxian’s explanation.

Although Empyrean Demondawn had discovered there was something strange with Xiao Moxian these past days, he didn’t think it was because she was pregnant. Rather, he would never have guessed in his wildest dreams that it was because she was pregnant. This was because in his eyes, this little granddaughter of his was a naturally haughty and proud individual. Let alone something as ridiculous as being pregnant, even her dedicating her love and attention towards a man was an incredibly difficult matter.

Thinking of this, Empyrean Demondawn faintly frowned. He suddenly remembered a marriage proposal that the saints kept suggesting. Of course, for this he wanted to ask Xiao Moxian’s opinion.

If Xiao Moxian didn’t like the Good Fortune Saint Son at all, how could this marriage be carried out?

“Xian’er, I want to ask you… about the Good Fortune Saint Son… what do you think of him?”

As Empyrean Demondawn asked this question, Xiao Moxian nearly jumped up where she stood. She definitely knew why he had asked this question. She decisively shook her head and said, “I don’t like him at all!”

After being directly cut off by Xiao Moxian, Empyrean Demondawn didn’t have the chance to say the good words about the Good Fortune Saint Son he wanted to say afterwards. He helplessly frowned and said, “Well alright, you rest for a while first. After an incense stick of time we’ll arrive at the monster race. This year, the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast is an extremely important event. If you are still feeling ill I can help you take a look and see what is afflicting you.”

“Thank you Grandfather, but I’m fine.” Xiao Moxian quickly refused. If Empyrean Demondawn were to probe her inner world the results could be imagined. She feared that once this happened, she absolutely would not be able to conceal the truth any longer.

“Mm… okay.”

Empyrean Demondawn nodded and turned to leave.

Xiao Moxian let out a long breath of relief. She turned towards the porthole, feeling her hands and palms wet with sweat.

And at this time, outside of the porthole, she could see that the spirit ship had already arrived on a mainland. This mainland was covered with vast verdant forests. The trees were thousands of feet high and would take several hundred people to encircle them.

The monster beasts raised within these massive forests were extremely terrifying. This was the territory of the monster race!

Faintly, deep in a forest, Xiao Moxian could make out a city of the monster race. Within the sprawling city there was a massive black pagoda that seemed as if it was holding up the skies. This was the Heaven Lifting Black Pagoda where the Monster Emperor dwelled.

After an incense stick of time, the black spirit ship slowly descended towards this heaven-supporting pagoda. The black spirit ship was hundreds of thousands of feet long, but in front of the Heaven Lifting Black Pagoda, it seemed like a fly buzzing around a tree, simply not worthy of mention at all.

The spirit ship steadily descended. Empyrean Demondawn and Xiao Moxian both flew down, accompanied by many attendants. And beneath the spirit ship, thousands of monster disciples were already lined up in a procession, waiting.

The one leading them was a beautiful woman dressed in a coat of white fox fur – this was Monster Concubine Archess.

The moment Xiao Moxian saw Monster Concubine Archess, she tightened her inner world and restrained her aura. But, she kept a cute and lovable smile on her face at all times, remaining completely calm throughout.

“Junior Xiao Moxian greets Concubine Archess.”

Xiao Moxian greeted in the manner of a junior.

“Humph!”

Monster Concubine Archess snorted. She was utterly respectful towards Empyrean Demondawn, but towards Xiao Moxian, there was even a hint of disrespect in her tone!

Xiao Moxian was stunned. She didn’t know just what Monster Concubine Archess meant by this.

Xiao Moxian’s thoughts raced, a strange feeling coming over her. She felt that Monster Concubine Archess was extremely unfriendly towards her, and even her eyes were as sharp as swords. It made Xiao Moxian feel as if she had been seen through.

“How did I offend her?”

Xiao Moxian thought, puzzled. At the same time, she was even more careful in concealing her aura. She had an extremely bad feeling of foreboding…

………

And as Xiao Moxian and Empyrean Demondawn arrived at the monster race, there was also another spirit ship flying towards the monster race’s world. This spirit ship wasn’t overly large, but it shimmered with a clear radiance, as if it were carved from the finest crystal.

On the side of this spirit ship was a mysterious symbol. This was a word of an ancient language in the Divine Realm, meaning ‘Dream’.

The spirit ship naturally belonged to Divine Dream Heavenly Palace.

With the arrival of the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast, Lin Ming accompanied Empyrean Divine Dream to go to the monster race’s world.

“During the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast I should be able to see Xian’er. I wonder how she’s been doing in Demondawn Heavenly Palace.”

Xiao Moxian would definitely participate in the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast. Lin Ming was a little worried about how she was doing.

“The Good Fortune Saint Son… he really came…”

At this time, Empyrean Divine Dream’s voice echoed out in Lin Min’s ears. Looking out a porthole, Lin Ming could see that several hundred miles away, there was a giant floating fortress.

This fortress was bright silver all over and covered with sharp spikes. It looked extremely fierce.

“This is the Good Fortune Saint Son’s transportation?”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank.

Empyrean Divine Dream nodded.

Chapter 1753 – Who Is He

Xiao Moxian’s entire body was being corroded by poison energy. The agonizing pain of her blood being burned by poison was beyond description. This sort of pain was the same as having concentrated acid mixed into her blood, as if her marrow was crackling like heated oil.

She gripped her fists, withstanding the waves of pain. All of her remaining essence was used to protect her inner world. With things having come this far she could only quietly continue in hopes that she wouldn’t be discovered. Otherwise, the matter of her pregnancy would become known.

Black blood began to drip from the sides of Xiao Moxian’s lips.

As this black blood flowed out, Xiao Moxian’s heart skipped a beat and her complexion changed.

The baby in her stomach was connected to her own bloodline. If her blood was corroded by the poison to the point of turning black, no matter how much energy she summoned she would not be able to cut off the streams of black blood from entering the baby within her!

The fetus was at its earliest developmental stage. Xiao Moxian absolutely could not allow it to be affected.

Ignoring the violent poison energy all around her, she forcefully revolved the nirvanic flames within her body and had the terrifying burning heat flood her blood vessels, crazily burning away the poison energy!

For a time, Xiao Moxian’s body became a battlefield. The poison energy intensely fought with the nirvanic flames. The pressure on Xiao Moxian’s mortal body could be imagined.

Even though she had a half God Beast body, withstanding such pressure still caused her blood vessels to explode and blood to shoot out.

Monster Concubine Archess grinned as she saw this. She could faintly feel that Xiao Moxian wouldn’t be able to last much longer.

Just as she was about to put forth more energy, a furious voice slammed into her ears like a thunderclap!

“Fuck off!”

With an explosive sound, Monster Concubine Archess felt a tyrannical and fierce strength rush into her body, causing her to violently shake and directly smashing her away.

Peng!

Monster Concubine Archess was blown away and sent crashing into the table. Countless glazed dishes and bowls were shattered and her entire body was drenched in the dregs of spirit foods and spirit drinks, making her look extremely miserable.

Seeing this, the Monster Emperor thought of moving. But in the end he didn’t.

He let out a long breath. He never thought that today’s welcoming reception would have such a scene.

In a pile of debris, Monster Concubine Archess propped herself up on her arms, gnashing her teeth as she looked at Empyrean Demondawn.

Facing the angry and mighty Empyrean Demondawn, it was impossible to say she wasn’t afraid.

The savage battles of the demon and monster races were far more barbaric than those of the humans.

If the races of the Divine Realm were compared to those of the mortal world, then the monster and demon races were comparable to primitive nomadic tribes and barbarians. For a battle to suddenly occur at a banquet wasn’t strange at all. Even if Empyrean Demondawn were to heavily wound Monster Concubine Archess, that would also be a likely possibility!

“One move has already passed!”

Empyrean Demondawn’s voice held a faint trace of killing intent. Monster Concubine Archess stood up from the mess, circulating the energy within her and using the power of darkness to clean away the food that stained her. Soon, her clothes seemed as if they were completely new.

As for Xian Moxian, her face was still wan. A great deal of Monster Concubine Archess’ poison was still in her body.

Empyrean Demondawn looked at Xiao Moxian and suddenly walked over to her.

“Grandfather…”

Xiao Moxian held her breath. The poison that Monster Concubine Archess left behind within her wasn’t fatal at all; resting for a day would have been more than enough to completely recover. But now that she was pregnant, everything had become far more complicated.

If Empyrean Demondawn helped then he could certainly rid her body of all of the poison instantly. But, there was a 100% likelihood that the secret of her pregnancy would be discovered.

When Empyrean Demondawn was a hundred feet away from her, Xiao Moxian subconsciously stepped back. Her heart had caught in her throat. She was unable to find any excuses to refuse her grandfather’s help.

At this time, Empyrean Demondawn had already reached out a hand towards her.

“Xian’er! What are you hiding from me?”

Empyrean Demondawn’s voice was filled with fury. He had already felt that something was wrong, but he just didn’t truly suspect Xiao Moxian. However, when he saw Xiao Moxian use her nirvanic flames as well as her strange actions that didn’t conform to her normal behavior, he had confirmed that she was hiding something!

“In the Asura Road, just what happened to you?”

Empyrean Demondawn grabbed onto Xiao Moxian’s arm.

Xiao Moxian’s heart shrank. Suddenly, she felt it nearly impossible to breathe. It was no longer possible to hide the truth!

She was like a puppet, directly held by Empyrean Demondawn.

As Empyrean Demondawn’s energy rushed into her blood vessels, Xiao Moxian felt the world slow down to a crawl. All sight and sound seemed to fall away…

Chi chi chi!

A black vortex appeared in Empyrean Demondawn’s palm. In just a moment, all of the poison within Xiao Moxian was swallowed up by the black vortex.

This was Empyrean Demondawn’s Heaven Absorbing Demon Art.

The poison was eliminated and the agonizing pain in her body also disappeared. But compared to the suffering in her heart, that physical pain hadn’t been anything at all.

Time passed, one breath of time after one breath of time. To Xiao Moxian, every breath of time was as long as a year.

She didn’t dare to look at Empyrean Demondawn’s face. She didn’t even dare to breathe.

As for Empyrean Demondawn, he remained completely quiet. As he grabbed Xiao Moxian’s arm, a long period of silence passed.

Rivulets of sweat dripped down Xiao Moxian’s back and forehead. She felt as if she could collapse at any moment.

“Brother Demondawn…”

At this time, the Monster Emperor finally spoke up.

Before, he had already been suspicious about Xiao Moxian’s bodily state. He felt that her primordial yin energy wasn’t as steady as it should be, and her energy was in utter chaos.

But when he considered that it might be because Xiao Moxian didn’t consolidate her foundation in the Asura Road, the Monster Emperor didn’t care too much about this matter. But then, in the battle just now, he saw Empyrean Demondawn’s expression.

The Monster Emperor seemed to faintly realize what happened.

“All of you, leave!”

The Monster Emperor waved his hand and the monster race martial artists began to file out. They never imagined that things would develop to such a degree. When Monster Concubine Archess and Xiao Moxian had begun to fight, all of them had fallen silent, none of them daring to utter a single word.

Whether it was Xiao Moxian or Monster Concubine Archess, they both had a status far above their own.

“You also leave.”

The Monster Emperor looked at Monster Concubine Archess.

Monster Concubine Archess clenched her teeth and silently withdrew.

Before she left, she cast a deep look towards Xiao Moxian. She had already faintly guessed what might have happened. Monster Concubine Archess possessed a half-step Empyrean cultivation and in the monster race her status was only inferior to that of the Monster Empress and several great God Beasts.

She carefully observed Xiao Moxian and had discovered several questionable points.

After a time, in the entire hall, there was only Empyrean Demondawn, the Monster Emperor, and Xiao Moxian left.

“Tell me, who is he?”

After remaining silent for a long time, Empyrean Demondawn finally spoke up. At this time, he was like a furious lion.

Xiao Moxian trembled. She looked up towards her grandfather.

Empyrean Demondawn’s eyes had turned blood red as if they could swallow her alive!

Xiao Moxian bit her lips and remained silent.

“Good! You don’t want to tell me!? Fine! Then I’ll just refine the bastard in your womb! In any case, a bastard of unknown origin is the shame of my demon race!”

As Empyrean Demondawn spoke, he lifted his left hand. A brilliant black vortex appeared in his palm. This vortex was his Heaven Absorbing Demon Art. As long as this black vortex was thrust into Xiao Moxian’s stomach, whether it was the baby’s forming soul, its flesh and blood, or its energy, all of it would be devoured without a single speck remaining!

Seeing Empyrean Demondawn raise his hand, Xiao Moxian closed her eyes and decisively said, “Grandfather, if you will do that then kill me as well. If I cannot protect my child then I do not wish to live in this world any longer!”

Xiao Moxian’s voice was resolute.

The Monster Emperor’s heart skipped a beat. He was well aware that with Xiao Moxian’s character, she would stay true to her words. If Empyrean Demondawn really did as he threatened then Xiao Moxian would instantly commit suicide!

“Brother Demondawn, calm down!”

The Monster Emperor quickly spoke out. He could feel that this time, Empyrean Demondawn was truly angered!

In the past, no matter what Xiao Moxian did, Empyrean Demondawn would always accommodate her. No matter what trouble she stirred up, no matter who she provoked, he would always play damage control and deal with the aftermath. But this time, she had touched upon his bottom line!

The Monster Emperor feared that in his violent rage, Empyrean Demondawn would do something he could not take back.

If anything happened to Xiao Moxian, it would be a tremendous loss to the monster and demon races!

Even the baby in Xiao Moxian’s womb needed further consideration. It had to be known that it was extremely difficult for a God Beast to become pregnant, especially for someone like Xiao Moxian. Once they had a child, after that child grew up they would definitely become an amazingly outstanding individual. To rashly kill such a child was too great a pity!

“…You want to threaten me with your death?”

Empyrean Demondawn’s complexion turned cold and grim. “In the Divine Realm, no one can threaten me, not even you! Do you not believe I don’t have a hundred methods to make it impossible for you to commit suicide?”

Empyrean Demondawn’s voice was ferocious. But, Xiao Moxian was also a stubborn and proud character. She clenched her teeth and said, “Even if you have 100 methods to lock in my energy so that I cannot kill myself, it is impossible for you to continue that for the rest of my life. As long as that spell is undone then I will instantly abandon my meridians and die!”

Facing Empyrean Demondawn who was roiling with killing intent, no one dared to speak to him like that. Even Monster Concubine Archess, whose status was in the top 10 of the monster race, didn’t dare to say a single word when she was struck to the point of spitting out blood in the face of everyone.

It was because when facing the enraged Empyrean Demondawn, the pressure was simply too great. No one knew for sure whether or not he would instantly strike to kill at any moment!

“Hehehe! Good! You truly are my good granddaughter. Is that little animal really worth you protecting him? That you would threaten me with your own death!? Do you think that just because you don’t say anything, I won’t know? The bloodline of the bastard within you has the aura of a True Dragon as well as the aura of a human. When you went to the Asura Road, Divine Dream Heavenly Palace’s Lin Ming also went. Along with the aura of a True Dragon and humanity, who else could it be but him?”

Chapter 1755 – Demondawn’s Turmoil

Three days later –

In a massive silver battleship outside Heaven Lifting Black Pagoda, the Good Fortune Saint Son sat above a stone bed, deep in meditation.

Then, a flame flickered in front of him.

This was the light of a sound transmitting talisman. A brief ray of thought penetrated into the Good Fortune Saint Son’s spiritual sea along with it.

Reading this message, the Good Fortune Saint Son grinned.

“Your Highness Saint Son, what are you so happy about?”

A rainbow-clothed girl tittered and asked from beside the Good Fortune Saint Son.

The Good Fortune Saint Son narrowed his eyes. He played with the burning embers of the sound transmitting talisman and leisurely said, “The Monster Emperor has sent me a message. Xiao Moxian has agreed to marry me. As long as I propose at the longevity fest, she will agree!”

“Hohohoho! Congratulations Your Highness!” The rainbow-clothed girl happily said. “I’ve already said that Your Highness Saint Son is a dragon amongst men. There are countless teams of proud daughters among the saints that are just waiting for the Saint Son to visit them. How could this Xiao Moxian possibly refuse Your Highness? If Your Highness Saint Son is willing to dual cultivate with her and take her primordial yin, that is her good fortune!”

The rainbow-clothed girl smirked as she spoke. She really did think that Xiao Moxian had obtained a great bargain by being able to latch onto a thigh of the Saint Son. This was because after the great calamity was over, the saints would capture the Divine Realm and rule the world. As for the Good Fortune Saint Son, he would eventually become the new Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. At that time, Xiao Moxian would be a favored imperial concubine of the Saint Sovereign, so of course she would easily profit from all this.

“Humph! This is simply a union of benefits. The Monster Emperor and Empyrean Demondawn are both eagerly waiting for me to hand over the method of becoming a True Divinity! However, even if I hand over the method to them their chances of breaking into the True Divinity realm are less than 1%, and even if they can, that is something that will only happen dozens of millions of years from now.”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, he walked to a window. Looking out the porthole at the Black Pagoda of the monster race, the smile on his face became increasingly wide.

At this time, the rainbow-clothed girl reached out from behind the Good Fortune Saint Son and held onto his waist. In a spoiled tone she said, “That seductress has a physique that is very suited to dual cultivation, so being able to take her primordial yin is extremely beneficial. Although Your Highness Saint Son has a new love, you shouldn’t forget your old flames either!”

As the rainbow-clothed girl spoke, a hand gently rubbed against the Good Fortune Saint Son like a spirit snake.

“Haha!” The Good Fortune Saint Son grabbed the woman’s arm and pulled her into his chest. He laughed, saying, “How could I forget the old. You follow me from your heart, but that Ji Xian’er might not be the same. If she knows her limits and takes care of me calmly and without reserve, then I might give her a proper status.”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, he picked up the rainbow-clothed girl and tossed her into the luxurious great chair. As she cried out in shock, the Good Fortune Saint Son had already thrown himself onto her.

For a time, the only sounds that filled the room were heated pants and moans.

And behind this extravagant and obscene scene, outside of the porthole, the monster race’s Black Pagoda stood tall, standing between the heavens and earth like an ancient dragon rising to the sky…

A gray moon hung high in the sky. Cold starlight sprinkled down, covering the Black Pagoda.

At the peak of the Black Pagoda, at a summit that stood a million feet up into the air, a black-robed man stood quietly, his gaze looking out a hundred miles towards the Good Fortune Saint Son’s silver battleship.

The black-robed man’s looks were cold and decisive. The edges and lines of his face were sharp and distinct. His eyes were like black gems, shining with a profound light.

This man was Empyrean Demondawn. He had stood here for three days and three nights, not moving in the least. He was like a black stone sculpture that had stood here since time immemorial.

“Haa…”

A faint sigh sounded out from behind Empyrean Demondawn. A middle-aged-looking man in a red robe slowly stepped onto the summit. This person was the ruler of the monster race, the Monster Emperor.

“Demondawn, if Xian’er doesn’t agree, will you really kill the child in her womb?”

Empyrean Demondawn slightly shook. He turned his head, In the bright moonlight, his profile was illuminated a dark silver gray.

He humorlessly chuckled. “If you ask such a question, we must first be able to hide the matter of her pregnancy before even considering it!”

Empyrean Demondawn shook his head once more. He loathed Lin Ming from the depths of his heart for stealing away his granddaughter’s chastity, and wished that he could tear Lin Ming to shreds. But no matter what happened, the reality was that the child in Xiao Moxian’s womb had the bloodline of their monster and demon races. Moreover, when he investigated the child with his energy, he discovered that it was beyond ordinary.

The child possessed a True Phoenix bloodline and True Dragon aura. Moreover, it also possessed a strength he could not understand. Although Empyrean Demondawn didn’t know what the origin of this strength was, it made his heart inexplicably race. Moreover, this child hadn’t formed a true fetus form and yet it was already able to affect heaven and earth origin energy as well as the Laws. This sort of talent was far too terrifying!

If the saints discovered the existence of this child, they absolutely would not allow it to be born in the world. They would destroy it before then!

The Monster Emperor said, “The energy lock you sealed away Xian’er’s dantian with comes from the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art. It can swallow all origin energy as well as the pure yang energy and fetal energy within her. During the longevity feast, as long as Xian’er doesn’t reveal any flaws or arouse the suspicions of the saints, she should be able to conceal what happened…”

When Empyrean Demondawn had placed an energy lock within Xiao Moxian, although it was to threaten her, the main purpose was to protect her.

“We must hide the truth, otherwise the consequences will be inconceivable!” Empyrean Demondawn grimly said.

At the longevity banquet, if Xiao Moxian’s pregnancy became known by the Good Fortune Saint Son and also made public there, the results would be unimaginable!

This wasn’t just a strike against the Good Fortune Saint Son’s face, this was completely ripping apart his face.

In a situation where the saints were making a marriage alliance with the demon and monster races, the fiancée Xiao Moxian had already been stolen away by the top genius of humanity, Lin Ming, and even carried his child. The Good Fortune Saint Son’s head would turn so red it would likely blow up.

Everyone under the heavens would laugh and jeer at the Good Fortune Saint Son.

Even within the saint race there would absolutely be some people and influences who didn’t like the Good Fortune Saint Son and would take advantage of this to stir up chaos.

At that time, the Good Fortune Saint Son would be blinded with rage and it was likely that their alliance would be ruined!

It had to be known that compared to the saints, the monster and demon races didn’t have much strength at all.

The saints didn’t necessarily need to ally with the monster and demon races. Their purpose in doing so was to strike at the confidence of humanity so that the saints would suffer fewer losses.

But on the other hand, if the monster and demon races didn’t ally with the saints, there was a 99% chance that the two races would be exterminated in the great calamity.

The safest path to take was naturally to kill the child in Xiao Moxian’s womb.

But, Empyrean Demondawn was well aware that if he did this… he would lose his granddaughter forever.

The next time they met in the future, it would be as blood sworn enemies!

“That damned little beast!”

Empyrean Demondawn suddenly gripped his fists, his knuckles crackling. He wished he could tear apart Lin Ming!

The truth was that dozens of years ago, not long after Xiao Moxian arrived at the Asura Road, Monster Prince Duyu had sent Old Blue a message which included the news Xiao Moxian was travelling together within someone. Monster Prince Duyu’s message had been filled with grievances. At the time, from the clues given, Empyrean Demondawn suspected this person was Lin Ming.

At that point, whether it was Empyrean Demondawn or the Monster Emperor, neither of them ever thought that things would develop to this stage.

“Lin Ming… agh! If it wasn’t for the great calamity then it would have been appropriate for Xian’er to be with him. But what a pity, the times will not accommodate them. The great calamity is soon to arrive and he is too young. I estimate that within the next several hundred years, the true great calamity will erupt. At that time, Lin Ming will not be any older than 500 years. A 500 year old junior, what use will he be in the face of a great calamity that has swept up the fates of two races? He is simply asking for death!”

The Monster Emperor shook his head. Let alone Lin Ming, just how much could Empyrean Divine Dream do when faced with the terrifying might of the saint race?

“Humph! Live to 500 years? It’s already more than enough for him to live long enough to fulfill his 100 year battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son!” Right now, Empyrean Demondawn felt bothered whenever Lin Ming’s name was mentioned. This wasn’t just because Lin Ming had left a massive pile of trouble for them to cover up, but also because Empyrean Demondawn felt that Lin Ming had stolen his granddaughter from him. From his previous exchange with Xiao Moxian, he noticed that every time she spoke up it was to help Lin Ming, even opposing her grandfather to do so! How could he not be angered!

“A hundred year battle… I really do hope that Lin Ming can win or at the very least not lose in an ugly manner. But unfortunately… that is impossible…”

The Monster Emperor said, dark clouds rising in his heart. In the depths of his heart he certainly hoped that humanity could survive the great calamity. After all, when the humans ruled the Divine Realm, the monster race was able to live on. But if the saints were to rule the Divine Realm, it was unknown what their situation would be.

Even though the Monster Emperor knew this logic, he had no other choice he could make.

When one was weaker than someone else, they could only bow their head in defeat.

Empyrean Demondawn let out a deep sigh. He looked in the distance, his eyes filled with bleak sorrow.

Facing the changing momentum of the world, he felt a deep sense of powerlessness.

It was like becoming an Empyrean was all in vain.

Whether it was his granddaughter’s happiness or the future of the monster and demon races, everything was spiraling out of his control.

If this was all he could accomplish in the entirety of his life, that was truly too much of a failure…

…..

As Empyrean Demondawn and the Monster Emperor were at a loss for what path to take, in Xiao Moxian’s room, the entire chamber was filled with an intoxicating fragrance.

A 100 square foot pool was filled with scintillating flower petals. The air was blurry with mist.

“Miss, please undress.”

Several maids wearing thin gauze knelt on the ground, each of them holding a variety of bathing tools as they waited upon Xiao Moxian.

Looking at the carefully mixed pool of water, Xiao Moxian’s demeanor was blasé. She removed her layers of clothing, revealing a perfect body.

She gently lifted her right foot, her pearly toes stepping onto the walls of the pool. Her snow white legs were so enchanting that they left one blinded with beauty.

She slowly stepped into the pool, her body sinking in.

The mist was like a dream. Xiao Moxian submerged herself in the pool. The several maids respectfully walked near Xiao Moxian, taking off their thin gauze clothes and stepping into the pool with her, beginning to help wipe down her body.

Her porcelain perfect skin dripped with crystalline beads of water. Her body was like a flower collecting the morning dew, leaving one mesmerized.

“Miss, please take this off.”

Several maids wanted to help Xiao Moxian wash her chest, but strung at her chest was a strangely exotic necklace.

With this necklace in the way, it was naturally inconvenient to wash her chest.

“You leave, I will wash myself.”

Xiao Moxian frowned, as if she were unhappy that these maids were touching her chest.

The several maids panicked as they saw Xiao Moxian become somewhat disgruntled.

“Leave!”

Xiao Moxian’s voice was harsh. But, her right hand grasped her necklace, holding it tight!

To Xiao Moxian, this necklace held extraordinary significance…

Chapter 1758 – Reunion of Young Elites

“Sir Lin, are you ready? Senior Divine Dream wishes to inform you that it is time to leave.”

The voice of a maid echoed out from the other side of Lin Ming’s room. Lin Ming lightly said, “I understand.”

After wrapping the spear shaft with a strip of cloth, Lin Ming put the spear away and stood up.

Although this was called attending a grand longevity feast banquet, to Lin Ming it was the same as stepping onto a battlefield.

At this time, Lin Ming heard Xiao Moxian’s sound transmission.

“Big Brother Lin, my grandfather just came and placed several spells on my body so that no one can make out any differences in me. My time in the longevity feast will be short. Moreover, I will need to agree to the Good Fortune Saint Son’s proposal in front of everyone…”

Xiao Moxian’s voice was a bit restless.

Lin Ming only said, “Do not agree to him. Leave everything else to me.”

“Mm.”

Hearing Lin Ming’s voice once more, Xiao Moxian’s heart warmed and her unease faded away.

“Miss, please hurry, we still must comb your hair and help you change clothes.”

At this time, Xiao Moxian heard the shout of a maid. They were worried that Xiao Moxian was planning some little trick to cause a problem at the longevity feast. If that happened, even 10,000 deaths wouldn’t be enough of a punishment.

“I’m coming.” Xiao Moxian coldly said. It had been difficult for her to get some time alone from these maids and she couldn’t delay them too long.

………

Two hours later, the Monster Emperor’s grand longevity feast finally began.

The group that Lin Ming traveled with gathered at a specified area.

On the fresh grass, two white-clothed women were talking and laughing. Although their appearances were clearly different, they gave off a feeling of similarity.

As the two women stood there, when combined with the wonderful background around them, it brought a completely natural sense of harmony.

“Senior-apprentice Sister… Miss Mo…” Lin Ming was surprised to see these two women. These two were the sisters Mo Eversnow and Mo Brightmoon. Originally, Mo Eversnow and Mo Brightmoon had stayed at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, so Lin Ming didn’t think they would suddenly arrive at the monster race.

“Lin Ming, you finally left seclusion…” Mo Eversnow looked at Lin Ming, her eyes deep and complex. Now that she was reunited with her sister, all of her wishes had been brought to completion.

The truth was that Mo Eversnow had already come several days ago. But in these past days Lin Ming had been deep in seclusion in order to confront the scene of the longevity feast, thus she only saw him today.

She had learned from her little sister than Tian Mingzi had been killed by Lin Ming using tricks and tactics. Although Lin Ming had drawn support from a death zone, for him to do so still left Mo Eversnow incomparably shocked.

To know that the deep hatred and animosity she had been shouldering for 50,000 years had been avenged all of a sudden, Mo Eversnow felt it all a bit unreal.

“Senior-apprentice Sister… you also came?”

Compared to dozens of years ago, Mo Eversnow seemed to have stepped onto a completely different road of cultivation. Even Lin Ming found it hard to see through her boundary.

This didn’t mean that Mo Eversnow was stronger than Lin Ming. But, because she had borrowed the mortal body of the goddess from the primal god race, Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, in many cases it was impossible to judge her strength using common sense.

Lin Ming could confirm that in these past several dozen years, Mo Eversnow had been following Empyrean Divine Dream in Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, training in the cultivation methods left behind by the ancient primal god race. It was inevitable that her strength would ascend to a completely new level.

The Laws of the god race were also one of the 33 Heavenly Daos.

“Mm… when Miss Frost Dream left seclusion, we came together.”

As Mo Eversnow spoke, amongst the many attending maids from Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Lin Ming could see a blue-clothed girl looking like a fairy that had fallen from the heavens, elegant and unstained by the mortal world.

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. This blue-clothed girl was Frost Dream, someone Lin Ming hadn’t seem for a long time!

Lin Ming already knew that Frost Dream was a reincarnation avatar of Divine Dream. As he looked at Frost Dream once more, he could feel that her aura was becoming increasingly similar to Divine Dream’s.

Perhaps in the near future, the two of them would fuse together as one.

At that time, Empyrean Divine Dream would truly step into the realm of True Divinity. However, it was unknown whether or not she could accomplish that before the great calamity erupted.

Lin Ming turned towards Frost Dream and faintly smiled, greeting her. Frost Dream slightly bowed in response, not saying anything. From the time he met her, she had always had a cold and distant personality.

“Lin Ming, when you killed Tian Mingzi, did you happen to keep his bones or head?”

Mo Eversnow grit her teeth beside Lin Ming. The hatred she felt towards Tian Mingzi was far too entrenched in her bones. She wanted to see Tian Mingzi’s severed head with her own eyes.

Lin Ming shook his head, “Tian Mingzi’s mortal body has already been destroyed. But, his soul is sealed in my Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. After the longevity feast ends, I can show him to Senior-apprentice Sister.”

“Great!”

Mo Eversnow took a deep breath, gripping her fists tight. She said in a low voice, “Lin Ming, thank you…”

“Senior-apprentice Sister, there is no need to thank me like a stranger…”

Lin Ming smiled. At this time, Empyrean Divine Dream arrived.

“Let us go.”

She lightly said. At the same time, Empyrean Divine Dream also cast Lin Ming a deep look. Lin Ming understood the significance in her gaze. She hoped that he would act accordingly in the longevity feast and wouldn’t suffer a loss.

Lin Ming nodded, expressing that he knew what he had to do.

Empyrean Divine Dream didn’t say anything further. Everything that could be said had already been said. She believed that with Lin Ming’s personality, he would never do something that was beyond his control.

Like this, the group flew into the skies!

As Lin Ming followed Divine Dream to the longevity feast, he was actually shocked by the inside background of the monster race.

So, it seemed that sealed within the monster race’s Heaven Lifting Black Pagoda, there was actually a sea.

The sea was incomparably proud. Origin energy was thick in the air as high and mighty waves tumbled about.

Without a doubt, this was a world that the monster race had sealed within the Black Pagoda. However, this world was far too large. To seal such a large world into the Black Pagoda, this was too shocking. At least, Lin Ming didn’t believe that the Monster Emperor had the ability to accomplish such a feat.

“The monster race has an extremely deep background. In the ancient past, their people also produced True Divinities…” Divine Dream faintly said from beside Lin Ming. “In the past, the monster race used to be one of the ancient races. 7-8 billion years ago to 10 billion years ago, the monster race was incomparably magnificent. Compared to humanity’s inheritances, theirs were far, far longer. Unfortunately, they have already declined, and it’s unknown just how much longer they will be able to continue living on for…”

Empyrean Divine Dream sighed as she spoke. Lin Ming knew that as she spoke about the monster race, she was also worried about the human race.

If the rabbit dies, the fox also grieves; it was easy to have sympathy for someone in similar distress. Humanity’s future was just as muddled and chaotic as the monster race’s was…

In the vast universes of the 33 Heavens, there had never been a race which was able to live prosperously forever…

“Is the god race also an ancient race?”

Lin Ming suddenly asked, looking at Mo Eversnow. Mo Eversnow had possessed the body of Heavenly Empress Xuanqing, and Heavenly Empress Xuanqing had come from the primal god race.

“Yes. 10 billion years ago, out of all the ancient races, the primal god race was the most powerful of them all, thus the reason they dared to call themselves the god race. Their race has a small population, but every individual among them is extraordinary beyond belief. The god race is likely the most perfect race that the heavens have ever created!”

The second time that Lin Ming went to the Eternal Demon Abyss, he had heard from the remnant soul of Empyrean Primordius’ disciple about the god race. The god race possessed a formidable divine soul, mortal body, and inner world. They were able to cultivate essence, energy, and divine. From the moment they were born they possessed great strength and a talent that defied the will of the heavens. Not just that, but their lifespan was ten times longer than that of a human.

They were indeed existences that defied heaven’s logic.

Unfortunately, even such a race wasn’t able to prosper forever. Their people declined over time, and several hundred thousand years ago they had neared extinction.

It seemed that afterwards, Heavenly Empress Xuanqing and Empyrean Primordius had built the Samsara Road together. Their goal was to draw support from the mighty strength of reincarnation through samsara and find the thread of hope for the survival of the primal god race.

But in the end, they had failed.

The Monster Emperor’s longevity feast was on an island deep in the center of the sea.

This island alone was 800 miles in diameter. All around this island were smaller islands that surrounded it like planets around a sun, dotting the landscape.

And in the seas amongst these islands, there were countless massive monster beasts, patrolling back and forth.

There were deep sea black turtles, horned sea flood dragons, heaven-swallowing pythons, sea hydras, and so forth.

These sea beasts were titanic in size and each one surpassed a Holy Lord in strength. All of them obeyed the commands of the monster race. If they were to battle, they would be a terrifying force.

“Senior Divine Dream! Brother Lin Ming!”

Suddenly, in the far off distance, a voice echoed out. Someone strode forwards in greeting, sending their regards first to Empyrean Divine Dream and then Lin Ming.

This person was unexpectedly White King, Empyrean Vast Universe’s core disciple. At the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, he had fought with Lin Ming on the arena stage!

Behind White King, there was a large and strong team of people. It was clear that Empyrean Vast Universe had also come.

“Long time no see.”

Lin Ming greeted. As he saw White King again, he felt his heart fill with emotion. For this longevity feast it was likely that all of the top young elites of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, those like Dragon Fang, Hang Chi, and Jun Bluemoon, would also come.

Of course, one of the main leads of this event, Xiao Moxian, was also one of the top geniuses from that year’s First Martial Meeting.

However, at the time of the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, Lin Ming would never have thought that he would one day come together with that overly arrogant and sometimes insufferably cute Xiao Moxian.

It could only be said that fate was far too wonderful.

Almost a hundred years had passed since that First Martial Meeting. Thinking back to those days, everyone had been far too young and filled with passion. Now that they met again, it was natural to be filled with emotion.

Chapter 1761 – Meeting Xiao Moxian

“Brat, are you looking to die!?”

The four minions surrounded Lin Ming. However, Lin Ming sat calmly in his seat, simply not getting up at all.

“You’re calling us minions? Hehe… just who do you think you are? Your status is given to you by humans, and when humans no longer exist, you’ll be nothing at all; even calling you a minion then would be too much for you! How much longer do you think you’ll be able to be so arrogant?”

The words of the four minions were forceful and menacing. Although they didn’t clearly state it, there was a hidden meaning in their words – that humanity would eventually be completely wiped out by the saints.

At that time when the young elites of humanity lost the asylum of their race, they would be as pitiful and pathetic as homeless dogs. They might as well become slaves of the saints.

It was also because of this reason that the saint martial artists were filled with energy and were incredibly conceited.

Although they were servants, they didn’t feel as if they were below humans. Rather, they felt as if their statuses were no different from those of the top young elites of humanity.

As these four people spoke, many of the human martial artists present frowned. Lin Ming slowly stood up from his seat, his aura as deep as a sea. Facing him, one couldn’t help but feel their heart skip a beat.

“Hey, you want to fight?” The four minions said.

Although the four minions said this, the truth was that they were afraid. After all, this was the Monster Emperor’s grand longevity feast and there were many Empyreans present. The four of them were borrowing the momentum and reputation of the saints to be cocky loudmouths, but it was impossible for them to strike out at Lin Ming at this longevity feast with so many Empyreans watching them.

Moreover, they didn’t know the limits of Lin Ming’s strength.

The group of four consisted of late Holy Lords and peak Holy Lords. If they couldn’t even face Lin Ming, they would lose all face for the saint race.

“Step back!”

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke up, his voice gloomy.

“Your Highness Saint Son…”

The four minions grit their teeth. Seeing the Good Fortune Saint Son’s cold gaze, they drew back.

The Good Fortune Saint Son looked at Lin Ming and chuckled. “What? Both of us are here to celebrate the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast, and the longevity feast hasn’t even started yet you’re trying to fight with my followers. If this is all you are then I have no interest in fighting you 40 years from now.”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s words dripped with a mocking tone, immediately placing Lin Ming on the same rank as his followers. If Lin Ming were truly someone with status, then there would be no point in facing off against his subordinates.

In the face of this taunting, Lin Ming maintained a smile throughout. “If the upper beam isn’t straight the lower beam will be crooked. Your servants know not the rules and loudly blather on as they please even when their master is speaking, not understanding the situation at all or knowing what to do. Really, even though these dogs were raised by you I have no idea what their master has taught them. If they are released on the street and randomly go around biting people then aren’t others allowed to beat them down with a stick?”

Lin Ming’s words struck back with equal harshness. His words caused the four minions to tremble. In such a situation there was nothing they could do; they could only endure the humiliation. The four of them had mocked Lin Ming but in the end they had brought trouble upon their own heads.

In regards to this, Empyrean Divine Dream faintly frowned with worry. Before this she had cautioned Lin Ming not to come into conflict with the Good Fortune Saint Son, but it seemed as if Lin Ming hadn’t heard her at all. Rather, it appeared he was deliberately targeting the Good Fortune Saint Son.

“This Lin Ming… what is he planning to do…” Empyrean Divine Dream looked towards Lin Ming, wanting to say some words, but eventually didn’t. In her mind, when Lin Ming did something he always acted within his limitations with full knowledge of the consequences.

“Your skills at being glib aren’t too bad.”

The Good Fortune Saint Son disdainfully laughed. “Do you even know your own strength? You are a mere half-step Holy Lord! 40 years from now, you should be able to break into the middle Holy Lord realm and achieve my current boundary. If that is true then I might be a little bit interested in you. Otherwise, you would be far too boring.”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, a hearty laugh echoed out. “Hahaha! Your Highness Saint Son, Sir Lin, the two of you are outstanding heroes and the day of your hundred year duel hasn’t arrived so there’s no need to act so unfriendly!”

At this time, a middle-aged man walked into the hall.

This middle-aged man stood tall and straight. His skin was fair and his eyes were profoundly deep. His black hair hung down to his waist. He had a majestic appearance, one that overflowed with a dashing heroic spirit.

This person was the true ruler of the monster race – the Monster Emperor.

The Monster Emperor’s appearance caused everyone present to calm down.

Lin Ming also respectfully bowed. The Monster Emperor was secretly paying attention to him. Lin Ming was well aware that the Monster Emperor knew about the matter of him taking Xiao Moxian’s primordial yin as well as her pregnancy.

However, he didn’t show obvious loathing like Empyrean Demondawn did. Rather, he maintained a calm and pleasant demeanor as if he knew nothing about that situation at all.

From this point, it couldn’t be said that the Monster Emperor’s background was deeper than Empyrean Demondawn’s. Rather, the Monster Emperor was someone that was good at concealing his true emotions and intentions. As for Empyrean Demondawn, he was blunt and inclined to go straight to the point. If Lin Ming had to compare the both of them, he naturally would pay more attention to the former.

As the Monster Emperor arrived, the Empyreans present rose up one at a time to congratulate him.

And at this time, there was an announcement of another higher level figure that arrived.

It was an old acquaintance of Lin Ming’s – Empyrean Vast Universe.

After Empyrean Vast Universe greeted the Monster Emperor and Divine Dream, he turned towards Lin Ming, a look of appreciation evident on his face.

In truth, the reason that Lin Ming set a hundred year duel with the Good Fortune Saint Son was because of Empyrean Vast Universe. Since Empyrean Vast Universe was protecting Lin Ming, the Good Fortune Saint Son had challenged Vast Universe to a duel in 300 years. Because Empyrean Vast Universe had been placed upon the crest of the waves, Lin Ming had instead spoken out to accept the challenge.

And from this point alone, Lin Ming owed graciousness to Empyrean Vast Universe.

“What a good young fellow, half-step Holy Lord! You’re just a step away from reaching the Holy Lord realm, in fact… you can break through whenever you want!”

Lin Ming’s cultivation speed left Empyrean Vast Universe flabbergasted. In the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting, Lin Ming had rolled over the competition. Amongst the other young elites of the Divine Realm, none of them were able to face him.

“White King, you should also learn a little from Lin Ming. You don’t have to do much. If you had even a fifth of Lin Ming’s achievements I would be more than content.”

White King was Empyrean Vast Universe’s apprentice and was also standing beside Lin Ming. As he faced Empyrean Vast Universe’s judging eyes, he secretly complained in his heart. To compare him with Lin Ming, wasn’t that just too difficult?

“Senior Vast Universe praises junior too much…” Lin Ming said. As he was about to exchange some more pleasantries with Empyrean Vast Universe, his body suddenly shook and the words he was about to speak caught in his throat. He froze where he stood.

He looked towards a corner of the main hall. From a side door, a black-clothed young girl had stepped out.

This young girl was accompanied by eight maids that walked with her. Her figure was slender and she was wearing a black formal dress. Her face was covered by a veil, only revealing a pair of beautiful eyes, making her seem like a dark enchantress of night.

She was Xiao Moxian.

Xiao Moxian’s current appearance was different from her usual style of dress. She had rid herself of her previously playful demeanor and gained a ladylike feeling, as soft and delicate as water.

However, Lin Ming knew that this sort of delicate and weak feeling wasn’t an act at all. Because Xiao Moxian’s cultivation had been sealed and she was also pregnant, she could really be called delicate and fragile right now.

Xiao Moxian’s appearance immediately drew everyone’s eyes.

Empyrean Demondawn had placed several cleverly crafted spells on Xiao Moxian’s body. No one knew that her cultivation had been sealed away, but only thought that she was deliberately concealing her aura.

And during this banquet, Xiao Moxian was the leader of the juniors from the monster and demon races. Thus, no one would do something so rude as to investigate her inner world. Even if they did, they would only find the Heaven Absorbing Demon Art within her, nothing else.

After Xiao Moxian appeared, her beautiful eyes looked over those present – she was searching for Lin Ming.

However, with her cultivation sealed away she couldn’t release her sense. To look for a single person in this massive longevity feast hall was not easy at all.

“I’m at the front left of you…”

At this time, a familiar true essence sound transmission echoed in Xiao Moxian’s ears. She trembled and looked towards Lin Ming.

As their eyes met, countless words seemed to be exchanged through them.

Xiao Moxian bit her lips and kept quiet. Tears seemed to shimmer in her eyes.

However, their eyes met for only a few breaths of time. Afterwards, Xiao Moxian turned towards the Monster Emperor.

From beginning to end, there was a pair of cold eyes looking at the both of them. The owner of these eyes was Empyrean Demondawn.

At this banquet, Empyrean Demondawn didn’t allow Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming to have any communications at all.

“Isn’t that Xiao Moxian? I haven’t seen her for several years but I never thought she would already turn from a naughty tomboy into a gentle and graceful woman!”

Someone in a guest seat praised.

“Whether it is the past or present, she can always leave one fascinated. Moreover, her physique is special. Anyone that can marry her and dual cultivate with her is truly blessed and honored!”

Several guests discussed amongst each other. Many handsome young elites looked towards Xiao Moxian, admiration and awe in their eyes.

Even though so many years had passed, Xiao Moxian and Frost Dream remained the two most outstanding young women in the entire Divine Realm.

They didn’t have any expectations of Frost Dream – no one could win her over.

Thus, Xiao Moxian naturally became the dream lover of countless men.

“These stupid humans. They don’t know that Empyrean Demondawn and the Monster Emperor have already agreed to my marriage proposition! It won’t be long before that goddess of your hearts is waiting upon my crotch!”

Not too far away, the Good Fortune Saint Son listened to these young elites talk, a smug smile on his face.

Xiao Moxian was a yummy little dish he was destined to eat. As the Good Fortune Saint Son thought of taking Xiao Moxian from the young elites of humanity, he felt filled with a deep sense of accomplishment.

In particular, after listening to the discussions of these young elites from the Divine Realm and then looking at the admiration in their eyes, a feeling of superiority rose in his heart.

Not only would he eventually destroy the Divine Realm in the future but he would even steal away the most peerless beauty of the Divine Realm. This conquest left the Good Fortune Saint Son extremely satisfied.

He playfully looked at Xiao Moxian, playing with the teacup in his hand.

Because the Good Fortune Saint Son was sitting in a seat near the front, he was quite close to Xiao Moxian. Xiao Moxian could faintly feel the Good Fortune Saint Son’s gaze on her, and she turned to look at him.

Seeing Xiao Moxian look at him, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s smile became even wider. He laughed and whispered, “Don’t worry, there is not even an incense stick of time left. Once the longevity feast begins I will take out a congratulatory gift. At the same time as I offer this gift, I will also discuss marriage with Empyrean Demondawn and the Monster Emperor. At that time, you will be mine.”

Chapter 1762 - The Method Of Becoming A True Divinity

As Xiao Moxian felt the Good Fortune Saint Son’s predatory eyes on her, she was filled with disgust. However, in front of the Monster Emperor, she could only turn her head and ignore him.

“Your Highness Saint Son, you seem to be quite interested in that half-phoenix body girl?”

The Empyrean who came with the Good Fortune Saint Son to celebrate the longevity feast slowly commented.

This saint Empyrean’s title was Shatter and he was a peak Empyrean. The reason he followed the Good Fortune Saint Son here to the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast was to display the strength of the saints as well as to protect the Saint Son.

“This Xiao Moxian’s physique is extraordinary. If I can dual cultivate with her then it will be a great help to me in attacking the sixth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art.”

The reason that the Good Fortune Saint Son was able to break into the fifth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art was because a number of coincidences had luckily come together. As for the sixth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art, it was far more difficult. Without reaching the Great World King realm, the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t have any confidence in success.

But if he could dual cultivate with Xiao Moxian, taking her primordial yin and also fusing with her God Beast blood, that would be greatly advantageous to his body transformation technique.

With that, he might be able to attack the sixth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art at the World King realm.

Even if he were to fail he would still be able to gather experience.

The earlier he broke into the sixth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art, the more benefits he would have. It would form an even more superior foundation when he tried to break into the realm of True Divinity in the future.

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, almost all the great guests that the Monster Emperor invited to his longevity feast arrived.

Rulers of influences from all over delivered congratulatory gifts in droves.

Most of these were Empyrean level treasures. If they were placed at the Divine Rune City Auction, they could sell for several hundred millions of points.

Empyrean Vast Universe gifted the great egg of an ancient desolate beast. Empyrean Traceless gifted an Empyrean spirit treasure that was dug out from an ancient ruin.

In the Divine Realm, reciprocating favors was an extremely important unspoken rule.

After being gifted these treasures, the Monster Emperor would eventually have to return the favor in the future.

As for Lin Ming, White King, and the other juniors, they naturally sat still in their seats. It wasn’t their turn to deliver congratulatory gifts.

And at this moment, it was time for the Good Fortune Saint Son to step on stage.

He laid down his teacup and strode atop the divine altar. Behind him followed his four followers. The four followers held two items; one was an exquisite pill box and the other was a simple jade box.

These two items immediately attracted everyone’s gaze; they wanted to see just what sort of gift the Good Fortune Saint Son would send out.

After arriving in front of the Monster Emperor, the Good Fortune Saint Son ordered his follower to open the pill box. This pill box contained a dark green pill the size of a longan. A fragrant medicinal scent wafted into the air, refreshing to the senses.

All of the martial artists present had discerning eyes. They could see at a glance that this was a transcendent divine pill.

A transcendent divine pill was a pill that an Empyrean level supreme elder could take. It could help an Empyrean level martial artist increase their cultivation or consolidate their foundation. It was a rare treasure, and if one were to fall into a World King influence, it would set off a bloody war of terror.

However, in the scene of the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast, a transcendent divine pill wasn’t much at all.

For instance, the Empyrean spirit treasure that Empyrean Traceless gifted was far more precious than this transcendent divine pill. For the Good Fortune Saint Son, someone who came from a True Divinity influence, to take out such a congratulatory gift, it was simply far too lacking.

Many human Empyreans were watching with critical eyes. They all wanted to see what the saints would be willing to put out. After all, there was still another box – just what was in it?

“Haha, what a wonderful transcendent divine pill!”

The Monster Emperor happily laughed. One of his disciples standing beside him moved forwards and received the pill.

The truth was that to the Monster Emperor, who was almost a peak Empyrean, this transcendent divine pill didn’t have much use at all. The most it could do was help raise a God Beast.

But at this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son picked up the simple jade box from his follower’s hands. The previous pill box had been opened by his follower, but this time the Good Fortune Saint Son was personally opening the jade box.

Within this jade box were layers of yellow silk. And above these layers of silk was a pure black jade slip.

This jade slip resembled black agate, shimmering with a profound light.

The Good Fortune Saint Son slowly picked up this jade slip, a happy expression on his face. “The previous transcendent divine pill was only for Your Majesty to casually appreciate. This… is the true gift…”

“This is…” The Monster Emperor looked at the Good Fortune Saint Son. He didn’t know why, but the black jade slip in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s hands made his heart beat faster.

“Your Majesty Monster Emperor, this is an inheritance fragment that my saint race’s Good Fortune Saint Sovereign obtained when he ventured into an ancient ruin. Although this inheritance is incomplete, it actually records the methods of breaking into the realm of True Divinity. Today, I bring this out as a present for Your Majesty’s longevity feast.”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s voice wasn’t loud, but his words spread through the entire audience!

For a time, everyone was utterly shocked!

In particular, many Empyreans present shot up from their seats to get a closer look.

All of their eyes locked onto the black jade slip.

The method to break into True Divinity!

No one imagined that the Good Fortune Saint Son would take out such a precious congratulatory gift at the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast.

Some Empyreans felt their hearts begin to race.

3.6 billion years ago, during the last great calamity, the saints waged a great war against humanity. Humanity had put forth the complete power of their race to survive and even Empyrean Divine Seal perished in the flames of war.

In that war, although humanity managed to force back the saints, their foundation had been severely damaged and countless inheritances had been cut off. Ever since then, there had never been a human supreme elder who had managed to break into the realm of True Divinity.

Many people suspected that the reason no human was able to break into the realm of True Divinity was because they had lost their most precious inheritances. In other words, the cultivation methods for breaking into True Divinity!

Now that the Good Fortune Saint Son suddenly brought out such a black jade slip that contained the lost knowledge, how could the Empyreans present not be excited!

For a time, the Monster Emperor’s mouth turned dry. He stared at the jade slip in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s hands and couldn’t help but probe it with his sense. And, the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t stop him either.

The Monster Emperor could feel the ancient and complex Laws within, leaving him shocked. With his sight, he could naturally make out many things. He could feel that this black jade slip truly did contain the methods to break into True Divinity!

“This…”

The Monster Emperor’s fingers trembled. No one could understand the temptation that the realm of True Divinity held towards an Empyrean.

Once one became an Empyrean, they could freely wander the world, ruling all within their sight. However, there were still many things they couldn’t reconcile with.

They couldn’t see the end of the road of martial arts and their lives were limited to a hundred million years. They couldn’t help but want to break into True Divinity, stepping further onto the road of martial arts, climbing higher so that they could see further ahead!

Even Empyrean Demondawn wasn’t able to remain calm upon seeing this jade slip.

The road of True Divinity, that was his lifelong pursuit!

“This move, is far too ruthless…”

In the honored seats, Empyrean Divine Dream’s eyebrows pressed together. As she saw the black jade slip in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s hands, she didn’t feel any temptation or excitement at all.

Rather, dark clouds began to cover her mind.

In a sense, the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast was a competition between the humans and saints. Each race would reveal their own strength and value and the monster and demon races would choose the one with more to offer.

Of course, from the very start the monster and demon races were already favoring the saints. The saints were simply far stronger than humanity was. Humanity wasn’t able to compare with them.

Even if Empyrean Divine Dream had already mentally prepared for the monster and demon races to ally with the saints, she never imagined that the Good Fortune Saint Son would take out the method to becoming a True Divinity at this longevity feast!

Whether it was the impact to the monster and demon races, or whether it was the impact to the human Empyreans present, this was a blow of incalculable damage!

It had to be known that humanity also had many Empyreans that were stranded before the gates of True Divinity. For them, True Divinity was a boundary they yearned for even in their dreams.

The saints took out this jade slip in order to easily subdue the monster and demon races.

Now, the problem was whether or not there were dastardly traitors that would appear amongst humanity’s Empyreans. Because of their desire for the method to break into True Divinity, would any of them switch sides and join the saints?

It was said that traitors were worse than dogs. Although everyone understood this truth, whether it was the mortal world or the world of martial artists, during every war there would always emerge a large number of traitors that were willing to sell out their allies.

The reason they did so was because the benefits of joining the other side were far too attractive. Even if these people had to live as slaves or dogs, to them it was still better than dying in battle for their race, because if they died they would really have nothing left!

As Empyrean Divine Dream thought of this, she found it increasingly difficult to remain calm. Although the Good Fortune Saint Son’s actions were brazen and ostentatious, the truth was that this was simply a façade he put up. Every action he did was to push humanity further and further towards the edge of the abyss!

This was true in the previous negotiations between the humans and saints where he put forth all sorts of impossible unfavorable conditions to lay down the future downfall of humanity. Not just that, but he simultaneously forced Empyrean Vast Universe to a challenge that was eventually received by Lin Ming.

It was also true in the following dozens of years when the saints and humans confronted each other. He directed the saint race’s armies to slowly nibble away at the territory of the Divine Realm.

Or even, for these past years, the Good Fortune Saint Son had repeatedly challenged human World Kings and Great World Kings, defeating them one after another and striking at the confidence of humanity and pushing the momentum of the saints to the peak!

Finally, at the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast began, the Good Fortune Saint Son took out the method to break into True Divinity. This was almost the final straw that crushed humanity’s last hopes.

Facing this sort of opponent, Empyrean Divine Dream felt deep unease, her back pushed to the wall!

It had to be known that the Good Fortune Saint Son was only several hundred years old and he also possessed the Grandmist Spirit Bead; his future was limitless!

He was the chosen descendant of the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign. In the future he would inevitably become the scourge of humanity, perhaps even becoming the one to dig their grave!

Originally, the supreme elders of humanity hoped that they could drag on the time before the great calamity truly erupted. The longer it took, the more beneficial it was because this allowed more time for the juniors of humanity, those like Lin Ming, Frost Dream, and Dragon Fang, to grow up.

But now, it seemed that the more they dragged on, the worse the situation became for them.

Currently, the human race seemed as if it would soon lose the monster and demon races as allies. And then, perhaps in just a few dozen more years, humanity would start to slowly crumble from within due to the pressure of the saints, and there would be people in their ranks surrendering on their own volition.

Once someone surrendered, there would be more and more that followed at an ever-increasing pace. If so, humanity would soon perish!

To subdue the enemy without fighting, this was the Good Fortune Saint Son’s plans.

While the saints were at war with the spiritas, he was unable to spare enough power to annihilate the humans for the time being. However, by increasing the pressure step by step, he could slowly disintegrate humanity from within. After all, with the pressure slowly increasing over time, there would inevitably be those within the human race that couldn’t withstand it and would betray their people!

This move, it was truly incredibly vicious!

Chapter 1765 – Spear Drawn

She chose Lin Ming! How was that possible!?

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s originally handsome face almost instantly turned liver red!

In the presence of so many people, he had spoken while utterly confident in himself, but now he had been struck silly by Xiao Moxian!

Before this he had clearly communicated with Empyrean Demondawn and the Monster Emperor, neither one of them expressing any problems, and even Xiao Moxian had agreed to the marriage proposal at the longevity feast. But now she had backed down from her promise!

At this time, everyone present began to speak in hushed whispers.

“Xian Moxian actually chose Lin Ming? What’s going on here?”

“Empyrean Demondawn clearly never thought this would happen. There must be something suspicious going on.”

Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son’s conditions were clear to all present; it was easy to see just who was the superior choice. In all fairness, even if any of the young human elites were in Xiao Moxian’s position, they would have chosen the Good Fortune Saint Son. Moreover, Empyrean Demondawn had chosen the Good Fortune Saint Son, so how could Xiao Moxian shame her grandfather in front of so many people?

In this sort of situation, there was only a single explanation. That was that between Xiao Moxian and Lin Ming, there was already some profound relationship, and they had already pledged themselves to each other!

And now Lin Ming proposing marriage might have been something that he and Xiao Moxian had discussed before already!

Upon realizing this, many people’s complexions changed. They looked towards the Good Fortune Saint Son with gloating eyes, waiting to see the play unfold.

Everyone thought that Lin Ming leapt up because there was something wrong with his head and he was simply asking to be punished.

But now, it seemed that Lin Ming had already won the prize. As for the Good Fortune Saint Son, he had merely come afterwards as a clown, nothing but a sucker.

As the Good Fortune Saint Son felt the thoughtful and mocking eyes of these people upon him, his lungs nearly exploded with rage!

He had lived his life high-spirited and full of pride. Since when had he received such an insult?

“Demondawn, what a good granddaughter you’ve taught!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son glared at Empyrean Demondawn.

Empyrean Demondawn was also surprised and furious right now. As he looked at Xiao Moxian, a thick killing intent burst out from his eyes.

During this longevity feast, Xiao Moxian’s choice had stripped him of any face he had!

“You unfilial girl, what use have I of you!”

In his rage, Empyrean Demondawn’s eyes had turned blood red. He lifted his hand and aimed a slap towards Xiao Moxian!

This palm caused a violent wind to stir up. Empyrean Demondawn certainly couldn’t bear killing Xiao Moxian, but this slap could still tear her skin!

Seeing this, Lin Ming felt his heart tighten. He wanted to intercept the slap but he knew that if he were to act out at this time, he would suffer the full might of Empyrean Demondawn. Empyrean Demondawn would take advantage of this situation to severely wound him, and in his rage, Empyrean Demondawn might even try to take his life.

Lin Ming could only watch helplessly on. Xiao Moxian bit her lips and closed her eyes.

And just as Empyrean Demondawn’s palm was about to strike Xiao Moxian’s face, a gentle and soft blue light wrapped around his palm like a ribbon, causing it to halt where it was.

Peng!

The pale blue ribbon of light suddenly tightened. Empyrean Demondawn stiffened. He turned his head and saw that the one who bound his hand was Empyrean Divine Dream.

Empyrean Divine Dream simply raised her right hand, an icy blue ribbon of ephemeral light flashing out from her hands and winding around Empyrean Demondawn’s. It was impossible to tell whether this ribbon was a beam of light or a magic tool.

Empyrean Demondawn looked at Divine Dream with smoldering anger.

“You are stopping me?”

“That’s right. I am stopping you…” Empyrean Divine Dream’s voice was cold and desolate. She stood up, facing Empyrean Demondawn.

She felt that Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian’s actions had truly and maliciously torn apart Empyrean Demondawn’s face, and his fury was justified.

But, she always stood on the side of humanity.

No matter what happened, she would support Lin Ming unconditionally.

Thus, although her words were calm, they were filled with a potent and forceful momentum.

If this is the limit of your strength, so what if I stop you?

“You…!”

Empyrean Demondawn felt his blood shoot towards his temples. He was originally breathless with anger, and now he also bumped into this aggressive Empyrean Divine Dream. And, what was worst was that he couldn’t untangle this blue ribbon from his hand. The blue ribbon seemed to contain a sly soul force. As it wrapped around his hand, the soul force pierced into his own spiritual sea, aiming towards his soul with thousands of icy blue steel needles. As long as he even thought about moving his right hand, an agonizing pain would shoot out from his spiritual sea.

“Divine Dream… has already reached this level?”

Empyrean Demondawn felt his palms become wet with sweat. As he looked at Divine Dream again, he had already slowly calmed down.

He grimly said, “Marriage matters are decided by me. You all are nothing but bystanders. What right do you have to interfere in the family matters of my Demondawn Heavenly Palace?”

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “I naturally cannot interfere in the family matters of your Demondawn Heavenly Palace. It is only that… the Good Fortune Saint Son proposed marriage and you happily agreed, but when Lin Ming proposed marriage, you hatefully glared at him. After that, when Xiao Moxian chose Lin Ming, you immediately moved to slap her in the presence of everyone here. Do you think that our Lin Ming is so easy to insult?”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s voice was clear and resonant, going straight into the hearts of most of the human guests present. As they listened to her, they also felt that Empyrean Demondawn was too great a bully.

“Hahahaha!” Empyrean Demondawn laughed. “Divine Dream! I know what you are thinking! You simply do not want to see the monster and demon races ally with the saints! You would try everything in your power to destroy the marriage alliance! Good! Very good! In I, Demondawn’s life, what I hate most is others using ruthless methods to force me to do something! The more you try to force me, the more I will never allow your plans to succeed!

“Today, allow me to tell you something! The alliance between the monster and demon races with the saints was decided by me! This marriage is also decided by me! Marriage of the children has always been the decision of the parents and elders; this is a completely justified matter! No matter how you try to twist things, I am the one standing on principle here! Let me take a good look and see just how you will take away my granddaughter today!”

Empyrean Demondawn’s words were the same as tearing apart any semblance of respect. Originally, with the humans present here, the demons and saints wouldn’t have flagrantly proposed an alliance. Rather, they took the circuitous route of proposing a marriage alliance. After all, they had to consider the feelings of all the human martial artists present. But now, Empyrean Demondawn had acknowledged his alliance with the saints in front of everyone. This caused the complexions of all the human guests to immediately become ugly.

Divine Dream frowned. With things having come this far, today’s events could no longer be salvaged!

Many people felt that Lin Ming’s actions of suddenly proposing marriage today and standing in sharp opposition to him were far too inconsiderate. Indeed, while Lin Ming had slapped the Good Fortune Saint Son’s face and had made him a public cuckold, although this was enjoyable to see, what would change?

His extreme actions had instead aroused the fury of Empyrean Demondawn, causing him to slide towards the saints even faster.

And no matter how powerful Empyrean Divine Dream was, it was impossible for her to use force to take Xiao Moxian away from here.

Then, Xiao Moxian would still have to marry the Saint Son. And because of today’s matters, whether it was in the demon, monster, or saint races, she would receive a cold shoulder from all of them and likely be mistreated by the Good Fortune Saint Son in the future!

Thinking of this, many people looked towards Lin Ming, feeling that he was just far too young and naïve. But now, he had ridden the tiger and could no longer climb down. Just how would today’s events end?

At this time, Lin Ming’s face darkened. He looked towards the furious Empyrean Demondawn and said, “Senior Demondawn, I respect you as a senior and will allow you to insult me as you please. But, I hope that you will not reach for a yard after taking an inch… after all, there are some matters that both of us wouldn’t like to be publicized, right?”

Lin Ming’s words left the martial artists present stupefied.

As a junior, Lin Ming dared to speak like this to an Empyrean, warning them not to take a yard after taking an inch! Was he looking to die!?

However, what surprised everyone was that even though Empyrean Demondawn was bristling with rage, he didn’t erupt. Rather, he maintained total silence, glaring at Lin Ming with eyes filled with hate.

He certainly knew what ‘matters’ Lin Ming was speaking of – it was the matter of Xiao Moxian’s pregnancy!

If news of this were to be revealed, the Good Fortune Saint Son might immediately storm away in a rage!

At that time, the alliance between the monster and demon races with the saints might be ruined.

Lin Ming’s words had struck at his most fatal point!

Empyrean Demondawn couldn’t understand how Lin Ming knew of Xiao Moxian’s pregnancy. He had clearly sealed away her strength with layers of spells and placed her under house arrest. But now, as he recalled Lin Ming’s proposal and Xiao Moxian’s betrayal, it was likely they had come to this agreement in advance!

This caused Empyrean Demondawn to feel as if he had been played by two juniors.

“This brat, he shouldn’t rashly destroy Xian’er’s reputation like this…”

Empyrean Demondawn felt a little fear. He didn’t dare to push Lin Ming too far. If he pushed Lin Ming over the cliff, Empyrean Demondawn would not only lose his alliance with the saints but also lose Xiao Moxian. In the future when they met, his granddaughter would treat him like an enemy.

“What’s wrong? Empyrean Demondawn is enduring the insult? What does Lin Ming have on him?”

Everyone glanced at each other, making all sorts of guesses.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt his intestines twisting together. He didn’t know what game Lin Ming and Empyrean Demondawn were playing, but now he felt that at this time, he had been made a fool.

He felt that staying here any longer was meaningless.

Even if he were the one to win Xiao Moxian’s hand in marriage at the end, he would still be ridiculed by all the young elites of the Divine Realm.

“Lin Ming, you remember for me. 40 years from now in our life or death battle, I will break apart all your meridians and make you beg for death! You only have 40 years of freedom left. Make sure you enjoy the final years of your life!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son looked at Lin Ming as if he were looking at a dead man, his eyes filled with absolute confidence. It was as if 40 years from now, killing Lin Ming would be no harder than slaughtering a chicken or butchering a dog.

But at this time, something occurred that left the Good Fortune Saint Son completely dumbfounded.

He stared blankly on as Lin Ming quietly extracted the Phoenix Blood Spear from his spatial ring. The spear point was cold, the light reflecting off it menacingly!

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and pointed it straight towards the Good Fortune Saint Son. His aura suddenly invisibly exuded outwards. At this time, Lin Ming was like an unrivalled divine spear, reckless and fierce!

He clearly and calmly said, “Since we must fight, why wait the full hundred years? Let’s settle this today!”

“What!?”

The entire audience wasn’t able to believe their own ears!

Chapter 1767 – Nine Orifice Exquisite Pill

“You…”

The Good Fortune Saint Son took in a deep breath – he never imagined that Lin Ming would pull out such a treasure.

Generally speaking, when comparing the same level of treasure, a spirit treasure was slightly less valuable than an inheritance.

But what Lin Ming took out was a peak True Divinity spirit treasure and what the Good Fortune Saint Son took out was only an extremely incomplete True Divinity inheritance.

Looking at the two items, the difference was far too great.

After fishing through his spatial ring, the Good Fortune Saint Son reluctantly took out an almost complete human True Divinity inheritance.

Even in the Good Fortune Saint Palace, there was an extremely small number of these inheritances.

Lin Ming probed the contents of the inheritance with his sense and was able to discern that it was indeed a cultivation method.

He had studied the Asura Laws, a cultivation method that already surpassed a True Divinity cultivation method. With that as his foundation, his ability to appraise True Divinity cultivation methods was beyond the understanding of the average person.

He could just barely judge the exquisiteness of the Laws within. What the Good Fortune Saint Son took out was only a low rank cultivation method, but its advantage was that it was complete.

After Lin Ming investigated the jade slip, the other Empyreans present also did so, unable to withstand their curiosity. Even the Monster Emperor probed with his sense.

However, besides Divine Dream, none of the other Empyreans had ever touched upon the domain of True Divinity. For a time, they had difficulties discerning the profound principles within.

“A lower-middle rank True Divinity cultivation method. Do you really plan on using that little thing to bet against my Black Dragon Spear?” Lin Ming tauntingly said. But as he spoke, his words shocked the Empyreans present. How had Lin Ming seen through the rank of the cultivation method?

He was only a half-step Holy Lord, and yet he was familiar with the boundaries of a True Divinity cultivation method?

Moreover, from the expressions of the Good Fortune Saint Son and that peak saint Empyrean, it seemed that Lin Ming’s judgment was correct!

“Humph! Even if I take out a more precious cultivation method, so what? You think you can obtain it?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son taunted back. But taunts were taunts; if he wasn’t able to take out an equivalent amount in treasures then he really wouldn’t have any face left. He also took out another jade slip fragment and pill.

This cultivation method was even worse. In fact, the entire Good Fortune Saint Palace only had these two human cultivation method inheritances. Their grades were extremely ordinary and the second set was highly incomplete.

But as for the pill, it was of an exceedingly high quality, nearly reaching the level of a True Divinity spirit pill.

“Nine Orifices Exquisite Pill! Although this is a transcendent divine pill, its level nears that of True Divinity. It was originally refined by His Majesty the Saint Sovereign for me to break into the World King realm! The materials required to make this pill are extremely rare and its value is no less than that of an incomplete True Divinity cultivation method fragment!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son bragged, Lin Ming looked over the pill, overjoyed in his heart. That was actually a pill refined by the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign, a top quality body transformation pill!

“This is really an unexpected harvest!”

Lin Ming thought to himself. In truth, he didn’t care about the rank of the human True Divinity cultivation methods at all.

As long as he had a True Divinity cultivation method, no matter high or low its grade was, it could stabilize the hearts of the human Empyreans and make it so that they didn’t defect to the saints.

This was enough.

To expect any human Empyreans to practice this True Divinity cultivation method and complete their breakthroughs in time to help in the great calamity was simply unrealistic. This was because their chances of doing so were pitifully low to begin with, and a breakthrough would require millions of years anyway.

In the great calamity, this would be of no help at all.

Lin Ming withdrew his sense and flippantly said, “With all that random stuff added together, it’s just barely enough.”

These few words had the Good Fortune Saint Son feeling wretched enough to vomit blood.

He felt very aggrieved. He had taken out all sorts of treasures, including even the Nine Orifices Exquisite Pill that he couldn’t bear to eat, and yet it was being described as ‘random stuff’ by Lin Ming.

However, in all fairness, it really wasn’t much to look at when compared to Lin Ming’s black spear that came from nowhere.

Then, Lin Ming turned to Empyrean Demondawn.

His words were no longer polite, because he knew that being polite had no use now. “Demondawn, the Good Fortune Saint Son has already agreed, now it’s you. If I win, I will take away Xian’er!”

Just this gambling fight with the Good Fortune Saint Son wasn’t enough. If Empyrean Demondawn didn’t agree, it was meaningless.

Empyrean Demondawn sneered. “You think you can win? What a joke!”

“Since you already think I cannot win, what’s the problem of making a promise to me?”

Empyrean Demondawn disdainfully said, “I don’t believe you have any chance of winning but I also don’t like being played by others, especially a junior like you. Why should I bother with you!?”

“Is that so…” Lin Ming traced his dantian and a black light projected out from his inner world, forming an image projection in the space near him.

In this projection there was actually a titanic black egg shown. The surface of this egg was covered with patterns, looking mystical and ancient.

Through the eggshell, if one looked extremely carefully, they could see a strong and healthy life within, one that constantly exuded waves of life aura like crashing waves!

“This is…” Empyrean Demondawn was panic-stricken. “Dragon egg! And it is a royal dragon egg!”

The monster race possessed God Beasts, but they were extremely rare. As for royal God Beasts, there were even less of them!

Empyrean Demondawn never imagined that Lin Ming would put out a royal dragon egg.

Moreover, what was rare was that this dragon egg had developed extremely well in Lin Ming’s inner world. Once it hatched it would soar into the heavens, becoming a powerful young dragon!

“This brat, where did he get so many treasures!”

First it was a peak True Divinity spirit treasure and then afterwards a dragon egg. These were things that even Empyrean Demondawn didn’t possess!

Many of the extraordinary characters present were stunned. Perhaps even just a part of Lin Ming’s treasures was worth far more than their total assets combined!

“If I lose, then this dragon egg is yours!”

Lin Ming grit his teeth as he spoke. This was the life legacy left behind by Senior Black Dragon; he absolutely could not lose!

“I can’t believe you are willing to!”

Empyrean Demondawn’s eye burned brightly. He could actually sense that this dragon egg had already become one with Lin Ming and they shared both flesh and blood. Once it hatched from the egg, it would be greatly helpful to Lin Ming’s strength. If he were to leave this egg at the monster and demon races, that would be a tremendous loss to him.

He was staking everything he had on this single gamble – could he really defeat the Good Fortune Saint Son?

Just as Empyrean Demondawn thought of this, he immediately felt it was impossible.

“Good! If you can win then I will let you take away Xian’er. But at the same time, I will also announce that me and Xian’er have cut off all ties as a grandparent and grandchild!”

Empyrean Demondawn’s words were watertight. Drawing back, even if Lin Ming won and Xiao Moxian married him, there wasn’t any loss.

In that sort of situation, Lin Ming would already have been heaven-defying to the extreme!

This sort of heaven-defying talent would be enough to make up for his disadvantage in age!

Even if he couldn’t play much of a role in the great calamity, it wouldn’t be easy for the saints to kill him either!

Once the great calamity arrived, Lin Ming could quietly endure and cultivate. Then, one day, he could rely on his strength to reverse the heavens!

At that time, if Xiao Moxian were to follow Lin Ming, Empyrean Demondawn could feel relieved about her.

And even if Empyrean Demondawn had chosen wrongly in this great calamity and wasn’t able to bear the consequences of his failure, even if he were killed, Xiao Moxian could still rebuild the demon race and allow them to continue onwards.

As for him cutting off his relations with her, that was to draw a clear boundary between them, so there were more escape routes for her.

If he really did choose wrongly, then cutting off relations could help protect Xiao Moxian.

Xiao Moxian shivered, remaining silent.

Lin Ming said, “Not only will I take away Xian’er, but if I win I want to take something from you – the Annihilation Fire Elemental.”

When Lin Ming and Xiao Moxian had killed the Undying Polar Ice, they had obtained the Undying Inferno’s soul fire afterwards.

Lin Ming had given the soul fire to Xiao Moxian, but she had initially refused. This was because Lin Ming would soon attempt a breakthrough into the third Dao Palace of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace – the Extreme Polar Dao Palace. At that time, he would need to choose two types of source strengths to serve as the catalyst. To Lin Ming, the two source strengths most appropriate were Fire Elementals and Thunder Sources.

Xiao Moxian wanted to give the Undying Inferno’s soul fire to Lin Ming to help him break through the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, but he refused.

One reason was because it would just be a waste of such a treasure. Moreover, it would be incomparably difficult for him to find a Thunder Source that was of similar quality to the Undying Inferno’s soul fire to pair with it.

Later, Xiao Moxian told Lin Ming that in Demondawn Heavenly Palace, there was an Annihilation Fire Elemental that had been saved for her. It could be used to help Lin Ming break into the Extreme Polar Dao Palace.

Now, Lin Ming natural took advantage of this moment to bring it up.

Empyrean Demondawn slightly frowned but didn’t refuse. The Annihilation Fire Elemental was originally to be given to Xiao Moxian. Although he had always been harsh and demanding of her, everything he did was for the demon race and to guarantee the foundation of their people. He also hoped that she would live a long and good life.

“Fine!” Empyrean Demondawn agreed.

Lin Ming took a deep breath and turned toward the Good Fortune Saint Son. With this, everything else had been settled.

All that was left over was…

To fight!

Chapter 1768 – Scorching Blood Sun

In this battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son, Lin Ming had bet nearly everything he had!

To win, was to forge a future for humanity and allow them a chance to breathe and gather themselves!

To lose, was to lose the Black Dragon Spear, to lose the black dragon egg, and to lose Xiao Moxian. This was a price that Lin Ming absolutely could not withstand!

As for how strong the Good Fortune Saint Son truly was, Lin Ming had no absolutely no idea.

If he were to fight the Good Fortune Saint Son at the end of the full 100 years, then he would have absolute confidence in victory. But now, because of what happened with Xiao Moxian, he had no choice but to fight here and now.

In this battle, Lin Ming didn’t know how many cards the Good Fortune Saint Son would have in his hands, nor did he know what kind of cultivation method the Good Fortune Divine Art was.

Thus, for this battle, Lin Ming had already thrown everything he had on the table and cut off all paths of retreat. He was determined to fight until the end!

On the other side, the Good Fortune Saint Son similarly couldn’t understand Lin Ming.

As for the depths of Lin Ming’s strength, not even Xiao Moxian was completely clear.

“I really have no idea where your courage comes from…”

The Good Fortune Saint Son stared at Lin Ming’s Black dragon Spear. Towards that spear, he felt nothing but incomparable jealousy. As long as he defeated Lin Ming, that spear was his!

He couldn’t take a liking to something like an Empyrean spirit treasure, but as for a peak top level True Divinity spirit treasure, let alone possessing one, he had only ever seen two in his entire life.

“If you want to deliver me your treasures, then come!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, his body flashed and he flew out from the main hall.

Lin Ming followed close behind.

In the blink of an eye, the two left the divine palace and flew a hundred miles away, floating high above the skies of the primal jungle island beneath them.

All around them great mountains towered and massive trees loomed!

This world was located within the monster race’s Black Pagoda. It was an ancient ruin opened up by an ancient True Divinity level powerhouse and the space here was as stable as a boundless true universe. No matter how Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son fought here, it would be impossible for them to cause this world to collapse.

Behind Lin Ming, the other Empyreans and young elites flew out in abundance, including even the Monster Emperor and Empyrean Demondawn.

All of them were watching this battle.

And outside of the divine palace, all of the young disciples that were waiting, as well the massive number of monster race disciples and followers, were all shocked as they looked up and saw Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son fly high up in the air, confronting each other, and then the droves of high level figures that flew after them.

What was going on here? Why did it seem that Lin Ming was going to fight the Good Fortune Saint Son?

Before they could think further, there was a loud ring as the Good Fortune Saint Son drew out a heavy sword from his spatial ring. This heavy sword was pitch black and didn’t give off any light at all. It was as long as a person and looked incredibly heavy.

The heavy sword’s blade had no edge, but with a weapon of this level, whether there was an edge on the blade no longer mattered.

Seeing this heavy sword appear, the human Empyreans present felt their hearts shake. “This is…”

The aura emitting from the Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword was clearly far inferior to Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear. But, it was far, far mightier than any ordinary Empyrean spirit treasure!

“That is a True Divinity spirit treasure, but amongst the lowest level…”

Empyrean Divine Dream faintly whispered. Her words caused everyone’s hearts to skip a beat. They felt that Lin Ming was inferior to the Good Fortune Saint Son, but by relying on the Black Dragon Spear, he should be able to make up for a part of the difference. Yet now, the Good Fortune Saint Son had also taken out a True Divinity spirit treasure!

The Good Fortune Saint Son diabolically grinned. “I am skilled in all weapons. Swords, sabers, spears, anything I touch I can wield! Your spear shall be taken by me!”

Although he was arrogant and insolent, he wouldn’t lower his guard. He didn’t believe that Lin Ming would be so stupid and freely deliver such treasures into his hand. But no matter what cards Lin Ming had up his sleeve, he had absolute confidence he would win!

And at this time, Lin Ming did something incredibly mind-boggling.

They saw Lin Ming put away the Black Dragon Spear and take out the Phoenix Blood Spear once more. He wanted to use the Phoenix Blood Spear to fight the Good Fortune Saint Son!

The eyes of all martial artists present turned as wide as full moons.

What was Lin Ming doing? Things had already come this far and he still wanted to hold back? Was he insane?

The Phoenix Blood Spear was only an ordinary spirit artifact. It could just barely manage to face an Empyrean spirit treasure, much less a True Divinity spirit treasure. It might even be instantly split in half by the Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword!

“Lin Ming! You brat, what are you doing!”

Empyrean Vast Universe was already breathless with anxiousness.

But Lin Ming remained unperturbed. He still used the Phoenix Blood Spear to face the Good Fortune Saint Son.

The Black Dragon Spear was almost 20 billion jins heavy. In order for Lin Ming to use it, he would have to consume his strength at an alarming rate. In the past, when killing the Undying Polar Ice, Lin Ming using the Black Dragon Spear in a single all-out attack had exhausted nearly half his strength.

After that, Lin Ming entered the final trial’s sixth level and obtained the Asura Sutra’s second volume. With several years of training, his comprehension and skill in the Asura Laws increased by leaps and bounds. Finally, he could use the Asura Laws to control the Black Dragon Spear to barely utilize a few percent of its power. However, this had to be done when a battle reached its most white-hot stage.

Otherwise, he would rapidly exhaust his strength and no longer be able to defeat the Good Fortune Saint Son. At that time, Lin Ming would only be able to wait to be struck down.

In a way, it was similar to a long distance contest. If he sprinted at the start it would be impossible to keep running near the end. Only at the final stretch where he ran with everything he had would he be able to fight for victory.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son came to a conclusion as to why Lin Ming put away the Black Dragon Spear. He laughed and said, “I understand now. It’s true that you have a peak True Divinity spirit treasure, but you simply aren’t able to use it! Even for the heavy sword in my hands, I was only able to move less than a tenth of its power after breaking through to the fifth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art. And, this edgeless heavy sword is amongst the worst of True Divinity spirit treasures, whereas your Black Dragon Spear is a peak True Divinity spirit treasure. It’s unbelievable how much strength it must take to wield, so how could the likes of you possibly use it??”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s words were like a bucket of cold water that was poured over Empyrean Vast Universe’s entire body, making him feel chilled to the bone!

All of the human Empyreans present felt their hearts drop. They had been hoping for the Black Dragon Spear to show some miraculous effect in battle, but it seemed that this spear could not be used because Lin Ming wasn’t able to control it!

Then what was the point of fighting!?

Did Lin Ming plan on using the Phoenix Blood Spear to contend with the Good Fortune Saint Son’s True Divinity spirit treasure? Wasn’t this just a hopeless struggle?

The Good Fortune Saint Son became even more arrogant, more brazen. “I was also afraid of that spear because I thought it might contain the battle spirit of some True Divinity, but now it seems that you cannot even use it. Just how do you plan on fighting with me? Just sit down and die!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke his body shot forwards. The astral essence around him shot out like endless golden divine swords, making him seem like a scorching blood sun, making it impossible for others to look at him.

His sword cut down. As his long hair scattered, a wild and savage light burst out from his eyes.

From the heavy sword, a several hundred thousand foot long black light split apart the blue skies. The towering mountains and massive trees were swept up by this sword light. For a time, stones crashed to the ground and pieces of shattered wood swirled in the air.

This sword light left all the young elites holding their breath. Even though they were dozens of miles away, they felt their mortal bodies nearly be crushed by the terrifying momentum alone.

It was hard to imagine that this was a battle between juniors. Even those lords who had ruled for several hundred thousands of years were humbled in the face of such power!

Facing this sword, Lin Ming’s complexion was earnest and dignified. In a situation where he couldn’t use the Black Dragon Spear, his weapon became his weak point. It would be hard to directly confront this attack!

He drew back and opened the Heretical God Force. The power of thunder and fire erupted, wrapping around his body. A boundless and ancient strength rose up, completely surrounding Lin Ming!

This was Lin Ming’s grandmist force field, an offensive and defensive ability.

Ca!

As the black sword light broke into the barrier of the grandmist force field it was rapidly weakened by the grandmist space. Then, Lin Ming thrust out the Phoenix Blood Spear again and again. With the support of his immense bodily strength, the weakened sword light was pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear.

A crazy and furious energy erupted outwards. Lin Ming was forced back 100 miles and wherever he went, mountains and rivers would disintegrate and the earth would be hollowed out. It was unknown how many towering ancient trees were twisted to pieces by the energy and evaporated into ash!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s black light seemed to contain a dark demonic strength to it. Any object that was swept within would be completely annihilated, leaving almost nothing behind. As the young elites saw the millions upon millions of ancient trees be destroyed in the maelstrom, all of them felt streams of cold sweat dripping down their back.

If they were sucked into that black sword light, even just the tiniest bit, perhaps they would turn to nothing but ashes.

At this time, there was a loud explosive sound as the black sword light completely dissipated.

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear, standing proud and tall in the wild fluctuations of energy.

“He withstood it, he withstood the Good Fortune Saint Son’s first sword strike. However, that wasn’t a true frontal confrontation but rather avoiding the sharpness and then using his own force field to diminish the sword light. As for what Lin Ming finished off with his weapon, that was in truth just a tiny part of it.”

An Empyrean commented. In just one move, the battlefield that Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son had been fighting on was razed. Where Lin Ming had withdrawn by a hundred miles, a massive chasm formed with everything within it annihilated.

This was the horrifying scar that the Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword light left upon the land.

All of the human Empyreans present were nervous. Although Lin Ming didn’t suffer a loss in that strike, he wasn’t able to directly confront the Good Fortune Saint Son. This made all the human Empyreans feel doubt in their hearts.

“Hey, all you can do is run away?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son held his black heavy sword in his hand, slowly flying in the air like a peerless war god. The bright light of the sun shined in his hair, casting a blinding golden light.

“You cannot withstand my attack directly… so you want to use skirmish tactics to fight me. If you don’t want to face me then should I chase you around like a mouse everywhere? Since I use a True Divinity spirit treasure I consume strength faster than you, and no matter how much strength I have I will suffer a loss. So, you want to use that tactic to slowly reduce my strength? A well thought out plan, but what a pity it is nothing but a dream! This time I’ll make sure there’s nowhere you can run!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, wild astral winds rose up all around him. These strong astral winds blew into the void, constraining the power of space!

With a light crackling sound, the space surrounding Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son was locked up like a cage.

“Let’s see how you’ll run away this time!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son maliciously grinned, rushing forwards. And as he did, the space cage also tightened!

With Lin Ming’s strength he could naturally break through this space cage and escape, but in the brief moment it took him to do so he would be overtaken by the Good Fortune Saint Son.

“Die! I will split you and your spear in half together!”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son hurtled forwards, his black sword slashed through space!

Chapter 1769 – Good Fortune Divine Art

Sword potential soared through the heavens as dark winds swallowed the world. The boundless black sword light seemed as if it would destroy the very foundation of this independent space, severing the pillars of the world!

Facing this titanic sword strike, everyone felt as if the apocalypse had come and the world would collapse and be annihilated.

Lin Ming grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear. The 10 foot long spear shaft gently shivered in this catastrophic sword light!

The Phoenix Blood Spear was only a spirit artifact. For it to face a True Divinity spirit treasure, even one that could display less than a tenth of its true power, was far too difficult.

Everyone looked at Lin Ming and held their breath. Without the Black Dragon Spear, how would he block the Good Fortune Saint Son?

But if he couldn’t use the Black Dragon Spear as he pleased, then facing this terrifying sword light that filled the heavens and earth, the Phoenix Blood Spear might be cut in half!

Wu – wu – wu – !

The Phoenix Blood Spear violently trembled, emitting keening cries as it was unable to withstand the burden!

Lin Ming’s complexion changed. His greatest weakness right now was his weapon, and at the start he really was planning on using guerilla tactics to slowly whittle down the Good Fortune Saint Son’s strength.

However, the Good Fortune Saint Son didn’t give him this chance. This move not only blocked out space, but it also forced him to directly meet his enemy!

Up until now, the Good Fortune Saint Son was the strongest opponent Lin Ming had ever faced!

Hum –

The vibrations traversing the Phoenix Blood Spear became increasingly intense. Seeing it reach its limits, Lin Ming turned his right hand and the Phoenix Blood Spear disappeared into his spatial ring. In the next moment, another spear appeared in Lin Ming’s hand. This spear was gold all over and blazed with a brilliant golden light!

This spear was named the Purple Gold Spear and was the Empyrean spirit treasure spear Duke Fullmoon used a sky high price of 2 billion contribution points to win at the Divine Rune City Auction. At that time, it had been Lin Ming’s intention to mess with Duke Fullmoon and cause him to lose more wealth.

Afterwards, Duke Fullmoon had been killed by Lin Ming and this spear finally fell into Lin Ming’s hands.

In terms of quality, this Purple Gold Spear was far inferior to the Good Fortune Saint Son’s black divine sword. However, it was far harder than the Phoenix Blood Spear. At the very least it wouldn’t break in half within the turbulent sword light.

Ca!

The Purple Gold Spear violently collided with the black sword light. Massive chunks of golden light were swallowed up by the black sword light.

Lin Ming was forced back again and again. As for the Good Fortune Saint Son, he pushed forwards with unstoppable force, his every sword strike aiming for Lin Ming’s neck.

Pa!

Lin Ming struck the barriers of the space cage!

The Good Fortune Saint Son hurtled forwards. The astral essence around his body blazed like a scorching sun. With his black hair wildly flying about, he was like a peerless war god.

His arms were as sharp as swords and energy erupted from his body like waves in a stormy sea. His blood vitality billowed upwards, shooting straight into the starry skies!

“He’s been suppressed!”

Seeing this scene, the human Empyreans nearly felt their hearts leap out of their chests. The Good Fortune Saint Son was just far too strong and the blood vitality and physical strength he possessed was nearly that of a grown God Beast. It was simply impossible to match him!

On the other hand, although Lin Ming had taken out an Empyrean spirit treasure, the grade of this spear wasn’t even too high amongst Empyrean spirit treasures. It was still far too difficult for him to use this spear to block the Good Fortune Saint Son.

Now, Lin Ming had been forced back to the edges of the space barrier. He could only forcefully withstand the Good Fortune Saint Son’s strike!

“Even if you could use a True Divinity spirit treasure you would be far from my match, much less the current you that cannot use a True Divinity spirit treasure. Now, watch as I take your head!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son cruelly chuckled. He could finally strike Lin Ming with everything he had. After this strike, all of Lin Ming’s meridians would be torn to pieces and his organs would be reduced to a puddle of goo!

Facing the Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword, Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. At this time, a blue divine light shot out from deep within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, pouring into the shaft of the Purple Gold Spear.

This was Lin Ming’s large success blue soul battle spirit!

By fusing his weapon with his battle spirit, he could just manage to bridge the difference in weapon grades!

In that instant, Lin Ming opened the Heretical God Force to the limit. Behind him, the phantom of an ancient and massive tree appeared. The bough towered into the skies, blocking out the clouds and shrouding the sun.

Even when that annihilating black light shined upon the crown of this ancient tree, it found it difficult to penetrate through.

All of the energy condensed, forming a giant vortex in front of Lin Ming. Lin Ming thrust out his spear, sweeping through the void.

Eternal Darkness!

Bang!

A terrifying eruption exploded between Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son. A tide of energy cracked open a massive fissure in the ground, and even the sea that was hundreds of miles away began to violently rage and storm as tsunamis started to form.

Lin Ming grasped the Purple Gold Spear, solidly clashing with the Good Fortune Saint Son!

Spear to sword, it was a simple but brutal collision!

Lin Ming’s muscles began to bulge. His meridians and blood vessels expanded, and with a loud cracking sound, the space barrier behind him collapsed from the pressure!

“What?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son never thought that Lin Ming would manage to block his direct strike.

Although the Good Fortune Saint Son hadn’t used his complete strength nor had he used the Good Fortune Divine Art, in his opinion, the strength he used now should still easily be able to defeat Lin Ming.

Especially since Lin Ming’s weapon was far inferior to his own.

“The Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword light was terrifying but it was still blocked by Lin Ming. And Lin Ming has only a half-step Holy Lord cultivation…”

A hundred miles away where members of the monster race had gathered, the young elites were all quietly watching this battle. Although they had heard that Lin Ming possessed a talent that defied the will of the heavens, today was the first time they witnessed it with their own eyes.

“Amongst the juniors, no one can compare to Lin Ming’s heroic daring. If the young elites of my race were compared to him, it would be no different than fireflies to a bonfire. It's no wonder he had the courage to challenge the Good Fortune Saint Son.”

To fight the middle Holy Lord Good Fortune Saint Son with a mere half-step Holy Lord cultivation, and also with a weaker weapon, everyone thought that Lin Ming would be quickly defeated. But in two continuous moves, Lin Ming still hadn’t fallen.

Just this alone was more than enough to be proud of!

“Your Highness Wumo, what are you doing? You must hurry and defeat this Lin Ming. In this battle you have the advantage of cultivation so you must thoroughly obtain victory. You must not only defeat him but also rout the confidence of the humans, otherwise it is the same as you having lost! Do you not see the expressions that these human Empyreans are making? Destroy their hope, make it so that they lose all courage to resist our people!”

At this time, a sound transmission from a saint Empyrean echoed in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s ears.

The Good Fortune Saint Son took a deep breath. As the dignified Saint Son of the entre saint race and also with a middle Holy Lord cultivation, if he couldn’t defeat a mere Lin Ming who wasn’t even a Holy Lord yet and also drag out the battle for a long time, that simply couldn’t be justified.

At this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son had fallen completely silent.

He turned his burning eyes towards Lin Ming. “I will acknowledge that I have underestimated you. Your strength has surpassed my imagination, but even so, that will not change the outcome. You will still be miserably beaten by me.”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, the astral essence surrounding him turned pure gold, as if there was a golden sun burning within his body.

As the color of the Good Fortune Saint Son’s astral essence changed, his aura also experienced an earth-shaking transformation.

“This is…”

Many of the human masters present had keen senses. They realized that the Good Fortune Saint Son was undergoing some type of transformation at this moment, and his strength was rapidly ascending.

“This is the Good Fortune Divine Art! Several years ago when the Good Fortune Saint Son defeated a human Great World King, he used this golden astral essence!”

Amongst the human Empyreans, there were some that had witnessed the battle between the Good Fortune Saint Son and the human Great World King. Through that battle, they had gained a profound impression of the Good Fortune Divine Art.

The ordinary Good Fortune Saint Son and the Good Fortune Saint Son who used the Good Fortune Divine Art were two completely different concepts. Moreover, the current Good Fortune Saint Son had even broken into the fifth level of the Good Fortune Divine Art!

“Lin Ming, be careful of him! This Good Fortune Divine Art is an upper or even peak True Divinity cultivation method!”

Empyrean Vast Universe’s sound transmission echoed in Lin Ming’s ears.

Because his experience was limited, he couldn’t clearly distinguish what grade of cultivation method this Good Fortune Divine Art was.

With Empyrean Vase Universe’s words, Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat. A superior or even peak True Divinity cultivation method!

Lin Ming didn’t know what level True Divinity the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was, but what was without doubt was that through all the years of the saints, they should have obtained many rare and precious inheritances from the Primeval Realm Ruins.

Moreover, the saints possessed an unfathomably deep background. Their martial arts civilization and inheritances had never been cut off like humanity’s had, thus humans were incompare with them.

In this sort of situation, even if the Good Fortune Saint Son wasn’t a superior True Divinity, it wouldn’t be a surprise if he possessed a superior or peak True Divinity cultivation method.

If so, then Empyrean Divine Seal’s Divine Seal Art would most likely be inferior to the Good Fortune Saint Son’s Good Fortune Divine Art!

As Lin Ming thought of this, his complexion became increasingly grim.

And at this time, all of the strength of the world seemed to be summoned by an invisible call. All of it started gathering towards the Good Fortune Saint Son.

This strength consisted of not just heaven and earth origin energy, but all the strengths of the world.

Light, heat, microscopic ions in the air, the power of life, the power of the rocks, the power of streams, all of it began to gather towards the Good Fortune Saint Son!

With his own eyes, Lin Ming could see changes occurring hundreds of miles away.

Grass and plants began to wither and fall. Those towering old trees that reached the skies rapidly atrophied, becoming nothing but dead wood.

The rivers running through the forests evaporated, revealed dried up riverbeds.

This sort of feeling was as if the entire river had been sucked dry of its essence energy and vitality, and had undergone something similar to death. And all of the dissipated essence energy and vitality was completely absorbed by the Good Fortune Saint Son.

As the forest was completely destroyed, birds began to scatter. The land began to shake as all the creatures were filled with a manic fear. Beasts fled from the forest, as if they had encountered the most terrifying existence.

They crazily struggled in the withering forests, but just a moment later, all of these creatures emitted agonizing screams and their bodies burst open and they turned into masses of blood fog.

All of this blood fog also began gathering towards the Good Fortune Saint Son!

It was like the Good Fortune Saint Son was wresting away all the strength of the world, using it to strengthen himself!

This strength could no longer be called heaven and earth origin energy, but the power of good fortune.

The Good Fortune Divine Art was a technique that seized the good fortune of the world!

The so-called good fortune was that of nature. In a universe, besides the mortals that lived there, it was the sum of everything!

When a person seized the power of good fortune then the world would lose its spiritual energy and vitality, slowly moving it towards entropy, towards death and decay.

This was a truly cruel and overbearingly tyrannical cultivation method!

If a True Divinity were to use this ability, they could suck dry a great world!

Chapter 1772 – The Might of the Spirit Bead

Although Lin Ming had consumed a great deal of energy, the Good Fortune Saint Son was the same!

In every collision, although Lin Ming’s arms would be wetted with fresh blood and his meridians would break, he relied on his terrifying recovery ability to slowly restore the damage to his meridians.

This allowed Lin Ming to never be defeated. His tenacity exceeded the expectations of all present.

Woosh!

A heaven-shaking, earth-shattering sword strike cut through the endless sandstorm. This sword strike seemed to sunder the pillars that supported the world, and even the heavens seemed as if they would fall down!

The entire island was severed by this sword strike. An endless abyss formed, continuing for over 10,000 miles and stretching right into the sea!

The sea within the world of the Black Pagoda was countless hundreds of thousands of feet deep. Underneath the terrifying pressure, the wild sea tides gushed in, filling up the abyss.

Large tracts of land collapsed, turning into endless grains of sand that fell into the sea!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword strike had split apart all land for thousands of miles, the same as splitting a small planet in half!

The sandstorm began to calm down. But, the atmosphere entered into a state of unprecedented calm.

The Good Fortune Saint Son was flushed red and his breathing was rapid.

As for Lin Ming, even though his breath was gathered and steady, his entire body was still stained wet with blood.

The meridians in his arms were broken in innumerable places!

The golden spear in his hands was also covered with numerous dense sword marks!

These sword marks were shallow but it couldn’t be forgotten that this golden spear itself was an Empyrean spirit treasure and was a weapon refined by an ancient Empyrean. Even so, it had been scarred with so many sword marks. From this one could see just how strong the Good Fortune Saint Son’s attacks had been!

Although it seemed that the Good Fortune Saint Son had the upper hand, some people watching actually discovered that this wasn’t as true as they thought.

“The strength of Lin Ming’s mortal body isn’t much worse than the Good Fortune Saint Son’s…”

A human Empyrean said with shock.

Originally, people thought that because Lin Ming was a human martial artist and his cultivation was low, he wouldn’t be able to last long against the continued onslaught of the Good Fortune Saint Son. But, the truth was that by relying on the horrifying toughness of his body, he had persisted the entire time!

In terms of enduring the continued consumption of strength, Lin Ming had taken the upper hand!

The Good Fortune Saint Son wielding a True Divinity spirit treasure from the start until now had caused him to expend a tremendous amount of strength. As for Lin Ming, he used an Empyrean spirit treasure and he focused on defending. Even if he had to take a small wound he would do so in order to conserve energy.

Over the course of this battle, Lin Ming would spend energy at a far slower pace than the Good Fortune Saint Son did!

Moreover, even though Lin Ming had opened the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and affected his life source, the human Empyreans discovered that although Lin Ming was slowly burning his life source, it didn’t diminish at all!

“It is the Gate of Life…”

Empyrean Divine Dream eerily said. Although humanity had lost records of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, they had still maintained inheritances about the Eight Inner Hidden Gates.

The Gate of Life was an extremely important gate within the Eight Inner Hidden Gates. It brought with it the ability to regenerate one’s life source and blood essence to a certain degree and built a solid foundation for Lin Ming to desperately release the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace.

“The tide of battle is slowly changing. If they continue to fight like this, Lin Ming will be on the winning side!”

Some human Empyreans came to this nearly unbelievable conclusion. This was a completely unexpected result.

The decisive battle between the Good Fortune Saint Son and Lin Ming was like a long distance competition held in the mortal world. Lin Ming followed behind the Good Fortune Saint Son, allowing him to be in the lead first.

The Good Fortune Saint Son was strong and Lin Ming was also strong. However, he only fell behind the Good Fortune Saint Son by a little.

But during this time, Lin Ming had been secretly conserving his strength, planning to surpass the Good Fortune Saint Son in the final moment!

To force the Good Fortune Saint Son into this sort of situation had surpassed the imaginations of all present.

“Your Highness Wumo, stop hesitating!”

At this time, the angry sound transmission of a saint Empyrean echoed in the Good Fortune Saint Son’s ears.

With the fight having continued until now, it had been more than enough for Lin Ming to greatly show off his glory. Even though their saint race’s Saint Son had a far higher cultivation than this human youth, he still hadn’t been able to end the battle. This meant that their saint race’s Saint Son was inferior to the young elites of humanity!

The Good Fortune Saint Son clenched his teeth. Suddenly, his aura completely condensed within his body. He looked at Lin Ming, his eyes blazing.

“You have done well! Your tactics, strength, everything you have has surpassed my imagination! I cannot help but acknowledge that you are the most terrifying opponent I have faced in my life. But even so, you will lose all the same!

“Originally, I didn’t want to use this move…”

As the Good Fortune Saint Son spoke, a dazzling light burst out from his chest. In the next moment, a startling scene occurred.

The Good Fortune Saint Son thrust his hand into his chest and pulled out a bloody bead!

This bead was dark and dense, emitting a thick black light. For a time, the skies were covered in chaos. All the martial artists present felt as if their hearts would be swallowed up by this chaos!

“Grandmist Spirit Bead!”

Some martial artists cried out in panic. Even Empyreans also felt fear and apprehension upon facing this Grandmist Spirit Bead!

The Good Fortune Saint Son had finally used the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

The Good Fortune Saint Son had his pride. As the dignified Saint Son and also possessing a middle Holy Lord realm cultivation, he should have been able to rely on his own strength to completely roll over this human martial artist that was much younger than he was.

However, he had failed again and again. The Good Fortune Saint Son had then given up on rolling over Lin Ming and decided to defeat him in a high intensity melee.

But, that plan also failed.

With that, the Good Fortune Saint Son had no choice but to bring out the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

After bringing out the Grandmist Spirit Bead, the Good Fortune Saint Son felt wretched in his heart. As the Saint Son, he couldn’t defeat this human martial artist that had a lower cultivation, and even had to rely on the strength of the Grandmist Spirit Bead to obtain victory in the end. This was completely unreasonable!

Even if he won, it would still be a great loss of face!

However, winning was always better than losing.

“Lin Ming…” On the side of Divine Dream Heavenly Palace, Mo Eversnow and Mo Brightmoon both tensed up. The Good Fortune Saint Son was finally willing to go all-out. Would Lin Ming be able to withstand the attack of the Grandmist Spirit Bead?

Xiao Moxian’s forehead dripped with sweat. Lin Ming had already been injured many times, and although the wounds weren’t heavy, they had accumulated over time. Lin Ming may have possessed a formidable body, but it still wouldn’t be easy for him.

And now, the Good Fortune Saint Son had summoned the Grandmist Spirit Bead. The battle was reaching its climax!

Lin Ming quietly stared at the spinning black bead. He took a deep breath.

It had finally appeared!

He had been continually keeping his final cards in hand all in order to contend with the Good Fortune Saint Son’s Grandmist Spirit Bead. If he were to use all his master moves before the Good Fortune Saint Son took out the Grandmist Spirit Bead then he would have exhausted all his strength. Then, when the Good Fortune Saint Son did summon the Grandmist Spirit Bead, he could only sit and die!

The reason Lin Ming had such concerns was that no matter what happened, he didn’t dare to use the Magic Cube to struggle with the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

The reason that the Good Fortune Saint Son could freely and openly use the Grandmist Spirit Bead was because he had the entire saint race supporting him from behind.

But, if Lin Ming were to use the Magic Cube, the consequences would be disastrous.

Lin Ming possessed the Magic Cube. This was a secret that no one knew besides him, Xiao Moxian, and Mo Eversnow knew. It was a world creation class divine artifact. It was enough to arouse the greed of the saint race’s True Divinities, and especially the soul race’s True Divinities!

Just the Black Dragon Spear alone was not enough for a True Divinity level powerhouse to desperately struggle for it.

But, the appearance of the Magic Cube might even force the spiritas and saints to enter into a temporary ceasefire. Then they could join forces to attack humanity and steal away the Magic Cube!

If so, the result would be him and humanity perishing together.

Thus, even if Lin Ming lost to the Good Fortune Saint Son in this battle, he still couldn’t bring out the Magic Cube.

If Lin Ming couldn’t use the Magic Cube, he would have to retain all his strongest cards in order to battle the Good Fortune Saint Son’s Grandmist Spirit Bead!

“So that is the Grandmist Spirit Bead! The Good Fortune Saint Son has finally laid down his arrogant heart. Lin Ming, he… is in danger…”

Most of the martial artists present had never seen the Grandmist Spirit Bead before. This was because nearly all who saw the Grandmist Spirit Bead with their own eyes had died!

Still, the name of this divine tool struck like a peal of thunder in their ears!

Most people didn’t know of the existence of the Magic Cube or the Purple Card. To them, this Grandmist Spirit Bead was the number one divine tool to ever exist!

“What a terrifying aura. Even though I’m so far away and I’m not being targeted by the Grandmist Spirit Bead, I still feel my blood vitality tumbling in me, as if it’s about to be sucked away by that bead!”

A human master said, panic-stricken. He had a half-step World King cultivation.

Even a half-step World King was still affected by the aura of the Grandmist Spirit Bead, feeling as if the flow of blood in their body would reverse.

Then, without a doubt, if the Good Fortune Saint Son were to attack this half-step World King with the Grandmist Spirit Bead, it would only take an instant for his body to collapse, turning into endless flesh and blood essence that was absorbed by the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

Not to mention one half-step World King, even if many half-step World Kings and even ordinary World Kings were gathered together, they would still be instantly slain by the Good Fortune Saint Son!

Such a result left one drowning in despair!

This was the might of a divine tool!

Chapter 1774 – Peak Showdown

After galvanizing the Asura blood within him, it wasn’t just Lin Ming’s strength that had increased, but there was also a world-shaking change in his aura.

At the start, Lin Ming’s aura was incomparably swift and relentless, carrying with it an unstoppably firm will. It seemed as if no matter what stood in front of him he could still pierce through it.

But after utilizing the Asura blood, Lin Ming’s aura had become as fathomless as the bloody seas of hell, carrying with it a terrifying killing intent!

Even for the many masters present, even Great World Kings, when they faced Lin Ming they felt their minds and bodies be invaded by that vast killing intent, nearly causing them to suffocate as they gasped for breath.

“Lin Ming… still had such a hidden card? From the start he had kept back this last resort in order to deal with the Good Fortune Saint Son’s Grandmist Spirit Bead!”

Many human Empyreans suddenly realized.

The reason Lin Ming had been suppressed by the Good Fortune Saint Son since the start was not because he was weak, but because he was saving his strength and energy.

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s Grandmist Spirit Bead had long since been factored into his plan!

When he challenged the Good Fortune Saint Son at the Monster Emperor’s longevity feast, this wasn’t an impulsive decision he had made on the spot. Rather, he had come up with a thorough strategy and had been gathering his momentum all this time for this challenge!

This was the only reason he dared to recklessly bet everything he had!

After understanding this, everyone felt frightened and awed. This young man Lin Ming was just completely incomprehensible. Just when they thought they understood everything about him, they realized that what they knew was only the tip of the iceberg.

After not seeing him for many years, he left everyone’s line of sight and when he returned he soared into the heavens once more!

“What a terrifying youth… if he continues to grow, it’s certain he will become a True Divinity…”

The Monster Emperor said with a heavy sigh as he placed a hand on Empyrean Demondawn’s shoulder.

Lin Ming had even been able to shatter the shackles of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace with his own strength. To create another miracle and break through the realm of True Divinity, that shouldn’t be difficult for Lin Ming at all.

Empyrean Demondawn remained silent. He couldn’t help but admit that Lin Ming was the most terrifying youth he had ever seen in his life. Even the Good Fortune Saint Son was far inferior to him!

At just 100 years old, he had begun to show his towering might and potential. If it weren’t for the great calamity of humanity, he would absolutely become a character like Empyrean Divine Seal from 3.6 billion years ago, perhaps even surpassing him!

Thinking of this, Empyrean Demondawn’s heart trembled.

Empyrean Divine Seal… didn’t he also appear during a great calamity?

Perhaps… to Lin Ming, this great calamity wasn’t a disaster, but might actually be… a lucky chance!

As long as he could withstand the great calamity then Lin Ming would obtain an unbelievable advantage. He would be a phoenix reborn through nirvana, soaring to unimaginable heights!

“Perhaps Xian’er should really be with him…”

Empyrean Demondawn quietly thought to himself.

He thought… that perhaps… he had made the wrong choice…

But no matter what, he couldn’t rely on his own subjective judgment to decide these matters and gamble the future of his people.

Even if Lin Ming could survive the great calamity and become a True Divinity, that didn’t mean that his demon race would be equally able to survive the great calamity with Lin Ming. Oftentimes, when a peerless genius arose, the influences that they grew up with would experience unprecedented catastrophes. This was because the inside background of these influences was far too lacking and they couldn’t withstand the destiny that these unrivalled geniuses brought with them. In the end, all that awaited them was doom and destruction.

Empyrean Demondawn didn’t believe that the monster and demon races possessed such a background.

At this time, in the skies, the Good Fortune Saint Son was beginning his attack.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead hung high above his head. Countless ribbons of black light flowed out, sealing the surrounding space.

“Lin Ming!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes were cruel and vicious. Facing Lin Ming, he already felt a deep sense of frustration!

Originally, this should have been a battle that he easily won no matter what. However, with things having come this far, he had even taken out the Grandmist Spirit Bead but still wasn’t able to suppress Lin Ming. This caused the Good Fortune Saint Son to be enraged.

“I will kill you!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son clenched his jaws. Towards this person known as Lin Ming who completely suppressed him in terms of talent, the Good Fortune Saint Son desperately wanted to destroy him!

Woosh woosh woosh –

More and more black silk ribbons appeared. This was the Grandmist Spirit Bead’s force field. After being enveloped in this force field, Lin Ming felt the blood vitality of his body gushing out and even the power of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace was greatly limited.

Grandmist Spirit Bead… it was truly worthy of being regarded as the highest rank divine tools in existence. Even Lin Ming, who had an extremely solid foundation of blood energy, still found this enormous pressure difficult to withstand.

Then, at this time, the Good Fortune Saint Son moved!

His body hurtled forwards. The golden power of good fortune erupted from his body like a volcano, dyeing the endless skies a glorious morning gold!

Scorching hot power swept through the blue skies. It was like a golden sun had shattered in the skies, turning into endless rays of golden light!

Although this was the Good Fortune Divine Art, after using the Sovereign Blood body metamorphosis, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s utilization of the Good Fortune Divine Art was completely incomparable to before!

Seeing this scene, Lin Ming also no longer held back.

He opened the Heretical God Force to the limit. Behind him, the massive phantom of the Heretical God Tree appeared once more. Its vast power poured itself into the Black Dragon Spear.

This Black Dragon Spear was a True Divinity spirit treasure. No matter how much power Lin Ming poured into it, it would welcome all without reserve!

Perhaps even stimulating 10% of the Black Dragon Spear’s strength would be enough to suck Lin Ming dry of energy!

At the fifth level of the final trial, Lin Ming had only used one move with the Black Dragon Spear to crush the Undying Polar Ice.

For that one move, the strength Lin Ming poured into the Black Dragon Spear was nearly equal to half his total energy.

“First spear!”

Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear. Dozens of billions of jins of strength erupted from within him. Strength rose from his waist. Blood vessels bulged on his arms. With hands as heavy as a mountain, he thrust the spear straight out!

Behind Lin Ming, the giant Asura phantom fused into his body. Asura Law runes wildly danced in the air. In order to conserve as much strength as possible, Lin Ming used the power of the Asura Laws to stimulate movement of the Black Dragon Spear.

Rah - !

The Black Dragon Spear’s clarion cry rang out, like a dragon roaring into the deep blue skies!

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s black sword collided with Lin Ming’s spear!

An unimaginably violent force erupted, tearing the surrounding space to shreds!

The mortal bodies of the two opponents were as solid as divine iron. In such a violent collision, anything that wasn’t at least an Empyrean spirit treasure would be turned into ash. As for the energy waves, they blasted out onto the bodies of the two with metallic ringing sounds, forcefully withstood. Even the space storms that swept out were stiffly shouldered all the same.

Kacha!

With a loud explosion, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s black sword light was stiffly torn apart by Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear!

The Black Dragon Spear moved forwards with unstoppable force, pushing straight through!

Lin Ming’s right arm sank and dozens of spear lights shot out from the Black Dragon Spear. They were like massive mountains, locking down the heavens!

The Good Fortune Saint Son had immediately fallen into an encirclement of Lin Ming’s spear lights!

“Lin Ming has the upper hand!”

Some human Empyreans cried out in shock. They never imagined that Lin Ming’s strike would actually break through the Good Fortune Saint Son’s sword light, and even soon hit his body!

“Scales of the Sovereign Blood!”

Seeing Lin Ming’s spear thrust towards him, the Good Fortune Saint Son bellowed out loud. The golden scales covering his body began to emit a blinding radiance. He had actually chosen to forcefully withstand Lin Ming’s spear strike!

Although 80-90% of Lin Ming’s attack power had been blocked by the black sword light, the remaining 10-20% was still something that would not be easy to resist!

If the Good Fortune Saint Son chose to withstand this strike with his body he would absolutely be injured!

In that moment, Lin Ming’s strength gushed out. The True Dragon blood within him began to boil over! The two Dao Palaces within him erupted with an incredible strength again and again!

As he struck out with the Black Dragon Spear, he vigorously pulled back his spear and thrust out nine times, using the skill of the Hundred Layered Waves to superimpose the strength of these nine spear strikes together!

These nine spears strikes had no energy poured into them and were used with Lin Ming’s bodily strength alone. This was because Lin Ming had just used his first move and it was impossible for him to summon the strength for the second move too quickly. Thus, he could only use his bodily strength to stiffly stab out his spear several more times to increase the might of the attack; this was already the limit of what he could do.

Kacha!

The Black Dragon Spear heavily smashed into the Good Fortune Saint Son’s chest.

The horrifying striking power of a peak True Divinity spirit treasure was hard to imagine! Even though Lin Ming’s spear strike had been weakened again and again, it still cracked apart the Good Fortune Saint Son’s protective astral essence and shattered his golden scales, causing him to vomit a massive amount of blood!

“The Good Fortune Saint Son has been injured!”

Whether it was the human guests or the martial artists from the monster and demon races, they all gasped in shock. Ever since the battle started, this was the first time that the Good Fortune Saint Son had been injured!

Moreover, this was not a minor wound, but a severe injury that caused the Good Fortune Saint Son to vomit blood. Lin Ming with his half-step Holy Lord cultivation had actually forced the Good Fortune Saint Son into such a situation. Moreover, the Good Fortune Saint Son had even used his Sovereign Blood body metamorphosis as well as having summoned the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

The body-metamorphosized Lin Ming was far too terrifying. He was like an Asura of hell. Gods who blocked his way would be cut down, buddhas who blocked his way would be slain!

Chapter 1775 – Another Miraculous Move

Pa!

The bloodstained Good Fortune Saint Son suddenly grabbed onto Lin Ming’s spear shaft. After activating his supreme Sovereign Blood body metamorphosis and also using the Scales of the Sovereign Blood, his defensive ability had reached a terrifying degree. Even though he forcefully withstood Lin Ming’s attack and had been injured to the point of spitting out blood, the spear hadn’t pierced through his body.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. The Black Dragon Spear was like a living True Dragon in his hands, constantly breaking into the Good Fortune Saint Son’s protective astral essence!

With both sides deadlocked, the Good Fortune Saint Son lifted the black heavy sword with one hand and fiendishly grinned.

“Lin Ming, you’re dead!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s voice echoed in Lin Ming’s ears. Lin Ming was suddenly startled. From behind, he could feel a thick killing intent!

“Lin Ming, be careful!” Xiao Moxian cried out in alarm.

The many human Empyreans were also tense. At that time, a sharp black light was shooting straight towards Lin Ming from behind. And the center of the black light was the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

If Lin Ming continued to thrust his spear he could undoubtedly heavily wound the Good Fortune Saint Son, but at the same time he would also be struck by the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

If Lin Ming was struck by the Grandmist Spirit Bead, the injuries it would cause to his body could be imagined!

“Take back the spear and defend!”

Empyrean Vast Universe’s sound transmission crackled like thunder in Lin Ming’s ears!

He originally thought that the Good Fortune Saint Son seemed strangely weak in his collision with Lin Ming just now, but now it seemed that the reason was because he had split off a portion of his strength to control the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

The Good Fortune Saint Son would attack Lin Ming from the front and then use the Grandmist Spirit Bead to sneak attack him from behind, placing him in a pincer attack!

In this situation, even if Lin Ming took back his spear to defend, he had just attacked and his true essence was in a mess. He would still suffer heavy losses to the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

How the fight progressed after that could be imagined!

But if Lin Ming didn’t take back his spear to defend, the situation would be even worse. Only the heavens would know what consequences Lin Ming would suffer after being struck by the full strength attack of the Grandmist Spirit Bead. At worst, Lin Ming could even die here! Compared to death, simply losing to the Good Fortune Saint Son was much better.

This was the Good Fortune Saint Son’s sure-kill plan. With this attack, Lin Ming would likely lose. This was a truly vicious attack!

However, at this time Lin Ming seemed as if he simply didn’t hear Empyrean Vast Universe’s sound transmission. He continued to hold onto the Black Dragon Spear as before, thrusting it straight towards the Good Fortune Saint Son’s chest, utterly disregarding the Grandmist Spirit Bead that was hurtling towards him.

Within the brutal waves of energy, Lin Ming exuded a dense killing intent. The Asura phantom behind him clawed at the air like a demonic spirit trying to rip apart the skies!

“You… do you really want to die?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son was shocked. He never imagined that Lin Ming would be so ruthless and would continue attacking him even at the cost of being heavily wounded by the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

Seeing 90% of his own protective astral essence being broken by Lin Ming, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes flashed with a vicious light. He fiercely said, “Good, then if you want to die let me help you. Even if I have to withstand this attack the most I will suffer is a severe wound!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son grit his teeth, revolving the little amount of strength he had left to the limit!

“The one dying is you!” Lin Ming fiercely grinned.

Puff!

The Good Fortune Saint Son spat out a mouthful of blood as the Black Dragon Spear thrust through his chest. Then, he grabbed onto the Black Dragon Spear’s shaft, looking at Lin Ming like he was looking at someone already dead.

After using all his energy in this strike, Lin Ming absolutely wouldn’t be able to dodge the attack from the Grandmist Spirit Bead. And, his injuries would be far more severe!

It was even possible that the Grandmist Spirit Bead’s strike would greatly damage Lin Ming’s blood vitality and leave behind hidden wounds that hindered his future achievements. These thoughts made the Good Fortune Saint Son feel even better!

But as the black light of the Grandmist Spirit Bead was about to strike Lin Ming’s back, a figure rushed out from Lin Ming’s inner world!

This figure was similar to Lin Ming before he activated his body metamorphosis. The figure wore black clothes and its blood vitality soared into the heavens, billowing into the skies like a rocket!

“What? This is…”

In that instant, it seemed as if Lin Ming had split into two. Everyone’s eyes widened. Just what was happening?

Woosh!

As this black figure appeared, a black wheel appeared under it. This was Lin Ming’s Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. And in the hands of this black figure was the Purple Gold Spear that Lin Ming had been using before!

This black-clothed figure that suddenly appeared was Lin Ming’s avatar – the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone!

The Essence spirit Embryo Stone revolved its astral essence to its limits, combining it with the horrifying blood vitality that had been tempered within it for billions and billions of years. It grasped the Purple Gold Spear and shot towards the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

Kacha!

The Purple Gold Spear in the Essence Spirit Embryo’s hands smashed into the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

In that moment, the originally not too flexible Purple Gold Spear tightly curved, seeming as if it would break apart at any moment!

The arms of the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone exploded with blood shooting into the wind!

And once this blood shot out, it was all absorbed by the Grandmist Spirit Bead, making for an extremely ghostly and macabre sight.

For a time, energy erupted outwards. Behind Lin Ming, a violent detonation swept out, the raging strength like tides in a storm, flushing into Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son and causing them both to tumble away.

The Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was the essence energy avatar personally refined by the Asura Road Master!

Even if the Grandmist Spirit Bead was a peerless divine tool, the Good Fortune Saint Son could only bring out a limited amount of its strength. In the fierce collision, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone had only been struck to the point of losing blood.

And a part of the avatar’s essence energy had also been absorbed by the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

But this wasn’t a problem at all. The essence energy could be restored through the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel by sacrificing some of the souls within it.

Because the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone had moved to block over 99% of the Grandmist Spirit Bead’s attack power, Lin Ming hadn’t suffered from the shockwaves at all.

As the young elites witnessed this, all of them were dazed. They didn’t know just what words to say.

As for the Good Fortune Saint Son, he said with an incredulous voice, “How is this possible… how could you possibly have such a terrifying flesh and blood avatar!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son had clearly seen that the appearance of the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone was the exact same as Lin Ming’s. This was undoubtedly Lin Ming’s avatar!

But the avatar’s body contained a terrifying blood vitality, one that was even greater than the Good Fortune Saint Son’s by an unbelievably large margin. He simply couldn’t believe this was possible!

At this time, Lin Ming and the Good Fortune Saint Son had briefly exhausted themselves of energy. They lost their balance in the air and were sent flying away by the wild fluctuations of energy.

The Gold Fortune Saint Son tried to adjust his breathing and blood vitality, wanting to summon enough astral essence to attack Lin Ming once more.

Lin Ming simply sneered.

From his inner world, another figure shot out!

This figure wore purple clothes and a vast soul force gushed out from its body, as if it were a fathomless abyss of soul force. It formed a sharp contrast with the previously black-clothed Lin Ming!

“What!?”

The Good Fortune Saint Son’s eyes nearly popped out of his head.

All of the martial artists present cried out in shock, “There’s another one!?”

This purple-clothed figure was naturally the second avatar – the Soul Springs Divine Embryo!

This Soul Springs Divine Embryo stood atop a purple wheel – the Myriad Essence Reincarnation Wheel. It grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and hurtled straight towards the Good Fortune Saint Son!

In terms of defensive power, the Soul Springs Divine Embryo was far inferior to the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. But, its attacks were far more strange and cunning, nearly impossible to guard against!

The Good Fortune Saint Son could barely believe his own eyes. The Soul Springs Divine Embryo was aiming its spear at his chest, and the point where it aimed was where Lin Ming had wounded him before!

In Lin Ming’s battle against the Good Fortune Saint Son he used every method he could, taking advantage of all possibilities to add wounds upon wounds.

Seeing this spear point about to pierce him, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s face turned as pale as paper! Because he had exhausted his strength in the last attack he hadn’t been able to summon more astral essence. In other words, he couldn’t resist this attack!

Puff!

The Phoenix Blood Spear pierced into the Good Fortune Saint Son. The Good Fortune Saint Son’s chest collapsed inwards. However, his mortal body had been tempered innumerable times and was fused with almost endless essence, making it as hard as divine iron. Even though the Phoenix Blood Spear penetrated into his chest, it still wasn’t able to tear through his heart!

“That was close… but it seems this avatar isn’t too strong…”

The Good Fortune Saint Son immediately thought. But before he could rejoice, he felt an agonizing pain within his spiritual sea. The Phoenix Blood Spear contained a spiritual strike that was attacking him like a hidden viper!

The Soul Springs Divine Embryo’s strike had contained a soul attack!

“Ahhh!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son screamed out loud, his body shaking. The pain brought through a soul attack was several times that of a physical attack. The Good Fortune Saint Son grabbed his head, fiercely struggling with himself.

“Die!”

Lin Ming had recovered his strength again in the several breaths of time he had. He grasped the Black Dragon Spear and attacked the Good Fortune Saint Son once more!

When his main body used the Black Dragon Spear he could use three moves total – this was the second!

For a time, joyful dragon and phoenix phantoms appeared behind Lin Ming. In that moment, his aura climbed to new heights!

Chapter 1776 – Victory or Defeat

From within Lin Ming’s inner world, wild true essence and astral essence erupted. A dazzling brilliance covered the skies, as if a sun was exploding within him, causing everyone to close their eyes from the brightness.

Behind Lin Ming, nine massive stars appeared once more. Their vast starlight poured down like a waterfall, converging into Lin Ming’s body!

Paka paka!

Lin Ming’s joints released crackling explosive sounds. He bit down on his lip and spat out blood essence, brilliantly burning it!

By combusting his blood essence through the Gate of Life, Lin Ming’s strength rapidly climbed to the peak, soon approaching that of ten dragons!

The scattered wounds marring Lin Ming’s body also began to rapidly regenerate. In that moment, as he grasped the Black Dragon Spear, his long hair recklessly fluttering in the wind as he stood proud in the skies, he seemed full of an invincible might!

“This brat!” Empyrean Demondawn took a deep breath, a trace of fear and shock in his eyes. Lin Ming was just far too terrifying. In his battle with the Good Fortune Saint Son, he had experienced a brutal prolonged fight and had consumed a mind-boggling amount of energy, and his meridians and blood vessels had been torn in countless areas. Even so, in the final moments he was still able to erupt with such an overwhelming level of strength.

As for the Good Fortune Saint Son, he had been severely wounded by Lin Ming to the point of vomiting blood!

This was the saint race, a race renowned throughout the 33 Heavens for their body transformation technique. Out of all the races, they possessed the number one mortal bodily strength and endurance. By relying on their mortal bodies alone, they could struggle with True Dragons!

Yet at the end, Lin Ming’s endurance and physical strength actually surpassed that of the Saint Son.

How could Empyrean Demondawn not be amazed?

“Lin Ming!”

Facing this spear, the Good Fortune Saint Son gnashed his teeth.

His current situation was far worse than Lin Ming’s. His blood vitality was in a chaotic mess and his organs were damaged in many places. The astral essence around him had scattered and he could gather less than 50%.

All he could do now was rely on the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

The Good Fortune Saint Son roared out loud. He suddenly bit down on the tip of his tongue and burnt a wisp of his blood essence!

Seeing this, the entire audience of martial artists was left bewildered.

The Good Fortune Saint Son had been forced by Lin Ming to burn his blood essence!

Although the Good Fortune Saint Son’s supreme Sovereign Blood was incomparably powerful, that didn’t mean he had the ability to willfully burn it as he pleased. Once he burned a little, it meant he had that much less. And, the Good Fortune Saint Son’s bloodline was extremely special. Once he burned some of his blood essence it would be immensely problematic to make up for. This move clearly indicated that the Good Fortune Saint Son had gone all out.

Hu –

The Grandmist Spirit Bead fiercely spun, creating a dark red vortex. The Good Fortune Saint Son spat burning blood essence into the Grandmist Spirit Bead.

The Grandmist Spirit Bead then emitted an increasingly brilliant red light!

“I will swallow all of your flesh and blood essence energy!”

The Good Fortune Saint Son had bet everything on this. He poured the totality of his strength into this attack.

His remaining strength was clearly less than Lin Ming’s. He could only use the Grandmist Spirit Bead to make up for this deficiency.

The moment that the Grandmist Spirit Bead shot out, Lin Ming also attacked!

The Heretical God Force erupted. A tyrannical and savage power of thunder and fire turbulently poured into the Black Dragon Spear.

The spear thrust out. Like a mysterious vortex, all of the light in the skies was swallowed up by this spear, immediately causing the world to darken.

Everyone was shrouded in this darkness. Only the Black Dragon Spear in Lin Ming’s hands remained blindingly brilliant!

Hu – hu – hu – !

The maddening aura of the Asura Great Dao condensed. The surrounding space began to shatter like glass, large tracts of space collapsing in on itself.

Lin Ming’s spear strike already contained the charm of the Gate of Laws’ Black Asura’s final strike. This spear seemed as if it could pierce through the entire universe!

This was the power of the Asura Laws, as horrifying as the abyss of hell!

Lin Ming’s momentum was like a rainbow. A giant Asura phantom formed around him. With the support of this Asura phantom, Lin Ming struck out at the Good Fortune Saint Son!

And at the same time, two figures flew towards Lin Ming from two sides. Of these two figures, one wore purple clothes and one wore black clothes; they were Lin Ming’s two avatars. They each held onto their spear, sending out their all-out attacks, completely fusing together with Lin Ming’s strike.

This heaven-shaking spear light smashed into the Grandmist Spirit Bead!

Kacha!

An earth-shattering explosion burst out. The Grandmist Spirit Bead violently trembled. The surrounding space was like glass smashed with a hammer, all of it shattering to pieces!

Countless Asura Law runes flashed out from the destroyed space like stars.

“Retreat! Quickly retreat!”

Some martial artists cried out in alarm. In the face of such terrifying strength, even if they stood a hundred miles away they would still be swallowed up and annihilated!

But at this time, the human and monster races both had Empyreans take action. They set up shimmering light barriers that blocked the dreadful shockwaves of energy.

The energy crashed into the Empyreans’ light barriers. After causing them to fiercely shake, it returned like a lowering tide. The endless sand and sea water was swept into the air where it instantly disintegrated into the finest powder before scattering through the world.

For a time, it was like a massive meteor had crashed into the island. The entire island had been hollowed out and a crazy amount of water vapor soared upwards, rapidly condensing into dark clouds in the skies before falling back down like an endless rainstorm!

Endless sea water gushed in, filling up the titanic crater in the center of the island. Waves roared and ceaseless rain poured, making it seem like the end of the world.

“What happened?”

Many young elites looked at each other in dismay. They hadn’t been able to clearly see the results of the final strike.

Someone looked at the many surrounding Empyreans. All they saw was that there were several human Empyreans who were even shivering.

Among these people were Empyrean Vast Universe and Empyrean Traceless. The two of them had clenched their fists so hard that blue veins were visible and their knuckles had turned white. It was like space itself was breaking beneath their grasp!

After their cultivation reached the Empyrean realm, there was little that could cause them to lose their composure like this. The reason they had such an intense reaction, even shaking, was because their excitement had reached the limit. In their eyes there was nothing but absolute disbelief, interwoven with a zealous joy and trepidation!

Few understood the situation as well as they did. Humanity was lost in an eternal night, drowning in sorrow and misery without an end in sight. To them, this battle between the Good Fortune Saint Son and Lin Ming was of monumental importance!

This duel was enough to ignite humanity’s flames of hope!

“Could it be…”

Seeing the response of the human Empyreans, the hearts of the young elites present trembled. They turned their heads and looked towards the saint Empyrean.

Not too far away, the saint Empyrean floated high in the void. Even within the endless drops of falling sea water, not a single one was able to touch him. However, his complexion had become dark and gloomy enough to drip water!

The response of the saint Empyrean had confirmed their guesses.

“Lin Ming… won… he won!?”

As this thought flashed through all of the young human elites’ minds, the heavy rain finally finished falling. In the boundless mist, there was only a single proud figure remaining. This figure grasped the Black Dragon Spear, his long hair slicked back through the rain.

This person was Lin Ming!

And opposite Lin Ming, the Good Fortune Saint Son had disappeared in the endless mist, having completely vanished from sight.

As if… he had sunk into the sea…

Chapter 1782 – Lin Ming’s Plan

“Oh? See someone?”

Empyrean Divine Dream’s thoughts stirred. If Lin Ming wanted to see someone at this time then this person naturally wasn’t some common character. Moreover, Lin Ming clearly implied that this person could influence the situation between the saints and humans; this left Empyrean Divine Dream puzzled. Amongst the entirety of humanity, Empyrean Divine Dream couldn’t think of a single such person. “Is it someone you met in the Asura Road?”

Empyrean Divine Dream couldn’t help but think this. If Lin Ming had met some True Divinity level character in the Asura Road then this person might have the smallest chances of helping and indeed changing the fate of humanity. But, why would a True Divinity powerhouse easily involve themselves in the great calamity? In order to resist the entire saint race, a single True Divinity wasn’t enough, because the saints themselves likely possessed more than one True Divinity in their ranks.

As for what rank of True Divinity the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign was, that was impossible to guess.

Lin Ming said, “Indeed, this person is someone that junior encountered in the Asura Road. But, in order for this junior to find her, junior will need the help of Senior Divine Dream. Junior once heard that Senior Divine Dream ventured into the Soul World, grasping the principles there and dual cultivating essence and soul and finally establishing the Divine Dream Law, right?”

Empyrean Divine Dream looked at Lin Ming with surprise. “Are you saying you want to go to the Soul World?” She had originally thought that Lin Ming would return to the Asura Road.

Lin Ming nodded. Passing through the God Lamenting Wall to go to the Soul World was difficult. As for passing through the Asura Road, a martial artist had to use the Asura Command to do so, and the Asura Command only returned a martial artist to their original universe.

Lin Ming said, “Junior wishes to see a spiritas Empyrean. She is an acquaintance of mine…”

“Big Brother Lin, do you want to see Sheng Mei?” Xiao Moxian suddenly asked. If Lin Ming was looking for a spiritas elder, her first thought was naturally Sheng Mei.

At the very least, if they found Sheng Mei they would be able to clarify some matters. They would be able to find out why the saints were entering a truce with the spiritas. To humanity, this was an extremely important matter.

“Spiritas Empyrean?” Divine Dream asked, surprised. “An Empyrean… do you think she’ll be of help if you find her?”

“I’m not too sure…” Lin Ming couldn’t say with absolute certainty what would happen. If he found Sheng Mei, even if there wasn’t much she could do to help him there were at least some hopes.

“Senior Divine Dream, the person that junior wishes to see may only be an Empyrean but she is an extremely high level figure within the spiritas race. Junior wishes to find out from her just why the saints and spiritas would form a truce in the middle of their war, and whether or not humanity could pay some price to form an alliance with the spiritas.”

The enemy of an enemy was a friend. If humanity could ally with the spiritas then this great calamity might not be so terrifying.

“Form an alliance with the spiritas!”

Divine Dream’s eyes lit up. If this was possible then humanity would truly find a slim hope to survive!

But forming this alliance might not be so simple.

Not to mention that humanity might not be able to fulfill the conditions that the spiritas put forth, Lin Ming wanting to find Sheng Mei in the massive Soul World wouldn’t be easy at all.

To travel an ultra-long distance across the nearly limitless space of the universes of the 33 Heavens as well as be responsible for such an important mission that concerned the life or death of an entire race, this responsibility all fell onto Lin Ming’s shoulders. Divine Dream deeply sighed. “Lin Ming, in these past years you have done far too much for the human race. To think that the many Empyreans of humanity would have a junior like you bear such weight on your shoulders…”

Lin Ming said, “Senior Divine Dream, please don’t consider me an outsider. Humanity is my roots. If humanity is exterminated then I will become a leaf without roots… in any event, I will try my best to help humanity survive this great calamity. Concerning the question I asked Senior Divine Dream about the entrance to the Soul World, may I ask whether or not it still exists?”

“It is still there… it’s just that…” Empyrean Divine Dream pressed her eyebrows together, pausing for a moment before continuing to say, “It is a transmission array in an ancient ruin that I once stumbled upon during my youth. It is something passed down by unknown predecessors of humanity from 3.6 billion years ago, or even 4-5 billion years ago. For me to have my current achievements, a great reason for that is because I discovered this ancient ruin.

“This ancient ruin is in an extremely mysterious space. And because of some strange reasons, there is a crack in the God Lamenting Wall at this area…”

The walls dividing the 33 Heavens were by no means perfect. For a very small number of exceptions there were sometimes ‘wormholes’ or ‘black holes’ that broke through the space barriers in extremely mysterious places.

However, even if such mystical places existed it was still nearly impossible for a martial artist to pass through. But, if there was a True Divinity level powerhouse that was willing to sacrifice a portion of their cultivation, they could transform these mystical lands and form a connection through the barriers dividing the 33 Heavens.

When the saints first entered the universe of humanity to kill Empyrean Primordius and steal away the Grandmist Spirit Bead, that was all due to the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign personally creating a connection that passed through the God Lamenting Wall.

However, the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign didn’t find a wormhole or other crack in the wall. Rather, he used his powerful cultivation to penetrate a hole through the God Lamenting Wall.

But the ancient ruin that Empyrean Divine Dream mentioned was different. This place was originally a weak point of the God Lamenting Wall to begin with, and due to the efforts of the unknown ancient True Divinities, these places had become something similar to a transmission array connecting two universes that could be preserved for a long time.

After listening to Empyrean Divine Dream, Lin Ming was startled. To transform a weakened space and form a transmission array connecting through the God Lamenting Wall, this was truly an extremely skilled method. Perhaps even an ordinary True Divinity would be unable to do so, and one would need to be an outstanding existence amongst all True Divinities to succeed.

The history of humanity had once been grand and illustrious, with countless peerless elites rising from the ranks. But all of these people had been forgotten in the sands of time with nothing left behind…

Even the ancient ruin that Empyrean Divine Dream found had been left behind by some unknown ancient human sovereign.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “Lin Ming, only I know the location of that ancient ruin. It is just that because so much time has passed, the transmission array has become too dilapidated to maintain stability. If you want to forcefully enter then I fear it will be incredibly dangerous…

“The transmission array passes through the God Lamenting Wall where there are unfathomably fatal space storms. My worry is that you won’t be able to withstand them…”

“They are that strong?” Lin Ming was shocked. Empyrean Divine Dream already had a complete understanding of his strength and still had such worries. It could be seen from this just how horrifying those space storms were.

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “The terrifying space storms are just one aspect… another aspect is that the transmission array has become extremely frail over the ages, and it is now the same as a rotten plank bridge. If you use too much force on this fragile little bridge and furiously fight you will be able to force back the space storms. But the bridge itself might not be able to withstand the damage and could break apart. If so, you won’t even have bones remaining!”

Hearing Empyrean Divine Dream’s description, Lin Ming felt a chill crawl up his spine.

If he used too much strength then the transmission array itself would collapse, meaning he still wouldn’t be able to cross it!

Thus for this transmission array he would have to find some way to display the greatest efficacy with a limited level of strength. Only then would he be able to barely pass.

Perhaps in the entire Divine Realm there weren’t even a handful of people that could fulfill such harsh requirements…

Empyrean Divine Dream said, “Millions of years ago when I passed through the ancient transmission array it was in a much better state. But that is just how things were. After I crossed, the transmission array broke down even further. If you want to cross now, I have no idea what the situation will be like…”

Empyrean Divine Dream looked at Lin Ming, her lake-clear eyes filled with worry.

Lin Ming responded, “Even if it's difficult I must try. It is always better than waiting in the Divine Realm for that hundred year deadline to come and death to take us all. Moreover, when I go to the Soul World it’s to look for Sheng Mei but also to gain experience and temper myself. I won’t find that by secluding myself in the Divine Realm…”

In the Divine Realm there was no longer anyone that could contend with Lin Ming. To rule a tiny peaceful corner of the vast cosmos would be disadvantageous to Lin Ming’s growth.

Only journeying into the greater world and developing his field of vision, finding new and stronger opponents and struggling for more lucky chances would allow Lin Ming to grow into the person he needed to be.

“Since you have already firmed your resolve I will not try to change your mind. Lin Ming… you are humanity’s hope. Don’t forget that. For all of humanity, no matter what you try to do, nothing will be as important as making sure you stay alive. As long you are alive, that will be the greatest victory for us. If you can continue living for several hundred years or even millions of years, there will come a day when humanity will see the light of dawn once more!”

“Mm… I understand…”

Lin Ming took a deep breath and gripped his fists. The higher a martial artist’s cultivation was, the more difficult it was to go further. From a World King to an Empyrean, from an Empyrean to a True Divinity, these two large boundaries required an unbelievably long period of accumulations. This could not be substituted with any lucky chance.

Although Lin Ming might be able to compare with the weakest of Empyreans a hundred years from now, that was only in terms of fighting strength. In cultivation alone, it was unlikely Lin Ming would have broken into the World King realm.

There was still a long road ahead of him.

And the saints would not give him the time to walk down that road.

This was why Empyrean Divine Dream said that as long as Lin Ming lived on, that would be the greatest victory.

“I wonder what level I’ll reach several hundred years or even millions of years from now? At that time, will I be able to fight the Good Fortune Saint Sovereign?”

As Lin Ming thought of this, his heart filled with a heroic daring and fighting intent. This great calamity was a disaster to all of humanity, but at the same time it was also the seed for a great prosperous age to grow with countless lucky chances all around. Every young genius in the Divine Realm would be baptized in the fires of the great calamity.

Waves struck the shore but when the tides washed away, the real gold would emerge. For those that died, their deaths would be a loss, but for those that lived, all of them would become extraordinary individuals.

“Senior Divine Dream, when junior goes this time, my future will be uncertain. This junior would like to request that Senior Divine Dream takes care of my family, friends, and wives.”

As Lin Ming spoke to here, he looked at Xiao Moxian. “Xian’er, you should also stay at Divine Dream Heavenly Palace…”

“Big Brother Lin…” Xiao Moxian stiffened. As she looked at Lin Ming, there was some grievance in her eyes, and a bit of unwillingness. She had just reunited with Lin Ming and was now able to follow him in the future, but Lin Ming had decided to go to the Soul World and part ways for now. Of course she felt uncomfortable about this.

“I understand…” Xiao Moxian whispered, forcing out a smile. “Big Brother Lin, I will wait in the Divine Realm for your return.”

“I’m sorry...”

Seeing Xiao Moxian’s smile, Lin Ming felt even sadder. If possible he would definitely have loved to bring Xiao Moxian with him. No matter how perilous the Soul World was, he was willing to live and die with her.

But Xiao Moxian was pregnant.

Moreover, the child within her had an unusual level of talent. Before it took form, it was already able to absorb the power of the world. This was the reason why Xiao Moxian’s combat strength had dropped so drastically.

In this sort of situation, if Lin Ming brought Xiao Moxian to the Soul World to adventure he would definitely have all sorts of scruples. There would be many dangerous places he wouldn’t dare to go.

During this journey to the Soul World the perils were unknown, and in a sense it was the same as cutting off all paths of retreat. If he had too many worries it would be impossible to accomplish anything important. Then in this case it would be better to leave Xiao Moxian in the Divine Realm and have her cultivate in peace. This would be beneficial to both Xiao Moxian and their child.

Chapter 1785 – Thunder Punishment’s Inheritance

“Mm, sounds good.”

Lin Ming nodded. In the past, Empyrean Thunder Punishment was also a superior Empyrean if not a peak Empyrean. Any place of inheritance he established would not be easy to enter. Xiao Moxian was pregnant, and as for Lin Xiaoge, Mu Qianyu, and Qin Xingxuan, they were far from his strength. He didn’t want them to recklessly experience any dangers by entering deep into the Thunder Dominion.

“Go early and come back early!” The women looked at Lin Ming, a soft color in their eyes.

Lin Ming lightly nodded. Then, his gaze shifted to deep into the Thunder Dominion. With a wave of his sleeves he broke into the storm like a bolt of lightning. Time didn’t wait for anyone and with the full saint race invasion coming faster than thought, he needed to go to the Soul World as soon as possible. Before going to the Soul World, Lin Ming needed to make another breakthrough and increase his strength.

And the fastest way to make that breakthrough was to open the third Dao Palace – the Extreme Polar Dao Palace.

According to the Celestial Tyrant Manual, the Extreme Polar Dao Palace required two different types of energy to direct and catalyze the breakthrough. Lin Ming chose thunder and fire and in order to refine the pill required for the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, he needed an Empyrean level Thunder Source and Fire Elemental. Lin Ming had already obtained the Annihilation Fire Elemental from Empyrean Demondawn but now lacked a Thunder Source. With this, he naturally thought back to Empyrean Thunder Punishment.

It was certain that in the past Empyrean Thunder Punishment had possessed a top grade Thunder Source. Otherwise after he died there wouldn’t be such a massive Thunder Dominion that appeared above the Sea of Miracles and the 8000 Mile Black Swamp.

Now, Lin Ming only wanted to obtain the Thunder Source as soon as possible and combine it with the Annihilation Flame Elemental to make his breakthrough.

Bang!

Arcs of thunder lashed at Lin Ming like endless whips. But, they all vanished upon touching him without causing any damage at all.

After breaking over 40 miles deep into the Thunder Dominion, the power of thunder became increasingly strong.

This was different from the last time that Lin Ming had entered the Thunder Dominion. Now, the true meaning of thunder within Lin Ming had already reached the seventh level boundary.

Facing this rumbling thunder, all of it turned into endless thunder runes and source Thunder Laws within Lin Ming’s eyes. The thunder and fire above the Heretical God Tree within his body began to resonate with this thunder, helping him unconsciously clarify the true meaning of thunder and gladdening his heart.

Flying further in, the thunder light began to turn a deep purple.

Thunder roared through the world, turning into purple pythons and winding about.

A power of thunder a hundred times greater than before smashed into Lin Ming. As a result, all of this power of thunder was swallowed up by Lin Ming, intermingling with the thunder and fire that hovered atop the boughs of the Heretical God Tree.

As Lin Ming broke further and further in, the deep purple thunder light turned a destructive black… and then back to gold…

Zizizi!

Arcs of multi-colored thunder twined around Lin Ming, finally condensing into traces of dense thunder runes that percolated in his muscles, as if he was a god of thunder being reborn.

After delving further into the Thunder Dominion, Lin Ming’s understanding and experience in the Thunder Laws became even deeper.

When Lin Ming reached 90 miles into the Thunder Dominion, the thunder turned from golden red to an ephemeral purple gold.

Not too far in front was the 90 mile edge of the Thunder Dominion. A purple white dreamy light suddenly appeared like a sea amongst parting clouds, seemingly endless.

This mystic light was like the glow of a sunset. It illuminated the world, captivating the heart with a breathtaking beauty.

Lin Ming could feel that even though this purple white light appeared as calm as a placid sea, there was actually a wild and strange strength contained within it.

“We’re finally here.” Lin Ming whispered. His deep eyes looked through the dreamy mystic light in front of him and sighed.

The last time he entered the Thunder Dominion, he was able to sense that the most dangerous place was this 90 mile Thunder Dominion.

In his eyes, the dreamy mystic light before him became massive thunder runes that floated up and down like chains of islands.

Within these runes was the existence of the true meaning of thunder, making his heart itch.

Lin Ming was well aware that this place was the true edge of Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s inheritance.

As he continued forwards, the dreamy thunder continued washing over his body.

The Heretical God Tree within Lin Ming’s inner world rose. Endless thunder dragons hovered above the branches. As more and more power of thunder intruded here, it turned into thunder runes that stayed within him.

In the past this illusionary thunder would have horrified him. But now, it wasn’t able to harm him at all.

In a single breath he pierced a hundred miles deep into the Thunder Dominion. It was like his entire body was covered in a silver-white layer of armor, an extremely ghostly sight.

“Mm?”

On Lin Ming’s normally expressionless face, a rare solemn look appeared.

At the 100 mile Thunder Dominion, the thunder here was absolutely still. Thunder balls quietly floated in the air, seeming peaceful.

As for Lin Ming, with his current divine sense he was able to clearly see that the distortions around the thunder balls were shattered space. This space formed a cage around each thunder ball, sealing the thunder ball at its central point.

Deeper past these thunder balls, there were islands that floated up and down, emitting a strong aura of vitality.

And even further in there were increasingly intense fluctuations of life. Deeper in there were continuous mountain ranges and snaking rivers, all of them exuding the blood vitality of powerful life forms…

Lin Ming had seen these sights before. But as he saw it now, he was even more shocked.

In his vision, trillions of runes tumbled about like grains of sand, condensing into thunder balls.

And from the rules in which the thunder balls were arranged, he could make out clear lines.

These thunder balls were a continuous wall, each thunder ball as large as a brick. Within the walls of thunder balls were mountain ranges, rivers, and so forth.

Every thunder ball contained an inexplicably mystical force, each one resonating and constantly shifting along with the others. With the way these billions upon billions of transformations constantly changed, this should be a heaven-shockingly grand array.

Lin Ming didn’t doubt that if he tried to forcefully enter past the thunder balls and triggered them it would set off a chain reaction of explosions.

This sort of explosion would be enough to crack apart a planet. Although he wouldn’t die he would be severely wounded.

And the initiation of the chain reaction might automatically activate other mechanisms that Empyrean Thunder Punishment had left within, causing all the inheritances to be lost. The gains just weren’t worth the cost.

Lin Ming’s eyes flashed. He calmed his mind and deeply pondered how to deal with this situation. Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s inheritance had been carefully hidden in the deepest depths of these thunder balls. If he wanted to enter he would need to unravel this thunder ball array formation.

Lin Ming currently had a ridiculous accumulation of knowledge. The Asura blood had contained a part of the Asura Road Master’s infinite memories, and he had also swallowed up the memories of the dark divine runic grandmaster Shadow Overflow and several others. In terms of understanding array formations and the structure of runes, he had a vast breadth of expertise.

His pupils shined with a brilliant light. Within his gaze, every fluctuation and change of energy in the thunder ball array formation was clearly reflected.

He sat cross-legged in space and began to rapidly deduce the formulaic structures in his mind.

Gradually, an abstract of the entire thunder ball array formation appeared in his mind like a divine runic symbol’s structural diagram.

Through the endless deductions, the innumerable changes were peeled away like threads of a cocoon.

Suddenly, a sharp light burst out from within Lin Ming’s eyes like bolts of lightning. He stood up and thrust out the Phoenix Blood Spear.

As the spear thrust out, a cold red light drew a strange path through the air that conformed to the Heavenly Dao Laws and instantly arrived in the middle of the thunder balls. The extremely fierce spear light rumbled into a central point of the sealed space.

Within the originally perfectly fitted wall of thunder balls, an area began to shake and tear open like a slit in fabric.

A sparkling mystical power of thunder gushed out like starlight from the slit.

This strange mystic power of thunder was completely different from anything Lin Ming had experienced in the Thunder Dominion so far. It carried with it a vast and ancient aura, as if it had flowed out from the rivers of time, filled with a life of its own.

As some thunder balls bumped into these star-like power of thunder, they actually began to form lush branches and leaves that were overflowing with vitality. It was a strange sight to witness.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

As this small hole appeared, Lin Ming instantly shot out a million spear strikes, alternatingly hitting areas all over the thunder ball array formation and making the hole even larger.

The thunder ball array formation began to shake. Finally, an opening the size of a person was exposed with an endless power of thunder wildly surging out of it.

It was like a door of light had been opened.

Behind this door was still the gruesome roars of ancient beasts that seemed as if they could shake the world. There was also the outlines of massive mountain ranges that stretched out to the horizon, floating up and down within the thunder barrier.

Lin Ming’s heart chilled. He knew that he couldn’t miss this chance and quickly rushed in.

After entering the depths of the 100 mile Thunder Dominion, he could feel the atmosphere of boundless years past.

Beneath his feet was ground completely formed by condensed thunder crystals. In the far off distance he could make out innumerable islands that floated in the void.

And above these islands were giant trees that exuded an immense mystic power of thunder.

Every tree had countless condensed thunder dragons that circled around the trunk.

The trees were around the height of two people. They were surrounded by verdant green grass that shimmered with the power of thunder, making it an extremely strange sight.

Lin Ming could see that in the far off distance, there was a massive mountain range blocking the way that towered into the skies where it was hidden by thunder clouds.

At the summit of this mountain range was an inexhaustible mass of thunder clouds that converged into an endless vortex, seeming timeless and magnificent.

One could even faintly make out that on the peak of the highest mountain, there was a giant palace.

This palace was so high that it was impossible to see the end. All one could see was that the mountain-sized golden gates emitted an endless mystic power of thunder.

It was like a giant sun was burning without end at the top.

“…The land of inheritance!” Feeling the aura emanating from the palace, the Heretical God Tree within Lin Ming and the many thunder dragons that wound about it began to cry out in excitement.

Lin Ming could clearly the seventh level true meaning of thunder. It actually emitted an incredibly desirable aura as if it had a spiritual wisdom of its own.

Like there was something within the golden palace that was calling out to him.

Lin Ming was heated with excitement. Just as he was about to rush over, he heard a loud sound; it was the roar of a beast that seemed to echo through the heavens and earth.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming was startled. After all, this was a land of inheritance formed after Empyrean Thunder Punishment died. Although it was inferior to Empyrean Primordius’ inheritance, it was still extremely terrifying.

Even though Lin Ming had stepped into the Holy Lord realm, he still remained vigilant upon entering here and didn’t dare to lower his guard.

The roar that shook the world had come from within the golden palace.

Lin Ming’s mind went on alert. His footsteps crossed the void and he soon reached the summit of the mountain peak, right in front of the grand golden palace.

Chapter 1787 – Thunder Punishment’s Remnant Soul

In the darkened hall, the figure in front of Lin Ming that he originally thought was a corpse suddenly rose up, its eyes flashing open!

For a time two green lights lit up the hall. Those sharp eyes pierced through the darkness like twin bolts of lightning.

Lin Ming was aghast. He took a sudden step back. To encounter such a situation here would leave anyone creeped out.

“Thunder Punishment hasn’t died?”

This thought raced through Lin Ming’s mind, causing a cold chill to crawl up his back.

Lin Ming had originally suspected that Empyrean Primordius hadn’t died.

If that were true then it wouldn’t be strange for Empyrean Thunder Punishment to have not perished either, but instead be severely wounded like Empyrean Divine Mist and have sealed himself away to maintain his life.

If so, then this situation wasn’t good at all.

Facing this person who had once been sworn brothers with Empyrean Primordius and whose strength reached the upper levels of Empyrean powerhouses, Lin Ming didn’t dare to take any rash actions before understanding the situation more.

“After so many years, someone was finally able to enter here… what a rare sight…” Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s voice constantly fluctuated, but the tone remained slow and deep.

Lin Ming silently looked out at Empyrean Thunder Punishment as he rapidly assessed his strength. He could faintly feel that Empyrean Thunder Punishment was currently in a very poor state.

“Is he a remnant soul…?”

Lin Ming wondered. If only a remnant soul remained that had attached onto Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s corpse, then to the current him this wouldn’t be too terrifying at all.

“Is Senior the one who created the Thunder Dominion? Could this place be the land of inheritance that Senior left behind?” Lin Ming falsely asked.

“Indeed. This Thunder Dominion was created by me 100,000 years ago.” Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s heavy voice droned on. “For you to arrive here is your good fortune!”

As Thunder Punishment spoke these words his eyes blazed at Lin Ming, wanting to completely see through Lin Ming’s inner world.

Feeling the probing of Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s divine sense, Lin Ming’s thoughts chilled. He hurriedly hid away things that shouldn’t be seen by Empyrean Thunder Punishment like the black dragon egg, Primordius martial intent energy, and other things.

Even the overly powerful Asura Laws and the black hole created by the Divine Seal Art were covered up. This was because if Empyrean Thunder Punishment were to find such things it would naturally arouse suspicion.

It was impossible for a normal martial artist of the Divine Realm to possess such things.

After hiding these away, Lin Ming’s inner world became far more ordinary. Even so, his more ordinary inner world left Empyrean Thunder Punishment shaken just as it was. He looked at Lin Ming with amazement in his heart.

He originally assumed that Lin Ming might be some interstellar wanderer who had accidently stumbled onto the Sky Spill Planet and who also possessed ordinary talent. Even so, Empyrean Thunder Punishment still had to leave his inheritance with Lin Ming, because asking for a top talent to come to some remote place like the Sky Spill Planet was just impossible.

If Empyrean Thunder Punishment could hand down his inheritance he would be more than content. But, he never imagined Lin Ming’s talent would be so extraordinary.

“Your talent is much better than expected…”

Empyrean Thunder Punishment felt this was unbelievable. In truth, his ability to sense talent was limited and because he was only a leftover remnant soul, the force behind this divine sense was also ordinary. If Empyrean Thunder Punishment were to know what Lin Ming’s true battle strength was, he might have been shocked unconscious.

“Senior’s praise is too much. This junior’s talent is mediocre. It's only through some lucky chances that I’ve found some heavenly materials to consolidate the foundation of my blood vitality and obtain my current achievements.” Lin Ming casually explained.

“Heavenly materials? Empyrean Thunder Punishment repeated, startled. He immediately nodded. “Yes, your blood vitality billows into the sky, and it even seems to contain the aura of a God Beast. Without many heavenly materials to support you it would indeed be impossible for you to reach such heights. This proves that both your destiny and foundation are outstanding and that you are sufficient to become my descendant.”

Empyrean Thunder Punishment leaned forwards a little, his gaze focusing on Lin Ming’s face, as if waiting for an elated expression to show up on it.

However, Lin Ming’s face remained stiff, without any response at all.

This left Empyrean Thunder Punishment frowning a little. But thinking about it further, perhaps this youth simply didn’t know who he was, so he wouldn’t be aware of what the significance behind his inheritance was.

Thus, Empyrean Thunder Punishment lightly coughed and said, “You probably don’t know my identity. In the Divine Realm’s 3000 great worlds, I am the Empyrean of Thunderlight World – Empyrean Thunder Punishment. In the past I freely roamed the Divine Realm and my strength was also amazing even amongst Empyreans. The Thunder Punishment Heavenly Palace that I established was a peak Empyrean influence of the Divine Realm that had gathered countless outstanding geniuses. My Heavenly Palace even approached the number one Empyrean influence of the Divine Realm – Mount Potala!

“If I choose you as my descendant then that is completely different from taking you as a disciple. A disciple is someone to be taught my inheritance, but as a descendant not only would I teach you my complete inheritance but you would also possess all my treasures and take on my legacy. That is the same as inheriting the entirety of an Empyrean. Since you have already cultivated to such a boundary you should understand the meaning behind my words, right?”

As Empyrean Thunder Punishment spoke, he looked at Lin Ming expectantly. Lin Ming stiffly nodded, “Understood.”

“Mm…”

Empyrean Thunder Punishment dragged on his word, seeming a bit reluctant to continue. “For you to not panic in the face of such a lucky chance proves that your disposition is quite good. It’s no wonder you’ve achieved such achievements at such a young age.”

As Empyrean Thunder Punishment spoke, his figure suddenly rose up. He stepped through the void, one foot at a time, until he arrived right in front of Lin Ming.

That old and solemn face stopped just a foot away from Lin Ming’s own. From this distance, Lin Ming could feel a massive pressure slowly press down on him, as if a god of thunder had traversed the river of time, walking through 100,000 years to meet him.

Although Empyrean Thunder Punishment only had a wisp of his remnant soul remaining and not much strength left, this was the pressure of an Empyrean. Lin Ming raised his guard.

He could feel that the remnant soul in front of him contained the source of thunder. Although it was just a remnant soul he couldn’t underestimate it.

“Are you willing to inherit the whole of my legacy?” Empyrean Thunder Punishment slowly spoke, his words drilling into Lin Ming’s ears.

Although Empyrean Thunder Punishment was secretly unwilling, he had still once been a supreme martial artist. He didn’t want his lifetime of knowledge to be lost to the world, vanishing without a single successor.

Lin Ming’s thoughts raced. He asked, “Inheriting Senior’s inheritance shouldn’t be so simple, right? May I ask what conditions there are?”

“Haha! Smart young boy!” Empyrean Thunder Punishment laughed out loud. The pupils that he stared at Lin Ming with emitted a strange light, becoming increasingly hazy like a dream.

“…if you want to inherit my legacy, you must make an oath…” As Empyrean Thunder Punishment spoke, his pupils became increasingly profound and tinged with a deep hatred.

“I want you to vow that after you inherit my legacy, in your lifetime you must seek out all the roots and branches of that old dog Primordius and kill them all off. If you cannot complete this task then you will be punished by the heavens and your divine soul will be annihilated!”

As Empyrean Thunder Punishment spoke, he couldn’t hide the strong killing intent behind his words.

A strange color filled Lin Ming’s complexion. In truth, he already expected this kind of oath.

“Kill off all the roots and branches of Empyrean Primordius? Isn’t that just wanting me to commit suicide? I am the only one who inherited Empyrean Primordius’ legacy after all.”

As Lin Ming was thinking, Empyrean Thunder Punishment continued to say, “In addition to that, in the future you must gather soul-restoring heavenly materials for me. I only have a wisp of remnant soul remaining, and although my body has been preserved for 100,000 years using a secret technique, it has already reached the point of decay and cannot be further used. You must help me in my rebirth!

“I have a secret skill that can use the power of thunder to refine a living soul and suck out their soul essence to make up for my own lacking soul force. You must gather souls for me, the more powerful the better. Those souls that possess talent that can fight past their levels, those have the best effects!”

The power of thunder was originally the nemesis of souls. If a powerful soul was struck by thunder it would be turned into soul force essence. As for spirit marks and so forth, all of that would be turned to nothingness and there wouldn’t be any side effects to absorbing the leftovers.

And Empyrean Thunder Punishment was a master of thunder arts. This sort of demonic soul-restoring devil arts could be said to perfectly suit him.

“If I am to understand it, then after inheriting Senior’s inheritance I must endlessly kill people to help restore Senior’s soul?” Lin Ming asked.

“That’s right. The road of martial arts is a path of murder and destruction to begin with. Not only must you help restore my remnant soul but after doing so you must find me a suitable body so that I can seize it and be truly reborn!”

Chapter 1790 – Destroying Thunder Punishment

“You!!” Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s remnant soul violently shivered. He looked at Lin Ming, burning with rage. “You deliberately hid your strength to fool me!?”

At the same time Empyrean Thunder Punishment was furious, he was also panic-stricken. He was now just a remnant soul. Compared to his previous magnificence from 100,000 years ago when he had been a superior Empyrean that stood above all others, his strength had dropped precipitously. Even so, his insight was not something that an ordinary martial artist could hope to compare with, so how had he been played around with by a Holy Lord realm junior?

This boy, just what methods had he used?

As Empyrean Thunder Punishment was surprised, he felt an extremely familiar aura erupt from within Lin Ming’s inner world. Besides being familiar, this was also an aura that he loathed to no end.

For a time, his entire body seemed to light up with arcs of electricity as lightning burst out from his eyes.

His originally phantasmal figure began to rapidly rise as his momentum grew.

An inexplicable killing intent leapt out, wrapping around Lin Ming.

“Grandmist energy! You actually have grandmist energy within you!” Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s voice rang like layers of thunderclouds, echoing in the hall as it was filled with disbelief and wrath.

Lin Ming remained silent. The light of the Thunder Punishment Sword in his hand slowly faded away.

With a thought, the entire Gold Thunder Temple began to rapidly shrink, sending out endless runes that carried the true meaning of thunder within them. Finally, the temple turned into a palm-sized version in his hands that was easily held in his grasp.

Without fully extinguishing Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s remnant soul, Lin Ming wouldn’t be able to use the Thunder Punishment Sword and Gold Thunder Temple without worries.

“When you betrayed Empyrean Primordius in the past, did you ever think there would come a day when it happened to you?” Lin Ming lightly said. The light around him began to distort, becoming chaotic as it formed a strange field around him.

“Primordius martial intent! Good! Very good!” Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s pupils shrank. His form couldn’t help but shiver, even as a hateful light burst out of his eyes and locked onto Lin Ming.

“So you had already inherited the legacy of that old thief Primordius before coming here, and then you hid your aura to deceive me!”

Empyrean Thunder Punishment gnashed his teeth. This brat was actually the descendant of Empyrean Primordius!

He had waited for 100,000 years in this Thunder Dominion, existing in the state of a remnant soul. Yet, the only one who came to visit him after all this time was a descendant of his blood enemy. And what left Empyrean Thunder Punishment most perplexed was that he hadn’t been able to see through the illusions created by this junior, and as a result he had submissively given away his inheritance.

“Brat, you are seeking death!”

A sharp light burst out from Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s pupils. A powerful ghostly force thrust out from his eyes, mixed in with rumbling thunder as it rushed into Lin Ming’s body.

Facing the enraged Empyrean Thunder Punishment, Lin Ming simply thrust out his hand. Then, an icy cold aura gushed out from his body, an aura that contained the screams of 10,000 demons and countless ghosts.

Pitch black soul force condensed into a massive wheel, with Asura phantoms pushing it from above.

This was the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel.

Just as the overlapping layers of ghostly thunder were about to explode, all of it was diverted to the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and then slowly grinded away.

As this thunder was slowly grinded away, soul force dissipated from it before completely vanishing.

Seeing this, Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s complexion darkened. This was not a technique that a junior could possess.

“Who are you, it is impossible for you to be a Holy Lord realm martial artist!”

In Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s opinion, it was utterly impossible for any Holy Lord realm martial artist to fight with him. At the start, he had carefully verified that Lin Ming was indeed just a Holy Lord martial artist, and this was the reason he believed that Lin Ming could never escape his control.

Lin Ming simply didn’t bother with Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s nonsense. The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel slowly revolved, floating beneath his feet.

“Humph! Do you really think I can’t do anything to you?” With Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s cold cough, a strange sound emitted from his body. All around him, runes that contained the world Laws began to continuously appear.

These runes formed thunder dragons in the sky. As they soared into the wind, it seemed as if the entire world had become one of thunder.

In an instant, these infinite thunder dragons opened their bell-like eyes, dark and gloomy and emitting bursts of thunder light.

At the same time, meteor-sized thunder balls appeared in space, all of them exuding a strange mystic power.

Countless invisible hands seemed to appear in the air. Suddenly, Lin Ming felt as if he couldn’t control his body.

“This is a force field? With just a wisp of a remnant soul you can spur the power of the Laws as well as form this thunder force field?” Lin Ming was surprised. Empyrean Thunder Punishment was indeed far too powerful. His mortal body had been destroyed and his inner world no longer existed. Yet, by just relying on his remnant soul he was able to form such a formidable thunder force field.

Although Empyrean Thunder Punishment put on a brave front, the truth was that he was in a critical situation. He no longer possessed the power of his past, and this strange young man in front of him simply had far too many strange secrets.

Thunder Punishment thrust his hands out into the void. The power of thunder drawn out by this soul force began to wildly rage about. 10,000 thunder dragons howled. The void began to shake and contract upon Lin Ming as if it wanted to thoroughly swallow him up.

Lin Ming remained unworried. Without expression, he calmly stretched out a hand. Motes of black light condensed in his palm, sparkling. Then, these motes of light gathered together on Lin Ming’s palm, turning into a black cube that exuded an ancient and vast aura.

As the Magic Cube appeared, the surrounding space fell into a deathly silence.

Although the Magic Cube was currently just the size of a hand, it gave off an extremely offsetting feeling. It was like a black universe, encompassing all, terrifying and dense.

Every mote of black light was like an endless black vortex that emitted endless mystic strength.

Any soul force-condensed thunder dragons that approached were mercilessly pulled in by an invisible hand and swallowed up, completely disappearing. After they disappeared their connection with Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s soul force was severed.

Seeing this black cube appear, Empyrean Thunder Punishment began to shiver and his complexion completely changed.

His current form was nothing more than a remnant soul, making his existence sensitive to the Magic Cube. As a remnant soul, he felt an instinctual fear towards this divine tool. Just by looking at this black cube it felt as if the last dregs of his soul would be sucked up.

“What is that!?”

Empyrean Thunder Punishment didn’t recognize the Magic Cube. Although he knew about the Grandmist Spirit Bead, he had no knowledge of the Magic Cube.

From the middle of the Magic Cube, an all-annihilating black light suddenly erupted outwards.

As this black light expanded in all directions, it swept through the world.

The thunder force field that had been suppressing Lin Ming collided with the black light. Then, the thunder force field began to rapidly break down and be destroyed. Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s spirit mark within it was also wiped away.

It was all swept up by the black light and then swallowed.

Seeing this, Empyrean Thunder Punishment began to show visible panic. His soul force was so incredibly fragile in the face of the black light that it would collapse on the first strike?

Finally, he could feel the terrifying strength contained within that black light, one that seemed as vast and deep as the endless seas.

“If you were a ruined body, I wouldn’t be able to do anything to you. Too bad for you, you are nothing but a remnant soul, and this thunder force field is also formed by you using your soul force to move the Laws. After all, you don’t have an inner world so the amount of heaven and earth origin energy you can use is limited, thus of no threat to me at all.”

Lin Ming’s voice was indifferent. He directly summoned the Magic Cube.

For a time, a horrifyingly great energy vortex appeared in the skies.

Black light swept out. Empyrean Thunder Punishment felt a terrifying strength cover his body. This was a power of Laws that no one could resist. He wildly shouted out but the black light had completely covered him.

Whorl – whorl – whorl –

The Magic Cube began to expand. Empyrean Thunder Punishment roared out, “What is that!? Just who are you!?”

Empyrean Thunder Punishment was terrified. Although he hadn’t seen the Magic Cube before, he had seen the Grandmist Spirit Bead. He had a faint feeling that this cube was in no way inferior to the Grandmist Spirit Bead divine tool! Everything that occurred today had completely surpassed his imagination.

He had inexplicably encountered this terrifying youth who had come out of nowhere. Not just that, but this youth was in possession of an incredible divine tool that perfectly suppressed him, one which possessed a power he could not fathom!

This didn’t make any sense at all!

“Just die as a confused ghost.”

Lin Ming coolly said. He poured more strength into the Magic Cube.

From the black vortex, Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s pitiful wails could be heard.

He maliciously cursed out all the hatred in his heart, unwilling to die here. His ending was just far too miserable. His inheritance had been stolen away by the descendant of his blood enemy and now even his remnant soul was being eliminated!

How could he not hate this!?

However, no matter how much he cursed or struggled, a mere wisp of a remnant soul wasn’t able to cause a ruckus in front of the Magic Cube.

Time marched on. After an incense stick of time, Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s words slowly died down.

Lin Ming wasn’t in a hurry at all. He leisurely activated the Magic Cube to continue refining for a quarter hour before ordering it to stop.

At this moment, the spirit mark within Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s remnant soul had been completely erased by the Magic Cube.

“He was indeed worthy of being called a top Empyrean. His wisp of remnant soul didn’t even possess a tenth his original soul force intensity, and had even been weakened over 100,000 years. Yet I still had to summon the Magic Cube to subdue him. Otherwise, I fear that just relying on the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel alone wouldn’t have been enough to kill him.” Lin Ming tranquilly stated as he slowly took back the Magic Cube.

He knew that the moment he finished fusing his energies with the Thunder Punishment Sword and the Gold Thunder Temple, Empyrean Thunder Punishment would begin integrating the curse into his soul. At this time, Lin Ming would have no choice but to reveal his strength and also his status as Empyrean Primordius’ successor. Thus, Lin Ming had already kept the Magic Cube prepared.

After starting the battle with Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s remnant soul, he summoned the Magic Cube.

The Magic Cube was a divine tool that was the ultimate nemesis of all masters that used soul force. Even the remnant soul of a top Empyrean wasn’t its match.

As Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s remnant soul was destroyed, the entire Gold Thunder Temple and Thunder Punishment Sword were carefully put away by Lin Ming.

By the time Lin Ming finished all of this, several hundred miles from the center of the Thunder Dominion, the terrifying and billowing thunderclouds had mostly vanished.

As the thunderclouds disappeared in massive tracts, large swathes of a black swamp were revealed beneath Lin Ming.

In the midst of the darkness, Lin Ming grasped the glittering Thunder Source. The Thunder Source emitted wave after wave of shimmering arcs of electricity, as if it were a thunder emperor being reborn.

“I’ve obtained the Thunder Source. With the Annihilation Flame Elemental and some top grade Twinlife Thunder Crystals… I’ve fulfilled the conditions to refine the Extreme Polar Pill. After I do that, I can break through the Extreme Polar Dao Palace…” Lin Ming pondered. After he broke through the third Dao Palace, his strength would rise even further.

With that, he could go to the Soul World and seek out Sheng Mei!

Chapter 1791 – Opening the Extreme Polar Dao Palace

Looking up at the high skies, the stars shined brightly.

In the distant periphery of the Thunder Dominion, a group of people from the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom arrived, riding up in a golden chariot. They didn’t dare enter the depths of the Thunder Dominion itself.

The uproar coming from the Thunder Dominion was far too great, causing everyone to be alarmed.

They could see that in the deepest depths of the Thunder Dominion, dazzling bolts of thunder came rumbling down, as if the entire Thunder Dominion was about to be blasted open.

It seemed as if some people were engaged in a fierce battle, but with their strength it was impossible for them to see clearly.

Suddenly, everyone saw a blinding eruption occur from the depths of the Thunder Dominion.

The light was incredibly harsh and blinding. Just a single glance at the sight caused tears to fall.

Afterwards, massive swathes of the power of thunder began rapidly rushing back to the center of that brilliant light like a receding tide.

In just half an incense stick of time, the originally perilous Thunder Dominion was extinguished of all light. All that remained in the skies were some scattered thunder clouds; one couldn’t feel any power of thunder anymore.

“This is… what’s happening?”

The people from the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom were dumbfounded.

From the most ancient of historical records, the Thunder Dominion that existed above the Sea of Miracles – a place where even Divine Sea supreme elders would die if they entered – had suddenly vanished! This was simply incredible!

At the same time, at a place 30 miles deep in the Thunder Dominion, Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, and Lin Xiaoge were watching this occur with happy expressions.

Out of the group, Xiao Moxian was the strongest. With her vision, everything that occurred hundreds of miles away was reflected in her pupils.

“Big Brother Lin has received the Thunder Source…”

Xiao Moxian could see a dark place in the center of the Thunder Dominion.

Lin Ming sat in the midst of the void, his hands each holding onto the Annihilation Flame Elemental as well as the top grade Thunder Source. From afar it seemed he was holding a black sun and a purple sun in his hands.

A strange and mystical power of fire heavenly tribulation emitted from the pores of his body, carrying with it a rhythm like a beating lotus flower.

Every time this flame flickered, space would be burnt away like paper and massive space storms would howl out.

One could see from this just how hot these flames were.

Lin Ming’s hands were wrapped in electricity as he started to draw in the void. Runes appeared, each of them carrying the true meaning of the Dao as they locked in this part of the world and struck against the strange heavenly tribulation fire.

In a moment, the surrounding space distorted as the form of a furnace appeared in front of him.

After that, he tossed all sorts of heavenly materials, the Twinlife Thunder Crystals, top grade Thunder Source, and Annihilation Fire Elemental into the furnace.

With this, he began refining!

The entire refining process didn’t take too long. But in Xiao Moxian’s eyes, this sight was more than enough to stir the soul.

As Lin Ming reached the end of the refining process, truefire spewed out from every inch of his skin, rumbling into the furnace…

Seven days later, a massive explosive sound blasted out. A 100,000 foot thunder dragon and fire phoenix tore through the world, flying in tandem. Even the gray barrier that guarded the entire Sky Spill Planet was struck, the impact almost enough to shatter planets.

The momentum of the sound was titanic and without end.

At this time, in front of Lin Ming, a fist-sized pill appeared, one that resembled yin and yang fish swimming together.

One side was blue thunder and the other side was red fire, both of them emitting a terrifying energy.

Lin Ming swallowed this pill in a single motion. A booming explosion began sounding out in his body like thunderclaps.

After some time, his forehead, eyes, nose, everything began to erupt with a blinding brilliance that impacted into the horizons and scattered away the dark clouds.

From the originally gloomy skies, it was like some faint summons was being sent out as starlight began to fall down.

Nine vast and shining stars appeared high above the endless starry skies, arranged in a strange manner that was filled with profound meaning. Their light tore through the infinite dark, shining down and creating a separate world.

One of these stars in particular shined like a sun at noon. Its radiance was dazzling, seemingly carrying with it an incredible mystic strength.

This star was named Cherished Kismet and was one of the nine stars. As it bloomed with a brilliant divine light, the starlight fell down like a silver waterfall that contained a dreadful strength. Even Xiao Moxian felt goosebumps rise on her arms.

From the void, lines of the Great Dao appeared, condensing into a strange pattern that blocked out the dazzling stars above.

The true meaning of two peak strengths filled the space around the dao diagram, like a dragon and a phoenix protecting it together.

This was the Heavenly Dao array diagram that hindered humanity from breaking into the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace. This dao diagram was filled with an inexplicable charm, as if it were alive.

“…Extreme Polar Dao Palace… Big Brother Lin is finally starting his breakthrough!” Seeing this occur, Xiao Moxian was both nervous and happy.

In her eyes, Lin Ming suddenly erupted with an incredible strength that was accompanied by the thick smell of blood.

Loud explosions occurred non-stop within his body like endless thunderclaps, as if a True Dragon were awakening within him.

His figure rose and pitch black scales emerged from his body, forming armor around him. His aura climbed, becoming increasingly wild and swift, fierce with a brutal savageness. Behind him, a massive six-armed and three-headed Asura phantom appeared. This Asura phantom seemed to have crawled out from a blood pond of hell. Its two pupils burned like twin suns, releasing a dreadful light.

Lin Ming looked up towards the most brilliant star in the sky. Then, at this time, a towering tree began to rise behind him, as grand as a mountain.

This tree stabbed into the skies. Countless thunder dragons flew around it and innumerable fire phoenixes twined around its branches. The momentum it released was astonishing.

A pitch black spear appeared, like an ancient vicious dragon tearing through time to arrive here. The power of the world and all the surrounding Laws twisted around this black spear and were torn apart.

As this spear appeared, the numerous thunder dragons and fire phoenixes around the tree flew down to twine around it.

Waves of blood vitality also began gathering at the spear point.

Then, this black spear began to roar like a demon god. A blinding light erupted from the spear point, like thousands of supernovas occurring together.

Bang!

Lin Ming shot up from the ground, his feet stepping on space.

Beneath the tremendous impact of his strength, the space under his feet shattered like glass.

Man and spear shot upwards, becoming one.

All that was seen was the black spear in Lin Ming’s hands. Like a black dragon it endlessly attacked the dao diagram in the starry skies.

Bang! Bang! Bang!

Every strike of the black spear caused all the power of the world within a hundred miles to be drawn towards it. It swallowed all of this power, every strike impacting the dao diagram with the force of a burning star.

The entire dao diagram began to ripple.

Waves of dazzling Grand Dao lines fell down with starlight. As they struck Lin Ming’s body, the impact was as heavy as a planet…

Time passed quarter hour after quarter hour.

During this time, parts of the dao diagram would shatter and starlight would fall down.

There were also times when Lin Ming approached exhaustion. He would open the Purple Temple Dao Palace to stimulate his potential and begin rushing upwards once more.

Shockwaves tore through the void, causing the black starry skies to collapse like glass…

Lin Ming’s figure was completely covered with starlight and blood. As he collided with the dao diagram again and again, everything seemed to blend together as one.

Just as Lin Ming’s strength reached its limits, there was an explosion and a heaven-shaking noise that echoed through the world.

The dao diagram above Lin Ming loudly shattered and the lines of the Great Dao dissipated like clouds of smoke.

From the void, the glittering Cherished Kismet Star shined, its starlight flowing into Lin Ming’s body.

His broken bones and torn flesh began to visibly mend.

“Extreme Polar Dao Palace… I broke through!”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. After breaking past two Dao Palaces before, breaking into the Extreme Polar Dao Palace was much simpler.

One reason was that he had made sufficient preparations. Whether it was the Annihilation Fire Elemental that Empyrean Demondawn gave him or Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s Thunder Source, both were top powers of thunder and fire.

Another reason was that Lin Ming was stronger than before and he had also broken past the shackles of the Heavenly Dao. In breaking into the third Dao Palace, it was far more familiar.

The third Dao Palace, the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, corresponded with the Cherished Kismet Star.

This palace was located in Lin Ming’s inner world. After opening the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, Lin Ming could guide the power of the nine stars to enter his inner world and fuse with the energy within.

And the energy within Lin Ming’s inner world was mainly thunder and fire. This was the equivalent of adding the power of a star into the power of thunder and fire.

With this, Lin Ming’s thunder and fire origin energy would rise to another level.

As Lin Ming examined his own inner world, he found that at the central point of his inner world’s planet, the giant Heretical God Tree was bathing in the endless mercurial starlight, beautiful to the extreme.

Because he had broken into the Extreme Polar Dao Palace, the Heretical God Tree had benefitted from this and had become even more verdant and hardy.

Thus, Lin Ming’s strength rose again. For him to enter the Soul World alone, this provided him with more confidence.

There wasn’t much time left before the great calamity truly began.

Chapter 1792 – Towards Soul World

Three days later, Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom –

Lin Ming’s actions at the Thunder Dominion were far too gargantuan. It was impossible for him to not arouse the attention of the four great Divine Kingdoms.

In addition, some people had already notified the high level figures of the Nine Furnace Divine Kingdom. Thus, when Lin Ming finished breaking through the third Dao Palace of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace and left the 8000 Miles Black Swamp, a group of Divine Sea powerhouses was already waiting for him.

Lin Ming returning to the Sky Spill Continent once more was a momentous event; no one wanted to miss it.

However, none of these Divine Sea powerhouses ever imagined that after arriving at the 8000 Mile Black Swap they would witness such a ridiculous scene occur. The entire Thunder Dominion along with the Temple of Marvels had been taken in by Lin Ming.

This was an absolute life-forbidden zone of the Sky Spill Planet that had existed for 100,000 years. And now, because of Lin Ming’s return, it had completely vanished in a single night.

The Sea of Miracles, also known as the Ocean of Endless Storms, had turned into a normal sea. This sort of strange phenomenon caused many Divine Sea powerhouses to be dazed for a long time, as if they were living in some sort of dream.

Lin Ming didn’t bother much with these dazed high level figures of the Sky Spill Planet. He simply politely greeted them and then brought Mu Qianyu, Lin Xiaoge, Qin Xingxuan, and Xiao Moxian to fly straight towards the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom.

The Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom was one of the four Divine Kingdoms of the Sky Spill Continent. With Lin Ming’s current cultivation his sense could already easily cover the entire Divine Kingdom.

He flew as fast as a bolt of lightning. In less than a quarter hour of time, he arrived above a grandiose jade palace. This was the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom’s imperial palace.

Lin Ming’s sense covered the entire imperial palace. Right after, his figure flashed as he fell straight down, followed by the others.

He landed in a courtyard.

The courtyard was quiet and tastefully decorated. Several species of spirit bamboo were planted, their fragrance warming the heart and mind.

In this courtyard, there was a middle-aged man sitting down at a stone table, brewing some tea in the shade. Lin Ming’s sudden arrival caused the man to be startled for a moment. Right after, a woman also heard the commotion and came outside. As she saw Lin Ming, she was inexplicably surprised.

Seeing this middle-aged man and woman, Lin Ming’s heart filled with emotion.

“Father, Mother, your son has returned to visit you…”

……

Since the last time Lin Ming returned, 70 years had passed in the blink of an eye.

Originally, Lin Ming once had the thought of bringing his parents up to the Divine Realm.

However, as he realized that the great calamity would soon erupt in the Divine Realm and the fate of humanity was also unknown, he decided it was better to have them stay in the lower realms where it would be relatively safer.

Lin Ming’s parents had already missed their chance to cultivate. He also didn’t have any desire to have his parents cultivate martial arts. Instead, what he could do was use a variety of heavenly materials to lengthen their lifespans to several thousands of years.

Thus, as Lin Ming saw his parents now, the two of them still looked like a husband and wife in their mid-thirties. Even the wrinkles on his mother’s face had vanished beneath the revitalization of so many heavenly materials.

After Lin Xiaoge ascended to the Divine Realm, Lin Ming’s parents also had another baby boy. This boy was Lin Ming and Lin Xiaoge’s little brother.

For these highly traditional parents, if they didn’t have their children and grandchildren around them, then even if they lived for several thousand years they would still feel lonely and empty within.

Even after 70 years passed, the Lin Family didn’t have many descendants. Even so, they were undoubtedly the number one family of the entire Sky Spill Planet. Whether it was Lin Ming’s parents of the descendants of their family, all of them had extraordinary statuses.

Currently, the Lin Family had developed to seven or eight people. At this speed, the Lin Family would soon grow into a flourishing family tree. As for Lin Ming’s parents, this was the happiest scene for them.

In particular, after the two parents met Xiao Moxian and learned she was carrying Lin Ming’s flesh and blood, they were even happier than before.

As for Xiao Moxian, she was a bit wary. She never imagined the scene would unfold this way when she met Lin Ming’s parents.

Xiao Moxian’s sense was extremely keen. She could clearly feel the abundant love and care coming from the gentle eyes of these two elders.

Then, she thought back to her grandfather. No matter when it was, Empyrean Demondawn had always maintained his dignity and grandeur. Although it was true that he loved Xiao Moxian, his love was deep and heavy, sometimes to the point of leaving her gasping for breath.

Such a contrast naturally had Xiao Moxian feel a heartfelt closeness towards Lin Ming’s parents.

As Lin Ming saw the smiles of his parents, his increasingly prosperous family, and also the respect and fear of the juniors, he felt comforted.

He increasingly realized just how great the burden on his shoulders was. Humanity had to cross the great calamity and survive no matter what; only then could such a peaceful happiness be sustained. Otherwise, if the Divine Realm perished it would only be a matter of time before disaster reached the lower realms.

In the Vermillion Bird Divine Kingdom, Lin Ming enjoyed a rare time of leisure and joy.

Besides only doing the necessary meditation every day, he would accompany his mother to discuss cooking recipes and play chess and brew tea with his father.

These days continued for a full month. Then, Lin Ming bid his farewells to his parents and embarked on his journey once again.

The day that Lin Ming returned to the Divine Realm, all of the Lin Family members and nearly all the Divine Sea powerhouses of the Sky Spill Continent, including many high level figures of all four Divine Kingdoms, gathered to see him off.

The scene was grand and even festive.

After all, in the eyes of many the Divine Realm was a land filled with lucky chances everywhere. But no one knew that as Lin Ming left this time, he was in truth shouldering a life or death mission for humanity. His journey was one that was doomed to be filled with incomparable perils…

“It’s time…”

Lin Ming looked towards Xiao Moxian, Mu Qianyu, Qin Xingxuan, and also Lin Xiaoge who was still crying in her mother’s arms. He took out Primordius Heavenly Palace and all of them flew inside. Right after, they broke through the void and flew straight to the Divine Realm…

……..

After Lin Ming returned to the Divine Realm he flew towards Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. Empyrean Divine Dream was already waiting for him.

“You’ve finished your matters?” Empyrean Divine Dream looked towards Lin Ming and her thoughts stirred. She could faintly feel that after leaving for just over a month, Lin Ming’s aura had become even more intense than before.

“I’ve finished.”

“Mm. Then, let us go...”

After Empyrean Divine Dream finished speaking, a beam of light covered Lin Ming. Without using a spirit ship, the two of them simply stepped through space.

If they didn’t use a spirit ship, that also meant the entrance to the Soul World wasn’t too far away from Divine Dream Heavenly Palace. Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by this. The entrance to the Soul World was far too important and it was natural that Empyrean Divine Dream would want to protect it. When she was choosing the area to establish Divine Dream Heavenly Palace she likely considered the entrance to the Soul World first.

“Take this…”

Empyrean Divine Dream gave Lin Ming an ancient transmission symbol. Strange runes were engraved atop it, and Lin Ming was in fact quite familiar with these runes – they were Asura Law runes.

“This is the transmission symbol I obtained from the Asura Road in the past. It will protect you in the transmission.”

“Mm, I understand.” Lin Ming probed the transmission symbol with his sense and soon understood how to use it.

At this time, Empyrean Divine Dream had brought Lin Ming to a place where space was completely twisted. In this space, she continually used arcane space techniques, seemingly shuttling through the complex space labyrinth.

This space route was incredibly puzzling. If there wasn’t someone leading the way, then even for Lin Ming it would take an immense amount of time to find the way out.

He also had no idea how Divine Dream had arrived here in the past.

“Perhaps she had some sort of jade slip map…”

As Lin Ming was thinking, he discovered that along the way he could make out some ancient array formation ruins and even the skeletons of the dead.

Lin Ming didn’t know who these skeletons had once been. If they were truly characters from billions of years ago, that was truly shocking.

These skeletons had managed to be preserved here for billions of years without turning into dust. From this alone, one could imagine the cultivations they possessed when they were alive.

But these powerful existences had all perished here. Just what was the reason for that?

“Here it is.”

Empyrean Divine Dream stopped. In front of her and Lin Ming was an ancient altar.

This altar was covered with mottled lines. After so many years passed, no matter how powerful an array formation was it would still slowly weaken until it completely faded.

This transmission array before him clearly wouldn’t last for much longer.

Lin Ming stood before the altar, feeling its vast and ancient aura. The dust here had fallen into a thick layer. As he stepped into it, the dust covered his foot.

Lin Ming slowly approached the altar, mounting the steps one at a time.

When he reached the top of the altar and saw what was there, he was shocked.

It turned out that the middle of the altar was hollow. As he looked down into the altar all he could see was a fathomless abyss, an abyss that had no light and no bottom. It was unknown just what was inside.

Lin Ming tried to probe it with his sense but discovered that as he sent his sense inside, it was difficult to take back. His heart chilled. He finally realized that this abyss was not some ordinary pit, but a place that was constantly flooded with a fierce and violent power of space.

This meant that the abyss itself led to a different space.

And the abyss itself was the space channel!

In other words, this was the entrance to the Soul World!

This was also the so-called weak point of the God Lamenting Wall that Empyrean Divine Dream had mentioned. An ancient True Divinity had forcefully established a connection between the two universes and turned that connection into a transmission array. Even so, for what reason had the ancient True Divinity created this transmission array?

“Lin Ming, is this really what you have decided? At the other end of this abyss is the Soul World, but the runes of the transmission array have become incredibly frail, on the verge of collapse. I have no idea how much more energy it can withstand, and the transmission array itself hasn’t been used for tens of millions of years. If you wish to go to the Soul World, it will be far more perilous then when I used this transmission array in the past.

“Moreover, even if you go to the Soul World it is unknown what you can accomplish. It's also unknown whether you can find Sheng Mei or even form an alliance with her…”

Empyrean Divine Dream shook her head. Although she hoped that humanity could form an alliance with the spiritas, probability and common sense didn’t favor them.

What could Lin Ming offer that would tempt the heart of Sheng Mei?

If humanity was compared to the spiritas, then humanity was just far too weak.

Lin Ming stood before the abyss for a long time, silently probing the transmission array. Using his own knowledge of array formations he constantly calculated the risks involved.

Then, Lin Ming slowly drifted upwards. He looked towards Empyrean Divine Dream and said, “I humbly request Senior Divine Dream to please take care of my family. I must go to the spiritas no matter what, regardless of what the result will be…”

As Lin Ming spoke these words, he turned towards the black fathomless abyss and leapt down…

Mysteries of the Akashic Dream Battlefield

Chapter 1793 – Dreamsoul Heaven

Cardinal Sky World was one of the larger great worlds within Dreamsoul Heaven’s 3600 great worlds.

The main continent of Cardinal Sky World was an incredibly vast area, but most of the land here was covered by snow and ice at all times, similar to the Snowfall World within the Divine Realm.

Because of the snow that covered the entire world, many martial artists of Cardinal Sky World cultivated the power of ice. Of course, they were different from humans. Spiritas lived here and they communed with the Ice Laws through soul force. Moreover, their Ice Laws were used to supplement the effects of their soul attacks, making them strange and nearly impossible to defend against.

In Cardinal Sky World existed a large influence called Zenith Palace. Zenith Palace didn’t have many disciples, but they had produced extraordinary individuals since time immemorial and were a highly reputed sect.

At this time, at the outside edges of Zenith Palace, wind and snow drifted about, making the entire landscape misty. A group of Zenith Palace disciples were exploring an ice field. There were over 20 disciples; half of them were women and half were men.

The one in the lead was a white-browed old man. Beside him followed a peerless woman. She wore white clothes and her face was hooded by a veil. Her temperament was ethereal, like a blooming ice lotus.

“High Master, I don’t know if the previous intelligence was accurate… we’ve searched for several days already but haven’t found any traces of the hornless ice dragon.”

The bloodline of a hornless ice dragon was inferior to that of a True Dragon but it was still a peerless spirit beast. A hornless ice dragon was an absolutely important creature. If an influence could obtain it and raise it into their guardian God Beast, the advantages could be imagined.

The old man shook his head, “We’ve only been speculating. Several days ago, north of Zenith Palace, the power of space suddenly turned chaotic and the cold energy there increased, even affecting the land for 10,000 miles. The Palace Master has an extremely sharp sense. According to what we know, an existence that can stir the Space and Ice Laws as well as possess such momentum should likely be a hornless ice dragon…”

Seeing the woman still frowning with doubts as if this explanation didn’t seem too likely, the old man smiled and said, “This sort of lucky chance can only be found through a stroke of fate. Even if we do find the hornless ice dragon it’s not necessarily true that we can subdue it. This sort of spirit beast might not be willing to surrender itself to our sect, and if it doesn’t then that will be extremely troublesome.”

As the old man spoke, a disciple suddenly spoke up, “If we can’t subdue then we can kill it and use it for alchemy! The medicines produced from a spirit beast like a hornless ice dragon must surely be the most precious kinds!”

However, the disciple’s opinion caused the old man to maliciously glare at him, “You damned bastard idiot, do you know how much good fortune of the world has to gather and for destiny to accumulate over time for such a divine being to be bred? How could you dare think of killing it for alchemy? That will only draw disaster upon our sect!”

As the old man reprimanded, the disciple shrunk back, not saying a word.

Many martial artists possessed an incredible strength that could shake the heavens and earth, but they also held onto a firm faith of destiny, karma, and samsara. Many of these martial artists wouldn’t want to do something that could harm their own destiny.

“Look, the glacier in front of us has been destroyed again…”

The old man pointed at a glacier not too far away. This glacier had originally been massive but it had been sheared in half by something. The top had completely vanished.

This situation couldn’t be considered too amazing. The old man from Zenith Palace could easily accomplish this, but to encounter this same situation again and again for the entire surrounding 10,000 miles was out of the ordinary.

Just where would there be such a strong person that was so bored they would shear off the tops of a million glaciers for 10,000 miles just for fun? That would just be a great joke.

The veiled woman nodded. This didn’t resemble the actions of a martial artist, but a vicious beast experiencing heavenly tribulation, nirvana, or some other similar phenomena, and then leaving behind these traces during their furious struggle for survival.

As she was thinking this, not too far away a disciple cried out in alarm.

“Mm? Did you discover the trail of the hornless ice dragon?”

The sect Elder’s heart stirred. If the hornless ice dragon was present there would surely be some more movement than this. If they could just find a scale of the hornless ice dragon, that would be wonderful progress.

Everyone hurried over. All they saw was a female disciple that looked around 17-18 years old staring and pointing at a bulge in the snow. She said, “There’s someone buried there…”

“Person?”

The old man was disappointed upon hearing this. He shook his head with the peerless woman beside him. In the Great Desolate Glacier it was common to find the corpses of those who died here. It might be a mortal who had perished from the cold or starvation, or even a martial artist who fell here. Every year countless lives were lost within the Great Desolate Glacier, and many of them were forever buried beneath the snow, sealed for eternity.

“It's just a dead person. There’s no need to make such a fuss about it.”

Someone admonished the young girl who cried out in alarm.

The female disciple looked a bit aggrieved. She said, “I thought it was a corpse without any life force, but then I saw his finger move.”

“Mm? He’s still living?”

The old man was amazed. The veiled woman was also startled. She said, “Rescue him from there!”

Several disciples hastily dug out the snow, revealing a pale young man.

“It’s a young man, he looks around 20 years old and he really is alive..”

The veiled woman was astonished. The youth wasn’t breathing but his blood vitality was still running through him, and it didn’t seem weak either.

However, he seemed to have been injured by something so his state was a bit messy. It was impossible to see what his cultivation was.

“Bring him back to the spirit ship and give him some medicines. Whether or not he can continue living will depend on his good fortune.”

The veiled woman ordered. Then, she continued with the others to search for the hornless ice dragon.

Several days ago, the massive space storm that swept out for 10,000 miles had even changed the surrounding climate. In the eyes of Zenith Palace, even if it wasn’t a hornless ice dragon there should be some rare treasure being born.

Since they came here with such fanfare, they might as well return with some harvests.

…….

Several maids brought the freezing youth to a room. They acted according to the orders of the veiled woman and fed him medicines, attending to him with the utmost care.

“Miss and the Twelfth Elder are too kind to rescue this unknown person. Who knows if he is a good or bad person? Maybe he did something extremely evil and was only reaping the consequences of his actions.”

“That might be true, but why would our Zenith Palace fear any evil people? In the entire Cardinal Sky World there isn’t a single influence that dares to move against us…”

The two maids spoke. They were certainly annoyed at having to care for an unknown youth.

“Zenith Palace… Cardinal Sky World… this should be the Soul World…”

Lin Ming thought to himself.

The youth that Zenith Palace rescued was the recently arrived Lin Ming.

The truth was that for these last several days he had been lying in the snow and wind. Although it seemed as if he was in a coma, he knew what was happening around him with absolute clarity.

He also saw the scene of the old man and veiled woman ‘rescuing’ him.

In fact, without these people ‘rescuing’ him, he would have recovered in a few days anyways.

As Lin Ming recalled the space storms he encountered when travelling from the Divine Realm to the Soul World, he still felt a lingering sense of fear. That had been an utterly terrifying journey, one that had far surpassed anything Empyrean Divine Dream had estimated possible.

Otherwise Empyrean Divine Dream would never have allowed Lin Ming to take such a risk.

Not even Lin Ming had thought such dangers were possible.

Initially, Lin Ming was able to use his own strength to deal with the space storms; this wasn’t too difficult. Lin Ming’s cultivation of Laws was extraordinarily profound. He had already practiced using the least amount of energy possible to display the maximum effect.

However, the transmission array had decayed for far too long; it was already weakened to the point of ruin.

When Lin Ming was halfway through the transmission journey, the fallout of energy shockwaves had just happened to strike upon a weak point in the space channel.

Although these energy shockwaves weren’t too strong, them hitting a weak point caused a crack to appear in the space channel.

As this crack appeared, it was like the widening maw of a death god, leaving Lin Ming in a cold sweat.

With that, the space storms became even more crazy and fierce. This was the annihilation storm that existed in the gap between two universes. Once one was struck by it, flesh and blood would melt away and all things would be destroyed without even dust remaining.

Lin Ming had struggled with everything he had and was forced to use more and more strength. This caused the already cracked space channel to repeatedly expand!

Lin Ming hastened his speed. He had to rush out of the exit before the entire space channel collapsed.

But in the end, he hadn’t been able to make it in time. Just as Lin Ming was close to the exit, the entire space channel began to cave in on itself.

This caused Lin Ming to take desperate action. He summoned Primordius Heavenly Palace.

The summoning of Primordius Heavenly Palace meant the appearance of an Empyrean level strength. This caused the space channel to collapse even quicker. Although Lin Ming entered Primordius Heavenly Palace, the power of that horrifying space storm still gushed out from the space channel like a mighty torrent, wildly attacking the shields of Primordius Heavenly Palace and rapidly consuming its energy.

In the end, even the energy of the shields had been completely exhausted. Although Lin Ming was hidden within Primordius Heavenly Palace, he had to face the direct baptism of the space storm!

No matter how high Lin Ming’s cultivation was, having to withstand the strong astral winds that existed in the gap between two universes was impossible for him. He was swept out, receiving severe wounds that caused him to vomit blood and his meridians were also torn apart.

In the final moments, Lin Ming received the extremely damaged Primordius Heavenly Palace and then summoned Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s Temple of Marvels. Only with the Temple of Marvels’ final bastion of support was Lin Ming just barely able to make it out of the exit.

But at the end, even the Temple of Marvels had been depleted of energy and it also lost a great deal of its spirituality. It was clear from this just how terrifying the space storms that existed in the gap between two universes were.

This was a power that not even an Empyrean could contend with. Only a True Divinity could sacrifice a part of their cultivation and break through the barriers of the God Lamenting Wall.

When the energy of the Temple of Marvels was depleted, Lin Ming was heavily wounded yet again. He grit his teeth and broke into the Soul World. But when he entered the Soul World, a space storm spread out for 10,000 miles, causing destruction everywhere. A million glaciers had been blown apart and instantly evaporated. Luckily, no one had been in this part of the Great Desolate Glacier, otherwise countless lives would have been lost.

In one trip, the energy of two Empyrean spirit treasures had been used up. Without a long period of allowing them to repair and also supplying them with energy, these two Empyrean spirit treasures wouldn’t be able to be used for some time.

But this wasn’t a problem at all. These spirit treasures could be slowly nourished back to their original state. The crux of the problem here was that Lin Ming had received heavy wounds.

This left Lin Ming feeling bitter. His adventure to the Soul World hadn’t gotten off to a good start…

Chapter 1795 – Akashic Dream Battlefield

“Zenith Palace is searching for the hornless ice dragon to subdue it and make it their guardian beast?” Lin Ming thoughtlessly asked, not expecting the young maid to know anything.

The young maid nodded and said, “Yes, but the most important reason is because they wish to have the hornless ice dragon fight in the Akashic Dream Battlefield…”

Akashic Dream Battlefield?

Lin Ming was startled. He never imagined this young maid would know such information. Just what sort of place was this Akashic Dream Battlefield? Could it be the spiritas’ battlefield against the saints?

Lin Ming earnestly wanted to know just what the current situation was between the saints and the spiritas.

As he was thinking about it, the young maid asked with some envy in her voice, “Sir, if you can survive that terrifying storm, your cultivation should be quite fierce… could… could you be a Life Destruction martial artist?”

The young girl originally wanted to say Revolving Core, but she thought this young man should be a little better, and thus she asked him if he was at Life Destruction.

In her eyes, if Lin Ming could reach Life Destruction at such a young age then that was already extraordinary.

In the future there would be high hopes that he could break into the Divine Sea, Divine Transformation, or even Divine Lord realm. To humanity, this was a rare level of talent.

As she spoke she peeked at Lin Ming’s expression and discovered that he didn’t seem to be denying it at all. To her, this immediately confirmed her speculations. This youth was indeed a fierce young man.

Looking at the girl’s expression, Lin Ming felt a bit sad. He thought back to how humanity was said to have once been one of the three great races of the 33 Heavens and was incomparably glorious. Billions of years ago, there appeared many unrivalled heroes like Empyrean Divine Seal.

Even in present times with their inheritances severed and the hopes of reaching True Divinity nearly suffocated to death, there were still peerless masters that appeared like Emperor Shakya, Empyrean Primordius, and Empyrean Divine Dream. These characters were all just a single step away from stepping into the realm of True Divinity.

But now, in the Soul World, they had fallen to such depths.

This was because humans here lacked confidence in themselves.

Once a race lost all belief in their own strength, then there was only a single fate left for them – to be slaves.

However, Lin Ming couldn’t blame this on the humans of the Soul World, because this was an environment created for them that they were born in.

Lin Ming lightly sighed. Looking at the young maid before him, he could see that her road of martial arts would be long and rough. He took pity on her and took out a pill bottle from his spatial ring.

The pills in this bottle were those used by low level martial artists. To the current Lin Ming they were of no use and there was no reason for him to hold on to them.

He kept these pills in his ring because he planned to give them to his juniors as a greeting gift during the times he returned to the Sky Spill Continent.

However, even though these were pills for junior martial artists, with Lin Ming’s current level of vision they were still priceless medicines that these low level martial artists could only obtain through a stroke of fate.

“This is for you.”

Lin Ming passed over the pill bottle.

“This is…”

The young maid took the pill bottle in a daze and blankly opened it. A heartwarming fragrance spread out. Without a doubt, these were all top quality pills that Lin Ming had given her.

“This is too precious…”

The young maid was at a loss. But at this time, the door opened and two young girls walked in.

The young maid was shocked. She quickly put away the pill bottle in fear that it would be seen.

“Eh, you’re awake?”

The two maids casually said as they looked at Lin Ming.

These two maids were both spiritas and their cultivations were equal to a human Xiantian realm martial artist. Compared to the young human maid, they were considerably stronger.

It was obvious they also had a high status amongst the maids. The human maid appeared meek and cautious in front of them.

Lin Ming remembered the voices of these two spiritas maids; they had been the ones complaining about being ordered to take care of him.

“Since you’ve awoken, follow us. Miss wishes to see you.”

“Oh.” Lin Ming nodded. Since he had just arrived at the Soul World there were many things he didn’t understand. How to find Sheng Mei, what the situation was between the spiritas and the saints – he was completely in the dark about all of this. Not just that, but he was even wounded at the moment. His best route would be to find a considerably large influence to stay at for a little while and unravel his current conundrums before leaving again.

Thus, Lin Ming didn’t refuse the summons of this ‘Miss’ at all. After he rose, he spread out his sense like a web.

He discovered that he was within an ice spirit ship. When everyone in the ship including the maids was counted, there were just several hundred people. It seemed that this was a team that Zenith Palace had temporarily sent out to look for the hornless ice dragon.

On the spirit ship, the strongest ones were the old man and the veiled woman.

The woman had an elegant temperament and was a beauty. Her skin was fair and her two eyes were icy blue, seeming to be as smooth as crystal jade.

And sitting beside her was a 50-60 year old looking white-robed old man. He had a benign appearance and his aura was restrained.

At this time, these two people were talking about something.

They didn’t lay down any sound-insulating enchantments thus the content of their conversation all fell into Lin Ming’s ears.

Although Lin Ming was injured, his soul and the intensity of his divine sense hadn’t been affected. He could easily spy upon these two people talking without any worries of being discovered.

“Elder White, it doesn’t seem that we can find this hornless ice dragon. Perhaps we were mistaken, or perhaps the hornless ice dragon has already dug through the glacier and escaped. Either way, it will be increasingly difficult for us in the sect wars a month from now. Currently our sect is accumulating battle merit points at a worryingly slow rate. If this continues our situation will be troublesome.”

“Mm… a year ago our Zenith Palace was nearly completely annihilated in the Akashic Dream Universe. Besides you and Jadehall, the other disciples did horribly. On average they all received less than ten merit points. Even amongst influences of the same rank this is too embarrassing. I fear that if this continues, we won’t be assigned many resources from Cardinal Sky World…”

As Elder White and the veiled woman spoke, Lin Ming had a strange complexion on his face.

Zenith Palace was nearly ‘annihilated’ in the Akashic Dream Universe?

Then could the people searching for the hornless ice dragon be ghosts or something?

Naturally, none of this made sense. But slowly, the more Lin Ming listened, the more guesses he had. These guesses caused his heart to leap into his throat. He anxiously wanted to confirm them.

“Hey, make sure you don’t let your eyes just wander about. The one you’re about to see is the direct disciple of our Zenith Palace Master, Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver, someone who possesses a postnatal spiritual ice body. Although Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver currently has the status of a disciple, she is already treated on the same level as an Elder. In the future she might even become the next Zenith Palace Master. Do you have any idea just what kind of concept the Zenith Palace Master is?”

The young maid looked at Lin Ming’s listless expression. With his stupid appearance she was afraid he would randomly cause a ruckus with the high level figures of Zenith Palace, thus she gave him a warning.

Lin Ming couldn’t be bothered arguing with this kind of maid. His eyebrows arched up and he asked, “Is Zenith Palace a World King influence?”

After investigating that Elder White’s cultivation just now, he should be a half-step World King. If so, then he could infer from this that the Zenith Palace Master was most likely a World King. Moreover, it was possible that Zenith Palace had more than one World King. On a great world, such an influence was considered not too shabby.

“That’s right!”

The young maid looked at Lin Ming with surprise. She didn’t expect this fellow to know that much.

“Miss, I’ve brought the human here.”

Another maid notified the veiled woman.

This veiled woman’s thoughts stirred. She paused the conversation she was having with the old man.

“You’ve already rescued this human, but instead of having him leave, you summoned him here? Are you hoping to learn news of the hornless ice dragon from him?” Elder White shook his head, clearly not thinking Lin Ming would have any valuable information.

“Not only that. I just think that this person has a formidable blood vitality and his inner world is also extraordinary. It’s a bit strange to me. Perhaps he is some amazing character…”

As the veiled woman said this, the old man was about to respond but eventually didn’t and shook his head instead.

By now, Lin Ming had already walked into the room.

The room wasn’t too large but the décor was extremely unique and wonderful. There were ice crystal objects everywhere and abundant spiritual energy filled the room. The chairs that the veiled woman and Elder White sat on were crafted from ice jade. A faint mist dissipated from them. It was clear they weren’t ordinary treasures.

As Lin Ming entered the room, the veiled woman bid the maid pour Lin Ming a cup of spirit tea and then waved for him to take a seat.

“Sir, may I know your name?”

“My name is Lin Muk.”

Lin Ming casually made up a name.

“Ah, then it is Sir Lin. Sir Lin, for what reason did you come to the Great Desolate Glacier? And why were you injured?”

As the veiled woman asked this question her eyes stared at Lin Ming, as if she wanted to completely understand his cultivation.

With Lin Ming’s severely wounded state, his cultivation seemed to be between the Divine Sea and Divine Lord realm.

Lin Ming said, “I will answer all of Miss’s questions. But before that, I have some questions of my own that I hope Miss can cast light on.”

“Oh? What questions does Sir Lin have?”

Lin Ming said, “I am someone from the wilds. I’ve been training with my master since I was a child and just recently left his protection, so I know nothing of the outside world. As I was adventuring through the world I heard someone mention the Akashic Dream Battlefield and that sects of the Soul World would be engaging in sect wars within this place. May I ask what this Akashic Dream Battlefield is?”

Lin Ming guessed, and rightfully so, that his question sounded extremely stupid and might even rouse the suspicions of this Miss. After all, if this was something that even a young maid knew then it should be common knowledge.

However, he couldn’t care about this much. After all, in a mere World King influence like this there was no need to have too many scruples.

With his regenerative abilities, although his current wounds were serious they wouldn’t take too long to recover from.

And indeed, that veiled woman looked at Lin Ming with surprise, “You haven’t heard of the Akashic Dream Universe?”

Lin Ming shook his head.

“Your master actually never told you about this…” The veiled woman thought this was bizarre. Although Lin Ming had said he was someone who lived in the wild mountains and had never left before, still, his master should have taught him such common knowledge.

“The Akashic Dream Universe is a dreamland universe shared by all people of the Soul World. There, everyone exists in the form of soul energy. This universe is broad and boundless and covers all seven Heavens that make up the Soul World. From any place within the Soul World’s seven universes, one can use their own spiritual sea to connect to the Akashic Dream Universe.

“In the Akashic Dream Universe, a martial artist’s cultivation, strength, Laws, everything will be copied over exactly as in reality, and this even includes weapons and pills. If two martial artists fight in the Akashic Dream Universe, that is no different from them fighting in the outside world…”

As the veiled woman explained this, Lin Ming’s heart shook.

In truth, he had already faintly guessed what was happening.

This Akashic Dream Universe was in truth similar to the Divine Dream World that Empyrean Divine Dream had arranged for use in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting.

But, the Akashic Dream Universe was countless times larger than the Divine Dream World!

The number of martial artists that the Akashic Dream Universe could hold was trillions and quadrillions times more than the Divine Dream World!

“The spiritas actually had such a place…”

Lin Ming sucked in a breath of cold air. He was well aware of just how significant it was for an entire race to possess this sort of universe!

Chapter 1797 – Dispute

“Hand it over, otherwise we’ll mess you up!”

A cold girl’s voice sounded out. Her words had a bullying tone to them.

At this time, in the maidservants’ room, three beautiful young girls were holding their arms against their waists as they surrounded a small and weak 15-16 year old looking girl.

This young girl was pale and her fists were tightly clenched together. She subconsciously guarded her chest, clearly indicating just how much fear she was feeling right now.

“You lowly slut, delay any further and we’ll kill you! Hurry up and hand it over! When we entered the room we saw you panic and hide the pill bottle and we even smelled the medicinal fragrance. Don’t try to deny it!”

These three beautiful young girls were all spiritas maids. The young human girl they were bullying was the maid that Lin Ming had given a bottle of pills to.

To Lin Ming, these pills didn’t have any use at all. But to these young maids who were still struggling at the Houtian or Xiantian realm, these medicines were incomparably precious treasures.

When these maids had entered Lin Ming’s room they had smelled the light medicinal fragrance and were able to discern just how precious these pills were. They were definitely pills that could nourish one’s energy and soul. Whether it was for a human or a spiritas, they were highly beneficial.

Thus, they began to form thoughts of stealing them. However, they naturally couldn’t reveal these thoughts in front of Lin Ming, after all, even though Lin Ming was only a mere human, he seemed to be a martial artist at the Life Destruction realm or above and they were not his match. But now that these pills had fallen into the hands of this young girl, the situation was different.

One couldn’t only look at the demeanor that these spiritas maids adopted in front of their superiors; normally, they arrogantly rampaged around. The human maids were instead the ones forced to wash their clothes and do other tasks.

“Hurry up! Those pills aren’t something that a low class human like you should have!”

The maid with the highest status amongst the three, and also the leader of the maids, grabbed onto the young girl’s collar and slapped her face repeatedly. Her tone was threatening as she said, “So you want to do this the hard way, right? Be careful or I might rip your face off!”

The head maid began to pinch the young girl’s cheeks and slowly twisted the skin into a circle. Even as the head maid smiled, the young girl’s face was already twisted red.

The young girl held back her tears. She forcefully opened her eyes, not allowing any tears to fall or showing any pain. She clenched her fists and grit her teeth, saying, “This is something that the young sir gave me, it is not yours!”

“Haha! You little slut, you must have formed a crush on that human and thought that he would take you in as his concubine, right? Just who do you think you are? Take a good look at yourself in the mirror! You’re nothing but an inferior human maid, even if you died no one would care! If you died we would simply toss you off the side of the ship like we would a dead dog! Let alone you, even that ‘sir’ you speak of is only some human that was found frozen outside! Although he might be considered a master amongst us, in Zenith Palace amongst the Elders, Protectors and core disciples, he is just a dog!”

The maid shoved the young girl over.

The young girl wobbled and fell to the floor. Her head hit the wall behind her with a thick thumping sound.

The young maid had started cultivating the essence gathering system before training in the six stages of body transformation. Because of that, this strike caused her sight to blur. Even so, she grasped her fists and didn’t say a single word.

In this universe where spiritas ruled, it was common for humans to be discriminated against and bullied. This young girl was clearly aware that strength was everything.

Because she was weak, she could only allow herself to be pushed around like this.

For a young human girl to be killed by others and have her treasures stolen, that was a commonplace scene.

But now, she had managed to seize an opportunity with these medicines that the young sir had gifted to her. This allowed her to see the light of hope for making a breakthrough. How could she give up this chance and resign herself to her fate?

Perhaps in her entire life, this would be the only chance for her to crawl onto her feet and walk as a proud human.

“Ho! What a stubborn bitch! I can take it from you whether you want to or not, but if I do then your fate will be miserable!”

The head maid sneered as she spoke.

And at this time, another young maid said, “There’s nothing in her ring!”

As the maid spoke, she grabbed an extremely low quality spatial ring from the young girl’s finger and crumbled it. From inside fell out a pile of clothes, ordinary weapons, and some medicinal herbs.

These were the entirety of the young human girl’s possessions.

The head maid crushed these inferior medicinal herbs beneath her feet, jeering as she said, “Then she must be hiding them on her body. It’s impossible for her to have the time to refine such high quality pills or to swallow them all in one go. Tear apart her clothes until she’s naked. We’ll slowly look for what we’re searching for.”

“Okay!”

As the other two maids spoke she rushed forwards and began to pull the young girl’s clothes. With a ripping sound, part of her clothes tore apart, revealing her bellyband.

“Ahh!”

The young girl screamed out loud. But, the two maids’ actions became even more fervent.

“I found it!”

A young maid raised a pill bottle. After opening it, several jade-green, bean-sized pills rolled out.

“What great pills! Are these Blue Miracle Pills or something else? It seems that almost frozen human’s wealth isn’t too poor!” The maids laughed and looked towards that young girl.

“Finish her up. Tear off all her clothes and lash her!”

As the head maid spoke, she felt a sudden chill rush over her, causing her heart to skip a beat. She quickly leapt backwards and turned around in midair.

“Who!?”

The three maids were immediately vigilant. They discovered that a man had appeared behind them. This man’s face was dark and was emitting a thick killing intent.

“It’s you!”

The maids naturally recognized Lin Ming. However, they weren’t afraid of him. In this spirit ship there wasn’t anything that Lin Ming could do to them.

“Sir!”

At this time, the young girl cried out as she saw Lin Ming appear. Sadness, injustice, grief, all sorts of feelings rushed up in her chest before they came out as scalding tears in her eyes. Her knees seemed to give out as she tumbled over like a broken kite.

Her pills were taken and her clothes were torn; there was nothing in her heart but shame.

“You’re fine…”

Lin Ming suddenly said. He didn’t know what he was feeling in his heart. He had only crossed paths with this young girl once and didn’t even know her name, but right now, because of her bitter and painful experiences, he felt nothing but anger for her!

The reason might be because they were both from the human race. From this young girl’s bitter experiences he was able to see the future of the Divine Realm. This was the sorrow of a race that had their lands fall into enemy hands.

“You want to save this little slut? I never imagined you would be interested in such trash. Fine, to show you some face, we won’t press this issue anymore.”

As the head maid spoke, she received the pills.

The maids simply didn’t fear Lin Ming’s threats at all. Even if Lin Ming was strong, he was nothing but a mere human. This was a spiritas spirit ship; just what could he do here?

“You are courting death!”

Just as Lin Ming said these words, he took great strides forwards and punched out, smashing the head maid in the face!

Peng!

With a dull thump, the maid screamed out loud as she hurtled backwards and smashed into a wall, vomiting a great mouthful of blood.

“You… you hit me…”

The head maid said as she spat out blood. Her teeth had been knocked out and her face was filled with disbelief.

The other two maids were stunned. They never imagined that Lin Ming would be so reckless to attack them on this spirit ship.

“As well as you two!”

Lin Ming unfolded his arms like an eagle opening its wings. The two young maids were unable to put up even the slightest bit of resistance as they were smashed backwards. They screamed out loud and vomited mouthfuls of blood.

This was the first time that Lin Ming had struck women who weren’t able to fight back at all, and where he also didn’t show them mercy.

With the premise that he didn’t take their lives, he tore apart their meridians. With a low level martial artist’s restorative abilities, it would take at least a month of recuperation before they healed from this.

Pa!

Lin Ming flicked his finger and the head maid’s spatial ring exploded. He took back the pill bottle he had originally given the young girl.

These pills didn’t have any value to Lin Ming to begin with. But, he would rather feed them to dogs than give them to these three spiritas maids.

“Insolence! How dare you!”

At this time, a man’s icy voice resounded in the air. Lin Ming frowned. He knew that someone had been monitoring him the entire time. Now that he wounded someone, the people from Zenith Palace would immediately know of this.

He calmly untied his outer robe and draped it over the ragged young human girl.

The young girl grabbed onto Lin Ming’s hand, alarmed.

With that shout of ‘insolence’, she immediately understood that a high level spiritas had arrived. It was likely Lin Ming would be sucked into a mess because of her actions.

“Sir…”

The young girl’s eyes were filled with guilt. In this situation, Lin Ming would definitely suffer a loss.

“Put on some clothes first.”

Lin Ming calmly said. Then, he slowly turned around. Behind him, a youth with red eyebrows walked in. This youth was thin and had freezing cold eyes. His temperament seemed as if his entire being was carved by an ice saber and his cultivation was at the late Soul Lord realm.

As the red eyebrow youth appeared, the three spiritas maids perked up as if they saw their savior. They all cried and crawled over to him.

“Lord Yi, find justice for us!”

The several maids sobbed, their tears overflowing.

That Senior-apprentice Brother Yi looked over the injuries of the three spiritas maids. Then, his expression became increasingly cold. “You ride my ship and yet strike my people. Just who gave you the courage to do this?”

“You want to fight?”

Lin Ming frostily said, not wanting to drag things on. It was true that he was injured but a skinny camel was still larger than a horse. To deal with this unimportant figure in front of him wouldn’t take any effort at all.

It was just that if he were to fight with this Senior-apprentice Brother Yi, there was no way he could continue to stay at Zenith Palace. Currently, Lin Ming still wasn’t able to contend with the peak masters of Zenith Palace; his wounds left him unable to fully call upon the energy in his inner world.

“Hahaha! Did I hear correctly?”

Senior-apprentice Brother Yi loudly laughed. “You actually asked if I want to fight? You aren’t my match! You can’t even see through my boundary, all I would need is my little finger to crush you to death!”

Senior-apprentice Brother Yi coldly sneered, readying himself to attack. But at this time, from not too far away, an old man walked up and whispered something in his ears.

Senior-apprentice Brother Yi’s red eyebrows wrinkled. “What? This human garbage was chosen by Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver?”

“Yes, Miss believes that his talent is adequate and wants to borrow him to further perfect her virtual dantian. Thus it would be best if you don’t injure him, otherwise it will be hard to explain the situation to the Miss.”

As the old man spoke, he looked at Lin Ming and disdainfully said, “Consider yourself lucky this time! Next time I will make sure you walk around without any teeth.”

Chapter 1798 – Akashic Dream Battlefield Opens

The red eyebrow youth called Senior-apprentice Brother Yi walked away. The other three spiritas maids also stood up in a panic and hurried behind him, silently enduring the pain from having their meridians torn by Lin Ming.

Lin Ming didn’t stop these people from leaving. Originally, he had already expected that the status of humans wasn’t too good in the Soul World, and the reason the veiled woman from before was so polite to him was because she needed his help and also because of her personality. She was someone who had stood at the top for a long time and had developed a sense of deep superiority in her heart. She didn’t need to show disdain or contempt in her words to improve her own status.

But those people with slightly lower status were different. In front of their lords and masters they were timid and polite, but in front of others they blustered about.

“Get up…”

Lin Ming stretched out a hand and pulled up the young maid.

“I’m sorry…” The young maid quietly murmured as she bit her lips. She felt as if she had needlessly sucked Lin Ming into her problems.

“It’s no problem… what is your name?”

“My name is Wanyue.” The young maid whispered.

“Mm.” Lin Ming nodded and returned the pills that were taken from her. Thinking about it a bit more, Lin Ming added on another bottle of pills. Then, without paying attention to the young maid’s refusals he turned and left.

He needed to maximize his time to restore his strength.

His wounds would need several days before they could fully recover. Until Lin Ming was restored to his peak state he would find it difficult to remain tranquil.

Like this, Lin Ming rested in the spirit ship until they arrived at Zenith Palace.

Zenith Palace was located atop a million foot high snowy mountain.

And in the surrounding mountain range, there were areas swathed in array formations. In these areas, spirit springs gushed up and lush grass grew abundantly. All sorts of rare world treasures bloomed, making this land seem like a fairytale.

Witnessing this scene, Lin Ming wasn’t impressed at all. He had already seen places that were hundreds of times more beautiful.

“This is your residential area.”

Someone said to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming looked at the human residential area of Zenith Palace. There was no array formation here thus the buildings were wrapped in a world of ice and snow. Of course, to a martial artist this level of cold wasn’t much at all.

This living area had a richness of spiritual energy that was only a tenth of what the highest peak had.

Lin Ming wasn’t surprised by such a scene. In this bitter cold, to lay down a spiritual energy-gathering array formation that worked all year round would consume a considerable amount of resources.

In this area there were many human martial artists; most of them came from the surrounding regions of Zenith Palace and they stayed here to cultivate. Sometimes they would be summoned to the peak of Zenith Palace so that the Zenith Palace Master could observe their inner world.

In this land, the best dwellings had been occupied by others already.

Lin Ming casually chose a residence. This was a mansion, and although it was large in size the furnishings were barren and simple and the spiritual energy here was barren.

Lin Ming didn’t care for these details. As soon as he entered he began meditating.

As for that young maid Wanyue, she also lived in this area. She voluntarily chose to stay in Lin Ming’s palace and help tend to his daily needs.

The days passed in peace.

In this snowy area, very few people came, making it seem a bit lonely.

Lin Ming was glad for this. In these past days, his wounds had been rapidly recovering.

At the same time he also studied the inheritance left behind by Empyrean Thunder Punishment.

The current Lin Ming had no lack of top grade cultivation methods. Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s inheritance could only be considered a superior transcendent divine might; its grade wasn’t too high.

But, the key factor was that it was extremely well suited for Lin Ming. Moreover, he also had the support of Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s ready-made memories and his experience. With this, Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s inheritance provided a good deal of inspiration to Lin Ming in controlling the power of thunder as well as perceiving the Thunder Laws.

Simultaneously, Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s memories allowed Lin Ming to further understand what happened in the war 100,000 years ago.

The start to end of the war was almost exactly as Lin Ming had speculated. Unfortunately, Empyrean Thunder Punishment’s memory of events only lasted until he had been struck by Empyrean Primordius’ strongest attack and sent piercing through the Sky Spill Planet. After that, his soul had been scattered and his origin energy completely exhausted. All that was left over of him was a wisp of a remnant soul.

All matters that occurred afterwards, Empyrean Thunder Punishment had no idea of.

Like this, a month passed.

On this day, the meditating Lin Ming suddenly stood up. He wanted to leave the human residential area.

“Sir, is there some matter?”

Wanyue asked with surprise.

“Mm.”

Lin Ming didn’t speak further. He flew up and towards the peak of Zenith Palace.

He had already understood from Jaderiver and that Zenith Palace Elder that the sect wars within the Akashic Dream Battlefield would be occurring in a few days.

And in truth, in Zenith Palace, many disciples had converged in the main square before the central palace. These disciples were all outstanding individuals of Zenith Palace.

Among them were the elites from the core disciples as well as some people who were considerably older. These older people tended to be at the Holy Lord realm or above and were the backbone of Zenith Palace.

“There are three more days! That is when the war within the Akashic Dream Battlefield begins! When you enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield, you will need to stay there for a full three years!”

Standing in front of all the disciples of Zenith Palace was a grandiose white-robed old man. This old man was Zenith Palace’s Vice Palace Master.

“During these three years you will run into all sorts of enemies. This includes opponents from other sects as well as nightmare beasts. Cut them down to gather merit points!

“And the more merit points you gather, the more unimaginable the rewards you can exchange them for!

“Besides the resources handed down by Zenith Palace, the most important factor of all are the heaven-shaking rewards from the Akashic Dream Universe!

“The rewards of the Akashic Dream Universe are no trifling matter. In the legends, the Akashic Dream Universe was created by the first ancestor of all spiritas and the lucky chances within are incomprehensibly great. The highest rewards can even move the heart of a True Divinity!

“Of course, this is all far too distant for you. If any of you can open yourself just a small space within the Cardinal Sky World then that is more than enough to be proud of. This will allow your future road of martial arts to be free from many troubles!

“All of you should be aware that today is your good fortune as well as your opportunity! In these past years, amongst the World King influences of Cardinal Sky World, the results of my Zenith Palace haven’t been too great. Your results this time are directly correlated to the destiny of the sect! Empyrean Cardinal Sky has already sent out a proclamation that anyone who has outstanding results in the Akashic Dream Battlefield will be personally taken in as a disciple by him. All of you should be well aware of what it means to become a disciple of Empyrean Cardinal Sky!

“Not to mention the other benefits, just being a disciple of Empyrean Cardinal Sky will make you a candidate to be the next Zenith Palace Master! And as long as you can break into the World King realm in the future, that is a Highest Elder!”

The white-robed old man passionately spoke out. As the disciples of Zenith Palace heard this, all of them began to bubble with excitement.

If one could be received as a disciple by Empyrean Cardinal Sky, they could be the next Zenith Palace Master!

In addition, there was also the heaven-shaking rewards of the Akashic Dream Universe and the support of Zenith Palace’s resources.

This was a golden chance – just who would miss out on this opportunity?

This was all because Zenith Palace had started to decline in these last years. The two World King masters of Zenith Palace were well into their old age. Not only could they not enhance their cultivation boundaries anymore, but instead their vitality began to dissipate further with every passing day.

According to this trend, in less than 100,000 years, the two sect-stabilizing World Kings of Zenith Palace would drop to the weakest of World Kings in terms of fighting strength.

At that time, the grade of influence that Zenith Palace was would surely drop down by one.

And to train another World King powerhouse in these 100,000 years seemed far too unlikely.

This was the reason why Zenith Palace spared no expense in raising the younger generation. The accumulated inside background of the sect, their many resources, all of these things were used up without hesitation. Zenith Palace had staked everything in this gamble in the hopes that they would be able to produce an outstanding junior that was able to support them in the future.

“I ask the Vice Palace Master and all other Elders to feel at ease. Within the Akashic Dream battlefield, we shall write our own legends!”

“That’s right! For the sect and for ourselves, we’ll slaughter our way through the world!”

The disciples of Zenith Palace all shouted out together, their ardent chants filling the skies.

But at this time, there was the sound of splitting air. A blue-clothed youth cut through the vast blue sky at an incredible speed, flying straight towards the meeting square.

This youth was Lin Ming.

“Who is that!?”

The disciples of Zenith Palace were just starting their chant when an uninvited guest broke his way in. The high level figures of Zenith Palace frowned. Just where had this human come from? Moreover, to be so public with his actions and fly high in the skies was an extremely impolite action.

“Lin Muk?”

Jaderiver was certainly present. She immediately recognized Lin Ming and was stunned for a moment. Where had he come from?

“Lin Muk, what are you doing! Hurry up and come down!”

Jaderiver began to develop a headache. Just what was going on here?

Lin Ming fell down. The reason he came here was to borrow one of Zenith Palace’s spots to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Since he came here to request help, he naturally couldn’t be too reckless in his actions nor could he start a fight.

Chapter 1799 – Stealing the Stage

“Brat, so it’s you again!”

A red eyebrow youth looked up at Lin Ming. This youth was Yi Fan, the young man who had come into conflict with Lin Ming aboard the spirit ship.

He didn’t think that Lin Ming would actually show up out of nowhere during the assembly meeting for the Akashic Dream Battlefield; it seemed that he was tired of living.

According to the rules of Zenith Palace, if a low level disciple were to interrupt the speech of the Vice Palace Master during an important occasion, that was a sin of tremendous disrespect.

“Jaderiver, Yi Fan, you know him?”

The white-robed Elder looked towards Jaderiver, frowning.

“Yes…”

Jaderiver braced herself and nodded. She looked at Lin Ming and glumly said, “Lin Muk, how come you aren’t training in your residential area but instead came to the high peak?”

“Miss Jaderiver.” Lin Ming cupped his fists together. “I heard that the Akashic Dream Battlefield will be opening soon and would like to be granted a spot to enter. I wonder if the Akashic Dream Battlefield has any limits on race for entrance?”

Lin Ming’s words caused the entire audience to die down.

He wanted a coveted spot to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield? Who the hell did he think he was!

“Hahaha! Are you trying to make me laugh myself to death!? You are nothing but a human and yet you’re so arrogant! Only 9300 people can enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield and the list of names was decided well over three months ago! Besides 3000 disciples that were predetermined, the 6000 some leftover spots were all decided by a grand tournament held between the disciples of Zenith Palace, passing through layers upon layers of competition before they were able to win a spot!

“Every Zenith Palace disciple that could obtain a spot is an outstanding individual that can dominate martial artists of the same level and look down upon their peers with disdain! And yet you actually spoke of wanting to take a spot from these people, what an idiot!”

Yi Fan recklessly laughed. Although his words were contemptuous, this was also what the other spiritas martial artists present were thinking. They all thought that Lin Ming was just some brain-addled idiot.

“Oh? The list of people has already been determined?” Lin Ming hadn’t expected this. Before, Jaderiver said that they could enter the Akashic Dream Universe from any place in the spiritas’ seven universes.

Now it seemed that only location wasn’t limited. But as for wanting to enter the Akashic Dream Universe, there were inevitably other restrictions. Not just anyone could casually enter as they pleased.

Zenith Palace could only send 9300 people. Then, smaller influences were likely able to send in even less.

Lin Ming’s voice lowered. He said, “Then I would like to know, is there a limit to races that can enter the Akashic Dream Universe?”

“Who cares if there isn’t? You don’t have the qualifications to begin with!” Yi Fan sneered.

“Then… give me your qualifications.” Lin Ming calmly said as he looked at Yi Fan. “Since the spots are decided through competition within the sect and I am also a disciple of the sect, once I defeat you I should obtain your qualifications, right?”

“You!! You want to die!?”

Hearing Lin Ming’s brazen words, Yi Fan was enraged.

With a ringing sound, Yi Fang’s sword left its sheath. He pointed it straight towards Lin Ming!

“Since you’re in such a hurry to die, let me help!”

Yi Fan flew into the sky as he spoke. His eyes locked onto Lin Ming’s dantian.

Because Lin Ming had been injured before, his inner world had been in chaotic tatters. But now, Lin Ming had completely recovered and there was no need for him to conceal his inner world, thus Yi Fan was clearly able to discern Lin Ming’s cultivation.

“What? Early Holy Lord realm? So you are a Holy Lord realm human?”

Yi Fan’s words startled all the Zenith Palace disciples present. They all looked towards Lin Ming’s dantian and could feel the light aura of a micro universe from within.

In other words, his inner world had developed starry space and even bred planets.

“Early Holy Lord?” Jaderiver’s eyes flashed with astonishment. So the Lin Muk that she had rescued was actually an early Holy Lord realm martial artist.

In the Soul World, human Holy Lord realm martial artists were extremely rare.

Generally speaking, a human had to possess great talent and come across many lucky chances as well as have an extremely high degree of talent to just barely be able to break into the Holy Lord realm. Moreover, the Holy Lord realm was the terminus of human cultivation. To take a further step into the World King realm was impossible.

“Humph! Who cares if you are a Holy Lord? No wonder you have the guts to rush to the highest peak. Do you think that just because you are a Holy Lord you are that great? In Zenith Palace, a Holy Lord isn’t anything at all! Moreover, you are nothing but a human Holy Lord, you don’t even enter my eyes!”

What Yi Fan despised the most was human martial artists. In the Soul World, human martial artists were in a miserable state and it was nearly impossible for them to keep up with spiritas martial artists of the same level. In fact, even when facing a spiritas that was a small boundary lower, they still might lose.

Moreover, Yi Fan was an extraordinary core disciple of Zenith Palace and his cultivation was at the peak of the late Soul Lord realm; he wasn’t too far from the Holy Lord realm.

The reason he was able to obtain a spot to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield was not because he competed through the tournament but because he was elected and directly granted an entry token.

A talented disciple of a World King Holy Land possessed more than enough skill to jump ranks to fight. Even a spiritas Holy Lord might not be his match, much less a human Holy Lord!

“Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver, this person wants to walk down the road of death. Me killing him is also within reason so you should look for some other human to perfect your virtual dantian instead!”

As Yi Fan spoke, he slashed his sword down at Lin Ming.

His sword chopped towards Lin Ming’s forehead. Sword light shot out. Yi Fan had also combined a soul attack in this strike, going for a one hit kill!

In this situation, many of his fellow sect disciples were watching. If he couldn’t destroy Lin Ming in one strike then even if he won he wouldn’t have any face to greet them.

And at this time, Lin Ming also retaliated.

Facing someone like Yi Fan, Lin Ming had no need to use any transcendent divine might. Rather, he formed a spear with two fingers and cut downwards, sending out a brilliant divine light.

In that moment, many Zenith Palace disciples were forced to shut their eyes. That dreadful divine light was a nearly substantialized spear light. Just by looking at it they felt as if it would pierce their skulls, and even their souls shivered.

Peng!

Blood sprinkled down. Yi Fan cried out in pain and was flung backwards, his sword also sent scattering away.

His figure flew back a thousand feet before slamming into the ground like a meteor. He continued tumbling backwards until he crashed into an ice sculpture, causing it to explode into countless shards.

All of this happened in a split second. The entire audience was left in a silent daze.

The result of this brief exchange was completely unexpected.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Yi!”

Several disciples quickly ran over to help Yi Fan.

Lin Ming had held back. In Zenith Palace’s territory he certainly wouldn’t take Yi Fang’s life, but this strike was more than enough to keep him bedridden for a long period of time.

Since Lin Ming had already said he wanted to substitute for Yi Fan to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield, severely wounding Yi Fan so that he would have to spend a few months recuperating was the most appropriate decision.

“What was that? What happened just now?”

Many Zenith Palace disciples hadn’t been able to clearly see just what Lin Ming did.

“This human instantly struck down Senior-apprentice Brother Yi Fan! Moreover, he didn’t even use a weapon, he just used his fingers!”

The Zenith Palace disciples all looked at each other in shocked dismay. They couldn’t believe that a highly ranked core disciple had been defeated in such a manner.

Although Yi Fan was only a late Soul Lord martial artist, he could easily jump ranks to right. If one said he was equal to a Holy Lord realm spiritas martial artist, no one would refute that.

But in front of this human, he had been utterly devastated. The disparity was just far too great.

“This human martial artist is also a genius, a king amongst his level! Perhaps he might not be much worse than a middle spiritas Holy Lord or even late spiritas Holy Lord!”

“That’s too exaggerated. If so, then isn’t it likely he’ll break into the World King realm?”

To the disciples of Zenith Palace, the World King realm was a legend.

For the last million years of the sect, they had arduously accumulated a total of two World Kings. And in the future, it would be difficult for them to raise another World King to succeed the previous ones.

To break into the World King realm – wasn’t that easier said than done?

“No matter what, he is absolutely a master. He might not be any weaker than Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver!”

“Perhaps he might barely be able to compare with Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver. Although it was a Holy Lord against a Soul Lord, with a boundary difference dividing them, it was still incredible that he could win so easily. A human was actually able to grow to such a degree…”

That spear light Lin Ming shot out just now was only aimed at Yi Fan, but even so, the other martial artists who saw it felt as if they themselves had been pierced by the spear light and had been left panic-stricken.

And at this time, Yi Fan was also lying in a sludge of ice and bloody water. As he looked at Lin Ming, his eyes were blurry.

“You… you…”

“I only want your qualifications; I have no interest in killing you.” Lin Ming gloomily said. He no longer looked at Yi Fan but instead turned to the approaching Vice Palace Master.

“Senior Vice Palace Master, this Yi Fan had said that there was no limit to race in entering the Akashic Dream Universe, right?”

After being questioned by Lin Ming, the white-robed old man’s complexion turned ugly.

If Lin Ming was a spiritas then the Vice Palace Master would have been overjoyed if he had defeated Yi Fan with a single move. He would have regarded Lin Ming as the most precious of treasures.

But, the situation was different.

Lin Ming was a human.

A human disciple might be part of Zenith Palace in name, but the truth was that none of them existed in the high level ranks of Zenith Palace. Zenith Palace had always regarded humans as not being a part of their own, and felt a bias towards them as those of an inferior race.

“Yes, there is no restriction…”

The Vice Palace Master’s voice was low and deep. He looked towards the approaching Jaderiver.

Jaderiver also felt this entire situation unbelievable. Lin Ming’s strength had far surpassed her estimations.

As she recalled the location where she first found Lin Ming, a strange feeling surged in her heart. Why had Lin Ming appeared at the same time that the hornless ice dragon had, and why had he been injured? Was all of this a coincidence?

“Third High Master, the situation is like this…”

Jaderiver’s lips moved as she quickly explained to the Vice Palace Master about Lin Ming’s status using a sound transmission.

The white-robed old man carefully listened, his eyebrows shaking.

Such an outstanding disciple was actually not a spiritas; this left him feeling a deep melancholy.

If Lin Ming had been a spiritas then he could be raised with their full support and he might even become a World King in the future.

The white-robed old man looked at several Zenith Palace Masters that were standing nearby.

These people were all high level Elders of Zenith Palace. They glanced at each other, wanting to form a consensus of opinion. Finally, the Great Elder of Zenith Palace spoke up.

“Allow him to join the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Although he is a human, as long as he carries a battlefield token of my Zenith Palace then he is also a disciple of my Zenith Palace. This time, there will be 9300 people participating in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Besides Jaderiver and a few others, I fear no one else can keep up with this human. Let him enter so he can also help support the ranks.”

“Support the ranks… aiya, even a human is stronger than us. Has Zenith Palace declined so much that we have to rely on a human junior to support us? This is just too pitiful.”

Zenith Palace Elders began to speak amongst themselves. Their words were the same as stating that Lin Ming had the qualifications to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

Chapter 1800 – Entering the Battlefield

Like this, it was decided that Lin Ming would enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield. The rest of the spiritas disciples present felt as if they were living a dream. What happened today was far too strange. A human had rushed into their meeting site and instantly defeated core disciple Yi Fan without using a weapon, thus obtaining the qualifications to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

Their Zenith Palace would actually be sending a human into the Akashic Dream Battlefield. This was something that hadn’t happened for hundreds of thousands of years.

“Lin Muk, what were you doing on the Great Desolate Glacier? Don’t try and tell me you only passed by.”

Jaderiver felt the situation was strange. Lin Ming was mind-bogglingly strong and had also appeared in the same area as the space storm; she couldn’t help but link them together.

“It’s true, I was just passing by. I had just left the mountains not too long before that.”

Lin Ming had no intentions of revealing anything related to the Divine Realm. The existence of a space channel that crossed the 33 Heavens was far too important a secret.

Jaderiver shook her head. There had been far too many flaws in Lin Ming’s words. “No matter what the situation is, the reality is that I brought you into Zenith Palace. In the eyes of all present, you suppressed Yi Fan. Let alone slapping his face, you completely tore down any face he had. Since you high-handedly demanded a spot into the Akashic Dream Battlefield, I hope that when the time comes you will listen to orders and try your best. After all, this is a war between sects and the strength of an individual is limited. If you can gather enough merit points and contribute a decent amount to Zenith Palace then that will be greatly beneficial to you.”

Jaderiver seriously said. Lin Ming hummed in agreement. Right now he still had to rely on Zenith Palace.

Afterwards, the name list for those entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield was revised. Yi Fan wasn’t kicked out. Rather, Zenith Palace used their connections to abruptly add on another entry spot.

Even though Yi Fan had been injured by Lin Ming he was still a strong soldier of Zenith Palace; his combat strength couldn’t be underestimated.

After being struck silly by Lin Ming, whenever Yi Fan saw Lin Ming walk around he felt a deep sense of hate, but also fear.

The 9000 plus disciples of Zenith Palace that were participating in the Akashic Dream Battlefield were divided into groups. Lin Ming was placed in the first squad of the first group, and the captain of this squad was impressively Jaderiver.

“Miss Jaderiver, before I heard the Vice Palace Master say that those who obtain enough merit points in the Akashic Dream Universe can exchange them for heaven-shaking rewards, and some of these rewards could even tempt a True Divinity. Would you happen to know what sort of rewards these are?”

When the Vice Palace Master had been vividly speaking in order to muster excitement, Lin Ming had heard all his words with his sharp hearing senses before he rushed into the meeting site. After hearing all of this, he had become curious as to the details of the matter.

Jaderiver rolled her eyes at Lin Ming. “What are you asking about these things for? These simply aren’t things that you nor I can hope to reach for. Certainly, if there was something that would tempt True Divinities then these True Divinities would send their disciples to take them. But in the last several billion years there have been many disciples from True Divinity level influences entering the Akashic Dream Universe, and yet they haven’t been able to take out too much.”

“Oh? Then that means there have been people that have taken rewards out?” Lin Ming asked, sensing the meaning behind Jaderiver’s words.

“Just because someone can take out such a reward every billion years doesn’t mean you can too. Stop dreaming.”

At this time, a female disciple standing near Jaderiver suddenly interjected. Her name was Xiao Chi and she was also a core disciple of Zenith Palace.

“I was just curious.” Lin Ming’s eyes twitched. He really wanted to get to the end of this question.

Jaderiver helplessly shrugged. She said, “It is rumored that within the Akashic Dream Universe there are many treasures that are deeply buried. Amongst these treasures are top divine objects. For instance, legends state that there are divine soul springs, golden pages, undying divine medicines, and so forth.”

Lin Ming perked up, “Golden pages?”

“Mm, they are parts of an incomplete ancient text. I heard they are something that can even move the hearts of True Divinities. There are other things that can tempt True Divinities of course. For instance, undying divine medicines that can lengthen the lifespan of a True Divinity level powerhouse. If a True Divinity were to refine these medicines into pills then they could create pills that surpass a transcendent divine pill, in other words, pills of a True Divinity level. These pills contain the perfectly exquisite Laws of the Great Dao, and after swallowing them one can perceive the Great Dao Laws. For an Empyrean trying to break into the True Divinity realm, they are an immeasurable boon.”

Jaderiver had only heard some rumors and didn’t know the exact details of things. But her words caused Lin Ming’s heart to shake. Golden pages, undying divine medicines… was it possible that these golden pages were from an incomplete version of the Spiritas Holy Scripture?

The possibility was high. If the Spiritas Holy Scripture and Akashic Dream Universe both originated from the hands of the first ancestor of all spiritas, then these golden pages were extremely likely to be related to the Spiritas Holy Scripture. And, the Spiritas Holy Scripture was of utmost importance to the True Divinities of the spiritas.

“Besides the golden pages from something that might be the Spiritas Holy Scripture, there are also divine soul springs, undying divine medicines, and other treasures… it seems that everything within this Akashic Dream Universe is quite extraordinary. It’s worth looking forward to…”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, his thoughts began to heat up.

The reason he was going to the Akashic Dream Universe was not just to search for Sheng Mei but also to struggle for lucky chances.

There were still three days until the Akashic Dream Battlefield opened. During this time, Lin Ming didn’t do anything at all. Rather, he sat in meditation and adjusted himself to his peak condition.

Three days afterwards, the Akashic Dream Battlefield officially opened.

All disciples participating in the Akashic Dream Battlefield convened at the highest peak. Each person was given a token.

“Pour your energy into the token and you will be able to sense the existence of the Akashic Dream Universe. Afterwards, your spirit will enter while your mortal body will be sealed in a separate space. It is an extremely safe procedure!”

A white-robed Elder loudly proclaimed as he stood atop a high platform.

Lin Ming felt much more relieved upon hearing this. To have his spirit enter the Akashic Dream Universe and his mortal body sealed away in some separate space was perfect for him. If his mind entered the Akashic Dream Universe he wanted to ensure that no one would be able to harm his mortal body while he wasn’t there.

“Very good. The time has arrived. Everyone, prepare to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield!”

Not too far away from the white-robed Elder, there was a massive incense burner. This incense burner had a thick coiled incense burning within it, and this incense had now burned to its end.

“All disciples of Zenith Palace, listen to orders – open the Akashic Dream Universe!”

As the white-robed Elder spoke, every disciple of Zenith Palace poured their energy into their token. Lin Ming also did this.

9301 tokens began to emit a dim halo after absorbing the energy. As these halos gathered together, they combined as one, becoming an extremely brilliant and beautiful sight!

The entire sky was lit up with by the multicolored energies.

And at this time, the 9301 tokens projected thin beams of light. These thin blue beams shot into the endless skies, forming a bridge that spanned the heavens and earth, penetrating hundreds of thousands of feet upwards.

Chi chi chi!

For a time, the skies were pierced through by these 9301 beams of light. The power of space dissipated outwards, forming a massive dark red and purple space gate.

This space gate was like an ephemeral dream. The constantly shimmering purple and red surface changed again and again, as if a kaleidoscope of whole new worlds was within it.

For a time, all of the disciples of Zenith Palace that carried a token felt an irresistible traction force lift up their bodies and send them flying towards the space gate.

Lin Ming felt himself hurtle forwards faster and faster. As he flew, everything seemed to become further and further away. A tremendous tearing power started to work upon his spiritual sea.

His mortal body began to separate from his soul.

He stared helplessly on as his mortal body grew further and further away until it was sealed in a chaotic space. At the same time, his soul form was sucked into that red and purple space gate. After this, everything turned hazy in his mind.

This space gate was extremely mystical and there were countless exquisite Laws contained within that Lin Ming couldn’t understand at all. But, it was clear that these Laws were connected to the soul forging system.

Lin Ming couldn’t bother with delving deeper into this. All he felt was an agonizing headache as if his soul was being constantly distorted by some great strength.

He didn’t know how long these feeling continued for. In the next moment, Lin Ming’s body shook and he had arrived in an unknown world.

This area was bleak and desolate. The ground beneath him was sparse wilderness. The skies were high and far and covered in thick layers of clouds. It was a depressing sight.

“This is the Akashic Dream Universe?”

Lin Ming closed his eyes, allowing his sense to spread out like a web. All he felt was that there was an ancient and vast aura flooding this land.

This sort of feeling caused Lin Ming to think as if this universe was a world left behind from ancient times. Even through billions of years it had maintained its once glorious scenery.

And at this time, Zenith Palace disciples began to pop up all around Lin Ming. As they appeared, some of them stumbled to catch their footing. All of them were pale; it was clear they were feeling queasy from travelling through that space gate just now.

No matter how powerful one’s soul force was, one wouldn’t feel comfortable upon entering the Akashic Dream Universe. This was because the stronger one’s soul force was, the greater the backlash they would receive upon entering the space gate.

As the many Zenith Palace disciples appeared, the curtains for the sect wars had officially been lifted.

Chapter 1801 – Emperor God Wall

“The resting city is just ahead, so let’s go there first.”

Jaderiver said. Zenith Palace had sent more than 9000 disciples to participate in the Akashic Dream Battlefield and she wasn’t the decision maker.

The decision makers were the several half-step World Kings that had joined in. They were Elders of Zenith Palace and this also included the Vice Palace Master, the white-robed old man who had been hosting the meeting conference.

Entering the Akashic Dream Universe had no restrictions on age. Rather, it looked at whether or not someone was an outstanding individual and just how much potential they possessed.

Generally speaking, if one was doomed to never be able to take another step forwards in their cultivation road then there was no need for them to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Only those who had hopes of going further down their road of martial arts would come here to struggle for a lucky chance.

The city within the Akashic Dream Universe was extremely lifelike and none of it felt like an illusion at all. Touching anything gave a feeling no different than interacting with objects in the real world.

The truth was that the spiritual world and real world were never clearly distinguished to begin with. In fact, there were even some spiritas martial artists who theorized that the current 33 Heavens was nothing more than a dream of a sleeping creator god.

This city was incomparably broad and a massive number of outstanding elites were also gathered here.

Many more martial artists continued to hasten their way to the city.

Of these people’s cultivation, the lowest amongst them were at the Soul Sea realm, a spiritas cultivation realm equivalent to the human Divine Sea realm. As for the highest, they were Great World Kings, and more than one at that.

Lin Ming guessed that there were likely also half-step Empyreans here, and even true Empyrean supreme elders; he just hadn’t seen them yet.

As they arrived not too far from the city, Lin Ming looked up at the city gates that rose a thousand feet high. Above these gates were two strange spiritas characters.

Lin Ming had previously studied the language of the spiritas. He could see that these characters said – Emperor City!

Each character was the size of a large house and they were drawn in an illustrious manner. The aura they gave off was intimidating.

Even Lin Ming couldn’t help but feel a faint sense of awe and dread upon seeing these characters.

Emperor City was surrounded by walls on three sides, each side stretching out nearly a thousand miles long. As for the rear side of the city, it was backed up against a giant divine mountain.

This divine mountain was as smooth as a mirror and was covered with a canopy of runes.

As Lin Ming and the others approached within a hundred miles of this divine mountain, they felt a tremendous pressure.

Ordinary Zenith Palace disciples could not approach. As they tried, they felt all of their blood vitality, spirit essence, and soul force being pulled upon by this pressure, making the energy within them nearly explode outwards from their bodies.

Jaderiver said, “This is the Emperor God Wall. It has already existed for countless years and is the divine object of Emperor City. It is said that it was stained with the blood of peerless God Kings and their aura has yet to dissipate even after billions upon billions of years have passed. And, what we see now is only a projection of the Emperor God Wall. The true Emperor God Wall is not here, but every city has a projection of the Emperor God Wall.”

As Jaderiver spoke, the disciples of Zenith Palace were shocked. Even Lin Ming was left flabbergasted.

It was only a projection yet it exuded such a terrifying pressure.

Then, just what would the true Emperor God Wall be like!?

Some of the outstanding disciples of Zenith Palace strode within several miles of the God Wall. At this distance, they could see many martial artists tirelessly moving forwards as well as some others meditating beneath it.

“They are cultivating, trying to use the pressure of the Emperor God Wall to aid in their breakthrough.”

A Zenith Palace Elder explained.

By being beneath the Emperor God Wall, one would have to withstand a terrifying pressure. This pressure could burden one’s soul and spirit essence, and even directly work upon the martial artist’s body that was sealed away in a separate space to further temper their blood vitality, allowing them to make a breakthrough. It was an incomparably mysterious phenomenon.

“This cultivation isn’t too bad. Eh, there are also some characters on the God Wall.”

A Zenith Palace disciple exclaimed. Lin Ming looked up, able to clearly read the runes written atop the Emperor God Wall.

These runes were ancient and mysterious, consisting of the spiritas language from billions of years ago.

Not even Lin Ming could fully understand them.

“These carvings are…” A Zenith Palace disciple asked.

“They are the rules, as well as the divine objects within the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Look at the third row, that is the Wild God Creed. In the legends it’s said to be a holy text left behind by the first ancestor of the spiritas. The fourth row lists the Weeping God Springs. It is said to be a deep spring that can even help cleanse the marrows of a True Divinity supreme elder. If one could obtain that God Springs’ water to use for alchemy, they could make True Divinity level medicines. As for the fifth row…”

The one speaking was the white-robed Vice Palace Master. His understanding of the Akashic Dream Battlefield was more deep than Jaderiver’s, and as he slowly introduced the various objects, everyone who listened to him was left dumbfounded. Although they clearly knew they couldn’t obtain any of these things, just hearing about it was more than enough to cause their blood to boil over with excitement.

“How do we obtain these things?” Lin Ming asked. As for the other disciples of Zenith Palace, although they didn’t think they could ever obtain these treasures they were still curious about how one obtained them.

The Vice Palace Master said, “Some of these divine objects can be exchanged for using an incredible amount of merit points. As for some other things, they require achievements, lucky chances, or various other items to exchange for them.”

As he spoke, another Zenith Palace disciple said, “Look, there are also names carved upon the God Wall!”

Hearing this disciple’s shout, many people looked down. As he said there were indeed names of powerhouses left behind on the Emperor God Wall.

These names were all written in different handwriting styles and they emitted a dreadful aura. One could instantly see that they weren’t left behind by ordinary mortals.

“Those that can leave behind their names are mostly Empyreans as well as a small number of Great World Kings. They are all proud children of heaven that have existed through the history of the spiritas. There are some people that weren’t Empyreans when they left behind their names, but they would eventually become Empyreans in the future. Rather, it should be said that most of them became extreme Empyreans, and a few of them even managed to step into the realm of True Divinity.”

The Zenith Palace Elder’s explanation left everyone bewildered. Even amongst the spiritas, True Divinities were a mythical existence. It was hard for ordinary martial artists to imagine what they were like.

“Mm? Sheng Mei!”

Lin Ming’s pupils shrank. Amongst the many names, he could make out Sheng Mei’s!

Sheng Mei had also carved her name above the God Wall.

“Soul Empress Sheng Mei, her talent cannot be imagined. Through the vast 33 Heavens, no one can surpass her.”

Jaderiver thought that Lin Ming had come from the wild mountains and didn’t know about many matters, thus she briefly introduced Sheng Mei. Sheng Mei was absolutely the heroine of the spiritas, and as Jaderiver mentioned her name, she felt awe and pride.

“Not everyone can leave behind their name on the Emperor God Wall. These people have all achieved some peerless accomplishments or have accumulated merit points to a terrifying degree. Only then can they leave behind their name on the Emperor God Wall.”

Another Zenith Palace Elder explained.

At this time, everyone was startled. They watched as a decrepit one-legged old man with scattered hair walked towards the Emperor God Wall.

Because this person only had one leg, he seemed to hop as he walked. In addition to that, his entire face was marred with horrifying scars, making him seem like a ghost walking around during daytime.

“Just who is that? What a scary-looking old man.”

Standing beside Jaderiver, Xiao Chi couldn’t help but cover her mouth in shock.

“Stop spouting nonsense!” A Zenith Palace Elder hurriedly said. However, Xiao Chi’s words had already been heard by the one-legged old man.

The old man’s hearing was extremely sharp. He suddenly turned his head, revealing a grisly and humorless smile.

With this, everyone could see that he had a Great World King cultivation.

All of the disciples from Zenith Palace paled.

“Hehe.”

The one-legged old man diabolically grinned. As he stared at Xiao Chi, Xiao Chi shivered and a cold chill ran up her back. She felt as if she were being stared at by some viper.

“Our junior was being foolish. Senior, please forgive her.”

“Whatever. I am someone that bears deep grudges.” The one-legged old man simply didn’t place the Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master in his eyes. As he turned back and walked forwards, he left behind an endless killing intent.

For a time, Xiao Chi’s face turned as white as funeral paper. “Elder, I…”

No one thought that in Emperor City, just a few words could draw a catastrophe upon oneself.

The several Elders of Zenith Palace all had ugly complexions. That one-legged old freak had a bizarre personality. If one annoyed him, they definitely wouldn’t have a happy ending.

And at this time, a gloating laugh rang out. “Haha, congratulations everyone from Zenith Palace! You just arrived and yet you’ve already drawn a winning ticket. Looking at your expressions, it seems you’ll all be wiped out sooner or later.”

These words caused the disciples from Zenith Palace to frown.

They turned to see a middle-aged fat man jovially walking towards them, laughing all the while. Behind him was a large group all wearing the same uniform; it was clear that they came from the same influence.

“Eh? There’s even a human! Has Zenith Palace degenerated so much that they must even send a human to participate in the Akashic Dream Battlefield?”

The fat man openly mocked Zenith Palace as he saw Lin Ming.

“Forget about him, let’s go.” The Vice Palace Master was clearly acquainted with the fat man, but their relationship seemed extremely bad. He didn’t want to have any accidents occur. Within the confines of Emperor City, fighting wasn’t allowed.

Just as the Vice Palace Master was leading the disciples to leave, the skies suddenly darkened. A massive ancient vicious beast emitted a terrifying slaughter energy as it flew over the city gates and fell atop a tall pagoda within the city. This ancient vicious beast was huge and as it unfolded its wings, its wingspan was nearly a hundred miles wide, almost camouflaging the skies. The towering pagoda that it fell upon seemed as small as a toy.

A horrifying howl pierced through the heavens, making the ears tingle with numbness.

“What an amazingly dreadful aura. Just what kind of ancient beast is that?”

Many Zenith Palace disciples asked, horrified.

“That is a leviathan roc! Although it has an impure bloodline it can almost compare with a God Beast. It is even stronger than most half-step Empyreans.”

A Zenith Palace Elder whispered, his breath catching in his throat.

“I know this leviathan roc, it is Empyrean Heavencore’s personal mount. This isn’t even its complete form. When it fully manifests its body, its wingspan can reach a thousand miles!”

As everyone was speaking, the leviathan roc suddenly opened its gaping jaws. An army of martial artists walked out from within the stomach of the leviathan roc.

In the legends, the leviathan roc had a separate world contained within its body. It could easily swallow mountains and rivers, much less something as small as hundreds of thousands of disciples.

These disciples that marched out from the stomach of the leviathan roc were all from Heavencore Heavenly Palace.

Besides the outstanding young elites of Heavencore Heavenly Palace, there were also the core disciples and the martial artists that made up the backbone of Heavencore Heavenly Palace.

Lin Ming was vigilant as he saw this. Amongst these people, there were many World Kings, Great World Kings, and even half-step Empyreans!

They were all disciples of Heavencore Heavenly Palace. However, some of these people had already followed Empyrean Heavencore for 100,000 years and were no longer considered juniors.

These people possessed a profound cultivation. The reason they came to the Akashic Dream Battlefield was in hopes of going further in their cultivation. For instance, a Great World King becoming a half-step Empyrean, or a half-step Empyrean becoming a true Empyrean.

“This is an Empyrean level influence…”

Some people sighed in admiration. Just any one of these high level Heavencore Heavenly Palace disciples could easily sweep away Zenith Palace.

Far too many masters had gathered at the Akashic Dream Battlefield. It was destined to be an unrivalled war.

Chapter 1802 – Empyreans Involved

More and more martial artists began gathering at Emperor City. Many large sects had several tens of thousands or even hundreds of thousands of disciples arrive.

Among these people, Lin Ming saw a great deal of half-step Empyreans. However, he didn’t see any true Empyreans.

“There are so many World Kings, Great World Kings, and even half-step Empyreans. This is my first time entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield and my cultivation is just at the early Soul Lord realm. If I face opponents like these won’t I be instantly evaporated?”

A young Zenith Palace disciple timidly asked.

The Vice Palace Master shook his head, saying, “Our war will occur within the Akashic Dream Battlefield. The Laws there are special and will suppress everyone’s cultivation to the Soul Lord realm. As for those that haven’t reached the Soul Lord realm, their cultivations will be forcefully enhanced to that boundary, making everyone’s cultivation the same. Even so, a half-step Empyrean powerhouse isn’t someone you can deal with, because their comprehension of Laws and their skill in cultivation methods have reached an unimaginable degree. Even if you are both at the Soul Lord realm, it will only take an instant to kill you!

“But that doesn’t mean you have no chance of escape. If dozens of you see a half-step Empyrean you can all scatter in different directions. This will give you a chance of survival.”

The Vice Palace Master explained.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred; so there were such rules.

This was also reasonable. Lin Ming had seen many inheritance lands in the past that had similar rules. To lessen the disparity brought about by age, everyone’s cultivations would be equalized. In order for the most outstanding individuals to obtain the inheritances, all that would be tested was one’s talent and potential.

As everyone was speaking, howling winds suddenly rose up. Turbulent black clouds came roiling over from the horizon, blocking out the sun.

In this extremely gloomy environment, ghostly howls filled the air. Everyone felt an inexplicable sense of fear. As they all looked up into the skies they seemed to see endless ghosts dancing about amongst the dark clouds.

For a time, all the disciples of Zenith Palace were frightened. Even the Vice Palace Master had an extremely ugly complexion.

“It’s Empyrean Myriad Ghost! That old geezer, he’s here to make a mess!”

“Empyrean! Even an Empyrean came to the Akashic Dream Battlefield?”

The Zenith Palace disciples looked at each other, panic etched in their eyes.

Even an Empyrean had arrived! Even if their cultivation was suppressed to the Soul Lord realm, an Empyrean level powerhouse was far too powerful an existence and could instantly wipe out their group.

This Akashic Dream Battlefield was truly a convergence of masters!

“Normally there is no desire for Empyreans to come here. After an Empyrean is a True Divinity, and only the tiniest minority of Empyreans have been able to take this final step. Coming here for them is just a waste of time, and there isn’t anything they can learn through messing around with you juniors. But this Empyrean Myriad Ghost has an extremely eccentric and strange personality… I wonder just what he came to the Akashic Dream Battlefield for… all of you make sure to hide from him and have no contact with him at all.”

The Vice Palace Master urgently said.

“It’s a waste for an Empyrean to come? Since they are strong, wouldn’t it be easier for them to gather merit points and achievements to exchange them for rewards?”

Lin Ming asked. Some Zenith Palace disciples who had come to the Akashic Dream Universe for the first time also perked up their ears. This information was extremely important to them.

The Vice Palace Master simply shook his head, “Merit points are for the young; they aren’t something us old fellows can obtain. This is because after the three years are over, the final amount of merit points after being settled is based upon age. For instance, if an Empyrean that has lived for tens of millions of years enters the Akashic Dream Battlefield and slaughters their way to a billion merit points, their merit points are divided by their age, thus they might have a measly several hundred left remaining. There just isn’t anything they can exchange for with this amount.”

As the Vice Palace Master spoke, Lin Ming was suddenly enlightened about the situation. All things considered, the Akashic Dream Battlefield was a stage set for the younger generation, and this was also a reasonable premise. If the Akashic Dream Battlefield was a land of inheritance, then inheritances naturally had to be passed onto the young.

If old fellows like the Vice Palace Master came, they came not for the merit points but for the experience of fighting with martial artists of the same level.

After all, in the real world these older martial artists rarely had the opportunity to fight with other martial artists of the same age and boundary.

And without fighting, it would be difficult to hone their cultivation.

“He can’t obtain any merit points nor can he find anyone of his level to fight… is that Empyrean Myriad Ghost really here to cause a ruckus…”

The Vice Palace Master mumbled.

Some Empyreans had extremely peculiar personalities. For instance, there might be some Empyreans who didn’t obtain any advantages from the Akashic Dream Battlefield during their youth, thus they also didn’t want anyone else to obtain benefits.

It was true that an Empyrean couldn’t obtain merit points, but they also possessed the ability to ensure that no one else did either. For instance, they could do this by continually slaughtering everyone else…

If this were true, then during this venture into the Akashic Dream Battlefield, the low level disciples would truly be having a miserable time.

As the Vice Palace Master was lost in thought, at this time a vast slaughter energy as deep as an ocean covered the entirety of Emperor City, enveloping everyone. For a time, a horrifying pressure spread outwards and all the light within the city disappeared. The martial artists were stranded in this thick black chaos, leaving them suffocating.

“This is… the chaos force field, the signature domain of Chaos Demon God, another Empyrean!”

“I understand now. The reason Empyrean Myriad Ghost came to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield this time is so that he can fight with Chaos Demon God. Both of them don’t like each other to begin with, but if they fought in the real world then that would be an earth-sundering battle between two Empyreans. Moreover, if there were any wounds, those would be losses that neither side could afford! So, the two of them must have agreed to meet in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Like this, there won’t be any problems with the two of them fighting!”

The Zenith Palace Elders wryly smiled to each other as they realized this.

A battle between two Empyreans was bound to affect the little fish. The low level disciples of Zenith Palace were in for a tragic time.

If they were sucked into the battle, they wouldn’t even have ashes left over.

“All of you must be careful after entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Make sure you avoid those two old monsters at all costs. Aiya, what horrible luck this is.”

The Vice Palace Master sighed with emotion.

At this time, Lin Ming had regained his composure. He asked, “Senior Vice Palace Master, junior has a question he would like to ask.”

“Mm? What is it?”

Seeing the one asking another question was Lin Ming, the Vice Palace Master faintly frowned. It seemed all this disciple did was ask questions again and again.

“Junior would like to know just how many merit points are required to exchange for a golden page?”

On the Emperor God Wall, the rules for obtaining rewards from the Akashic Dream Battlefield were listed. However, because these rules were all written in the ancient language of the spiritas, Lin Ming found them difficult to read.

The Vice Palace Master was speechless. This disciple was far too curious. Just why did he want to know all of this?

“You sure have many worries. What you should be concerning yourself with is thinking about how to survive. The honest method of these sect wars is too kill as many enemies as possible. As for that golden page, that is something that hasn’t been exchanged for in the last several hundred millions of years. It requires a billion merit points, so don’t get your hopes up about obtaining it.”

The Vice Palace Master impatiently responded. Lin Ming smiled, “Thank you Senior for the guidance.”

“All of you rest early and don’t bother caring about such meaningless things. At dawn tomorrow we will be entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield. At that time, I also hope that you all will be able to fight for a little bit of glory for our Zenith Palace!”

The last several times that Zenith Palace participated in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, their results had been ordinary at best. This left the high level figures of Zenith Palace feeling anxious.

Like this, all disciples of Zenith Palace looked for a place to rest. Although Emperor City was large, there were even more martial artists. Most rooms were already occupied.

Spirit ships, cave dwellings, and other such magic tools couldn’t be brought in, so many martial artists spent the night sitting in meditation in the air.

At the dawn of the next day, the morning was misty and bright. Rays of morning light sprinkled down, reflecting from the Emperor God Wall and shining upon all the martial artists present.

Everyone was covered in this sunlight. Finally, this sunlight turned into countless motes of light that converged into everyone’s tokens.

“What is this?”

A young disciple asked with surprise.

“This is elementary spirit source. In truth, this is what the so-called merit points consist of. By killing your opponent you can plunder their token’s elementary spirit source and take it into your own. This is what merit points are!”

As people were speaking, at this time the entire Emperor City began to tremble. The great earth seemed to be split apart by a titanic divine sword. From the area where the land had split open, purple divine fire gushed out, burning up the skies.

A giant space gate slowly appeared above the sundered earth. It was like a purple sun had appeared in the world.

“The Akashic Dream Battlefield has opened. Let’s enter!”

Throughout all of Emperor City, countless disciples launched their movement techniques and flew towards the space gate.

This space gate was several hundred miles wide. The martial artists present all appeared like tiny specks in front of this massive space gate. From afar, it was like infinite locusts migrating towards the space gate.

Lin Ming also joined in. And at this time, the Vice Palace Master lit a rune. With it, all disciples of Zenith Palace were covered in a halo of light.

Covered in this halo of light, Lin Ming passed through the purple space gate…

Chapter 1803 – Bait

Hu - !

Endless beams of light passed over Lin Ming’s sight. After an unknown period of time, his environment brightened; he had arrived in some unknown world.

Emperor City had vanished. All around them was bleak and desolate earth. The land was marred with gaping scars as if a terrifying war had occurred here.

Mountains and rivers had been sundered in half or leveled off, and massive craters marked the land. There were even dreadfully deep abysses, as if some mighty supernatural being broke open the earth with their weapon.

And in the skies, there were numerous listless planets. These planets lacked even a little bit of life and resembled barren stones.

This was the Akashic Dream Battlefield!

The Akashic Dream Battlefield was but a miniscule portion of the Akashic Dream Universe. After entering this land, one needed to stay for a full three years.

During these three years, no one would be able to probe what was happening within the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Only when all the martial artists completed their journey into the Akashic Dream Battlefield three years from now would the results be known.

The disciples of Zenith Palace were all gathered here. As for the disciples of other influences, they had vanished; they had been transmitted to other locations.

This sort of situation clearly occurred because the Vice Palace Master had crumbled a talisman before he entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

Lin Ming had glanced over this talisman. It was an inscription symbol and its use was likely to make the disciples of Zenith Palace be transported to a location far away from the others.

The spiritas were a race skilled in inscription symbols. Many spiritas martial artists even carried inscription symbols on them in battles.

“Everyone, listen to my orders. We are a whole – do not separate from the group, otherwise you will be eaten up without any bones remaining. This is a war of sect against sect, the strength that an individual can display is limited!

“Obey all orders. For those that can obtain merit points, my Zenith Palace will never be stingy with rewards!”

As the Vice Palace Master spoke, everyone began to set off in droves.

The Akashic Dream Battlefield had special rules. Here, Lin Ming could already feel his cultivation being suppressed by the Laws.

His inner world was imprisoned and the true essence he could erupt with was greatly limited. Even the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace had been restricted. Although he could still open three Dao Palaces, he could only gather a twentieth of the previous power of stars he was able to.

“My cultivation has been suppressed to the early Divine Lord realm…”

Lin Ming thought to himself. Looking around, he could see that everyone was in a similar situation.

Only some low level disciples were an exception. For them, not only did they not weaken but they felt a strange power that wasn’t theirs pour into their body, causing their strength to rise. This was a never-before-felt feeling.

“These conditions are even more advantageous to me!”

As Lin Ming thought this, he slowly moved away from the crowd. Slowly, he submerged into the darkness, his figure disappearing from the crowd without a trace.

No one present had been able to discover this. It was only when the disciples of Zenith Palace reached their destination did someone ask…

“Mm? Lin Muk?”

Jaderiver was startled. Lin Ming had disappeared.

Lin Ming was a member of her squad. When they first entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield just now she had also seen Lin Ming, but he had disappeared from sight not long after.

Jaderiver’s words caused the Elders of Zenith Palace to immediately release their divine senses to search for him. After they swept their senses through the crowd, their complexions turned ugly.

Zenith Palace had a large troop of over 9000 people. If they all moved together it was really too difficult to detect if a single person disappeared.

“A foreign human indeed isn’t reliable.”

A Zenith Palace Elder indignantly said.

“He took up one of our spots just to run away as soon as he came to the Akashic Dream Battlefield!”

“Could he have betrayed us?”

Several Elders glanced at each other, their complexions ugly. Although Lin Ming was a human, they all had to admit that his strength was excellent. He would have been a great boon to Zenith Palace in the Akashic Dream Battlefield and would have helped them obtain many merit points, but before any fighting had started he had already disappeared.

“I apologize… I…”

Jaderiver was at a loss for words. She was the one who had introduced Lin Ming to Zenith Palace, and when he had asked to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield later, she had also supported him with her manner. But now that such a situation had occurred, she clearly wasn’t able to lift her head.

“Well, I wouldn’t go so far as to say that he betrayed us. The token he used to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield is provided by our Zenith Palace, so his merit points will also contribute to the total merit point score. Even so, we should be a little more careful. He might have been bribed by some other influence to disclose information about us.”

As the Vice Palace Master said this, the other Elders present appeared depressed.

“Let’s go somewhere else then. If that human reveals our position and we are ambushed here then the situation will be bad for us.” Someone proposed.

“Alright, it seems that’s all we can do.”

………….

At this time, a thousand miles away from where the Zenith Palace group was, Lin Ming was flying over a vast wilderness. He released his sense, investigating the surrounding area.

According to the Vice Palace Master’s explanation, Lin Ming was considering how many merit points he needed to obtain.

His skeletal age had yet to reach 130 years.

In order to exchange for the golden page, one needed a billion merit points!

According to the rules of the Akashic Dream Battlefield, at the very end of the three years when merit points were being calculated, the total would be divided by the martial artist’s skeletal age. In other words, Lin Ming needed to obtain almost 130 billion merit points in order to exchange for that golden page.

130 billion!

Lin Ming didn’t know what sort of concept that number was, but what he was sure of was that this was a truly terrifying number.

He would need to endlessly slaughter in order to reach it.

Moreover, listening to the Vice Palace Master’s words, this Akashic Dream Battlefield was not as simple as killing others to obtain merit points. There were also other lucky chances to be found.

Whether it was for the golden page or other lucky chances, Lin Ming was doomed to not be able to follow the mass army of Zenith Palace. They would simply be stones that weighed him down, making his every movement inconvenient.

As Lin Ming was thinking this, he had already flown for an hour. This Akashic Dream Battlefield consisted of an incredibly broad area. Even though he had been flying for such a long time, all he could see was endless wilderness.

And at this time, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred and he slowed down.

He could see that there was a swamp not too far away, and in this swamp there was some strange flower blooming.

This flower had no roots, branches, or leaves, but instead had a lush flower the size of a basin; it appeared exceptionally bright.

Lin Ming could sense a light divine soul fluctuation originating from it, as if this flower had a soul. And these divine soul fluctuations were subtly influencing Lin Ming’s spiritual sea.

Lin Ming didn’t doubt that this was a medicinal herb that would be greatly beneficial in nourishing one’s divine soul.

“Is this a medicinal herb bred within the Akashic Dream Battlefield?”

This medicinal herb in front of him wasn’t too precious; he believed this was only the beginning.

He began to slowly approach. But at this time he suddenly came to an abrupt stop.

After sweeping his sense over the swamp, Lin Ming revealed a sneer.

He carelessly walked towards the red flower and reached out to pick it. But just as his fingers were about to touch the flower, from a hundred feet in front of Lin Ming, the muddy ground suddenly burst apart. With a loud roar that shook the earth, a giant black lizard that was hundreds of feet long suddenly leapt out from the swamp!

This black lizard had blood red eyes and its body was covered with scintillating black scales. Its jaws opened wide enough to swallow a house and then a tongue as thick as an adult man shot out like a spear, hurtling towards Lin Ming!

It wanted to capture Lin Ming and swallow him whole!

“I’ve been waiting for you.”

Lin Ming was already prepared. Without even a change in expression, he waved his hand and a red spear appeared in his grasp – this was the Phoenix Blood Spear.

Woosh!

The Phoenix Blood Spear shot through the skies, carrying with it a howling power of thunder and fire that pierced into the black lizard’s mouth with unstoppable momentum.

Puff!

Blood shot out. The black lizard was pierced through by the Phoenix Blood Spear, followed right after with a shower of blood.

“Rahh!”

The black lizard roared in pain and anger. After being pierced by Lin Ming’s spear, it shot towards him, wanting to use its massive body to roll over him.

Lin Ming simply flicked his finger and the Phoenix Blood Spear reversed as it came hurting back and pierced through the black lizard’s back as easily as tofu. At this time, the power of thunder and fire contained within the Phoenix Blood Spear also detonated, and with a loud explosion the black lizard’s back was blown to pieces.

The explosive shockwaves were accompanied with endless fragments of flesh and blood. The black lizard’s spine and ribs were completely shattered and its massive body was blown in half.

Facing this endless rain of blood and flesh, an invisible barrier shimmered around Lin Ming, protecting him from any contamination.

After easily killing the black lizard, Lin Ming didn’t even pause. He bent down and picked up that deep blood red flower.

After breathing in the rich soul fragrance of the flower, he quietly said, “Come out. I know that lizard was not some wild creature, but your contract beast…”

Lin Ming indifferently said, a light killing intent in his words.

There were powerful nightmare beasts that inhabited the Akashic Dream Battlefield, but this black lizard hadn’t been one of them. Before landing here, Lin Ming had already felt a group waiting on the sidelines for an ambush.

Some people had decided to use this spirit flower as bait to set up a trap to kill anyone who dared approach it. If one was too impatient to pluck the treasure they were likely to fall for the trap.

At that time, with the black lizard attacking from the front there would also be other martial artists sneak attacking from behind. Unless one was far stronger than those ambushers they would be sure to suffer a loss here.

Unfortunately, Lin Ming had instantly killed the black lizard. This caused the other martial artists lying in ambush to not dare to attack.

Lin Ming slowly turned, looking at a grassy area in the swamp. He coldly said, “It seems you want me to invite you out.”

As he spoke he immediately attacked. He flicked his fingers and spear lights came shooting out!

“No! Ahh!”

Miserable cries ran out. Eight martial artists came rolling down on the ground. Their bodies had bloody holes pierced through them by the spear lights.

They all looked at Lin Ming, panic in their eyes.

As soon as they entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield they had set up a trap here and had laid in wait. But, they never imagined their first prey would be powerful to the point of instantly killing their contract beast.

Chapter 1804 – Reinforcements

The martial artists that rolled out from the tall patch of grass were all covered in blood. They wore similar sect clothing; it was obvious they came from the same influence.

Their tactics were to take advantage of the unprepared and to fight with a numbers advantage in order to slowly gather merit points. Although this method wasn’t the most efficient, it was far safer.

However, in their first attempt they had really managed to kick an iron wall; this was just their own unluckiness.

“Young hero, please show mercy and don’t kill us!”

Seeing Lin Ming overflowing with killing intent, the martial artists were terrified.

Although their lives wouldn’t be in danger if they were killed in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, the chance to enter this land wasn’t easy to obtain. They didn’t want to die just as the sect wars began.

After being killed in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, one’s body would be stranded in a separate space and forced to live out the remaining three year period there. The taste of this punishment wasn’t good at all.

Lin Ming didn’t say a word. The Phoenix Blood Spear howled and flew back into his hand. Then, he indifferently looked at these martial artists and pointed his spear straight at the forehead of a yellow-clothed man.

Lin Ming could feel that this yellow-clothed man was the strongest of the group; he should be the leader.

“Young hero, our Imperial Beast Sect is a Great World King influence that has a history spanning hundreds of millions of years. In the history of our sect, there have even been two Empyreans that have appeared. It’s just that for the last few tens of millions of years we haven’t been able to produce an Empyrean, and thus our influence has been downgraded. Even so, we still have a deep background. Young hero doesn’t need to kill us. We have some precious inherited information from our sect if young hero would like to take a look at it.”

As the yellow-clothed man spoke, his arms trembled as he lifted a jade slip and passed it to Lin Ming.

Lin Ming swept his mind over it. There wasn’t any problem with this jade slip. Then, he probed it.

After sifting through the jade slip, Lin Ming’s interest was piqued. This jade slip recorded many regional materials within the Akashic Dream Battlefield. There were even places listed where heavenly materials might appear as well as danger zones where nightmare beasts appeared more often.

Although the records within the jade slip were rough, it was good for referencing.

As Lin Ming was looking through the jade slip his thoughts stirred. He realized that while he was probing the jade slip, the furthest disciple of the Imperial Beast Sect had quietly reached out his hand and traced his spatial ring, taking out a talisman.

As this talisman appeared, it immediately burnt up and completely vanished.

“You sent a sound transmission talisman to request reinforcements?”

Lin Ming immediately thought. His eyes flashed with a murderous light. But, he maintained his composure, only looking at the eight martial artists in front of him.

His eyes were as deep as the nine nether abyss. Just looking into his gaze made one feel a shiver crawl up their spine.

“What… what do you want?”

The yellow-clothed martial artist asked with a fear-tinged voice.

They had indeed sent a sound transmission talisman requesting assistance from the sect. Although he thought his actions were discrete, he still felt weak at heart. He was afraid that Lin Ming would discover what they did and kill them all.

With them being severely wounded, it would only take Lin Ming a few breaths of time to kill them all.

The disparity was too great.

Lin Ming didn’t respond. He fiddled with the jade slip in his hands, spreading out his sense to the surrounding 100 miles.

His actions had the yellow-clothed martial artist exhaling in relief.

“This idiot hasn’t discovered anything at all. Just you wait! You are already dead!”

The yellow-clothed martial artist clenched his jaws, but on the surface he maintained a timid and terrified expression.

Time slowly passed. Soon, on the distant horizon, over ten small spots appeared in the skies, illuminated from behind by the sun.

These small shadows were extremely fast. In the blink of an eye they became as large as a palm in everyone’s sight. They were actually a group of flying dragons!

Each flying dragon had a wingspan that spread out over a hundred feet wide. Their claws were sharp and their teeth were gruesome. Each one resembled a vicious demon, terrifying to the extreme.

And standing on the backs of these flying dragons were many martial artists. These martial artists were all wearing sect clothing similar to the clothing that the martial artists who Lin Ming wounded had.

These were clearly reinforcements.

Whoosh! Whoosh! Whoosh!

As the flying dragons landed, they kicked up a giant sandstorm. On the backs of these flying dragons were more than 30 martial artists. The leader amongst them was a middle-aged man as thin as a string. His eyes were cold and gloomy and his momentum was intimidating. He obviously had a high status in the Imperial Beast Sect.

“Hahaha! Protector Sun, you finally made it!”

As the yellow-clothed martial artist with the gaping wound saw this middle-aged man, he began to recklessly laugh as if he had seen his savior. Not even the wounds marring his body were able to tamp down on his happiness.

“Protector Sun really came just on time!”

The other martial artists struggled to stand up. This included the martial artist that Lin Ming had seen spying on him and who had used the sound transmitting talisman to send a message.

The Imperial Beast Sect had come extremely fast. It seemed that they weren’t located too far away.

“It’s this little animal. He killed my black lizard and severely wounded us all, even stealing my material jade slip.”

The yellow-clothed man glared at Lin Ming, his expression full of spite and hate.

“That’s right, this is him. Protector Sun, don’t let him die easily. Make sure he suffers before that!”

“You were so arrogant just then, but now we’ll plant poisonous bugs in your body so you can experience what a pain worse than death is!”

As the reinforcements arrived, the originally heavily wounded martial artists all cried out with joy, their faces beaming with a fiendish delight.

“This is him? A human youth did this to you all? What a useless bunch.”

Protector Sun looked at Lin Ming, disdain written all over his face.

“Protector Sun be careful, this person is extremely fierce.” As the yellow-clothed martial artist saw Lin Ming remain as poised as before, without any panic on his face, he suddenly felt a bit weak at the knees.

“12 breaths of time…” Lin Ming suddenly said, “From the time that you notified the reinforcements to come here, you used a full 12 breaths of time. That was quite fast of them. These reinforcements must have laid down traps elsewhere to kill the martial artists of the Akashic Dream Battlefield, right?”

As Lin Ming swept his eyes over the crowd, he grasped the Phoenix Blood Spear and pointed it at the ground, without any haste or dread in his tone.

Hearing Lin Ming’s words, Protector Sun looked at Lin Ming with incredulous eyes. He sneered, “You’ve already stepped on the road to death and yet you’re so arrogant about yourself. Since you attacked my Imperial Beast Sect, that is already an unforgivable crime. Allow me to take your life!”

As Protector Sun spoke he immediately attacked right afterwards. Although he felt contempt at Lin Ming’s words, he still remained vigilant throughout. Thus, with this strike, he didn’t hold back at all.

Protector Sun drew out a heavy sword from his spatial ring. With a chop of the sword, a thin purple fog poured out.

Lin Ming didn’t need to look to sense that this sword contained a powerful inherent soul attack.

He used his foot to lift up the Phoenix Blood Spear. With a sweep of his spear, the power of thunder and fire erupted, like a red and purple wave gushing out together!

With a loud explosion, Protector Sun was sent flying backwards.

He cried out to the heavens in alarm. Lin Ming’s attack power had surpassed his comprehension. His protective spirit essence had been nothing but snow that rapidly shrank in the sunlight.

His face turned paper white. He wanted to take out an inscription symbol from his spatial ring, but the turbulent waves of thunder and fire had completely burnt through his spirit essence and had broken into his body, causing his organs and meridians to be damaged.

Peng!

Another explosive sound rang through the air.

Half of Protector Sun’s body had been baked black.

A pile of broken bones and chunks of meat went flying everywhere. Blood splashed all over the audience. Right now, Protector Sun’s breathing weakened with every second; he wouldn’t live for much longer.

“Protector Sun!”

The Imperial Beast Sect disciples were startled. They weren’t even able to react to this sudden change.

“How could this happen?”

In the eyes of the Imperial Beast Sect disciples, Protector Sun was an incomparably powerful existence. Not only was he an outstanding individual but his cultivation was profoundly deep.

After entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield, a martial artist’s cultivation was suppressed. But, their comprehension of Laws didn’t change and they were something that ordinary martial artists couldn’t deal with. Yet, Protector Sun had been instantly killed by someone!

“I was originally hoping you would all call some more people for me to earn some merit points, but in the end you only called 30 or so. How disappointing…”

Lin Ming’s words were like the whispers of a demon. As the yellow-clothed martial artist heard them, he felt all his hairs standing on end.

So this human had already realized they had sent a secret message, and the reason he intentionally waited here was to kill people and take their merit points?

“Everyone run! Scatter and run!”

The yellow-clothed martial artist screamed, as if he had just been awakened from a dream.

But at this time, Lin Ming finally moved. His speed reached an incredible velocity. The long spear in his hands was like the sickle of a death god. With every movement of his spear, someone’s head would fall down.

These people were all inferior to Protector Sun, so just where would they find the strength to revolt against Lin Ming?

Almost as soon as they met face to face, Protector Sun had suffered a most miserable death.

In the blink of an eye, blood dyed the floor and many Imperial Beast Sect disciples flew away in all directions as they tried to escape. But, these people were all pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear light!

Puff! Puff!

A flying corpse fell down from the skies. The scene was extremely terrifying.

“De… demon…”

Just before dying, the yellow-clothed martial artist spoke out some final words as he choked on his blood.

Lin Ming picked up his spear and directly pierced through the yellow-clothed martial artist’s heart.

In just ten breaths of time, he had solved the battlefield problem.

Lin Ming appreciatively held the jade slip in his hands. This jade slip that the yellow-clothed martial artist handed him could be called an unexpected harvest.

Chapter 1805 – Weeping Blood God Springs

After Lin Ming killed the disciples from the Imperial Beast Sect, he felt energy dissipate from their corpses and merge into the entry token he carried with him.

These energies formed tiny motes of light within the entry token.

As Lin Ming probed the entry token with his sense, information reflected back into his mind – he now had a total of 2100 merit points.

“Only 2100 merit points. Compared to the merit points required for a golden page, this isn’t even a drop in the bucket.”

Lin Ming shook his head.

These 2100 merit points would be divided by his total age when the three year deadline came. In truth, he had only obtained a dozen some points.

And to exchange for the golden page he needed a billion merit points. The difference was far too great.

“The stronger the opponents I kill, the more merit points I’ll obtain.”

Lin Ming could feel that of the nearly 40 Imperial Beast Sect disciples he just killed, the one to give him the most merit points was that Protector Sun; Protector Sun had given him almost a thousand merit points. As for that yellow-clothed youth, he had given several hundred merit points and the remaining people had only given several dozen merit points.

The worst of all these people had only given him single digits merit points; it was a completely negligible number.

In other words, if Lin Ming wanted enough points to exchange for the golden page then he would need to kill top powerhouses without end. This included the Great World Kings, half-step Empyreans, and even Empyrean powerhouses here.

The higher the original cultivation of the person he killed, the more merit points he would receive.

“I wonder how many merit points I can get from killing an Empyrean?”

Lin Ming whispered to himself in anticipation. Two Empyreans had entered this Akashic Dream Battlefield – Chaos Demon God and Empyrean Myriad Ghost.

If he could slay these two fellows then they would surely give him a considerable number of merit points.

“I’m quite lucky. During my first time entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield there were also two Empyreans that joined in. I really might be able to collect the full billion merit points required. However, this Akashic Dream Battlefield is far too large. It won’t be easy to find them.”

Lin Ming thought to himself. If Zenith Palace were to know of his thoughts, it was impossible to tell what their reactions would be.

Zenith Palace would be doing everything in their power to avoid these Empyrean powerhouses but Lin Ming actually wanted to search for them on his own initiative.

“The Akashic Dream Battlefield is only open for three years. I can’t just aimlessly wander around. If I continue at my current speed, I won’t be able to gather a billion merit points before the Akashic Dream Battlefield ends. I have to look for some place where many powerhouses gather so I can go wild and kill them all. For instance, some place where heavenly materials are born…”

As Lin Ming was thinking this, he put away the merit point token in his hands and took out the jade slip that the yellow-clothed youth had passed to him. As he swept his mind through the jade slip, information rapidly appeared in his mind.

“Soul Cave… Undying Ruins…”

Lin Ming soon selected these two places where heavenly materials would appear. He chose them because they were the two ruins that were easiest to find.

In particular, the Soul Cave was in an almost fixed position.

Lin Ming activated his movement technique and shot straight towards the Soul Cave.

His speed wasn’t too fast and he encountered several ambushes along the way.

Those that tried to sneak attack him were all martial artists from small sects. They gathered in groups and had been lying hidden in ambush, wanting to secretly attack martial artists that passed by and take their merit points.

Chi chi chi!

As Lin Ming flew through a mountain valley, several sword lights shot out from the underbrush, forming a web of sword lights that covered him.

Lin Ming had already noticed these people long before they noticed him.

He flicked his fingers and sent spear lights shooting out.

With a cacophony of miserable cries, all of those people who tried to ambush Lin Ming were instantly killed.

In a mere moment, he had obtained another thousand plus merit points.

According to the rules of the Akashic Dream Battlefield, after Lin Ming killed a martial artist, he would obtain a fixed number of merit points based on their skills and cultivation, and also a portion of the merit points they had accumulated.

Thus, as Lin Ming killed these people who had also slaughtered many others, he obtained more points than usual.

“Hey friend, your skills aren’t too bad!”

After Lin Ming killed these ambushers, a voice called out to him.

Lin Ming turned his head to see a purple-clothed girl flying towards him as she rode a rainbow luan. Following close behind her were seven martial artists in tight-fitting black combat clothes.

These black-clothed martial artists stepped through space, their steps vague and their auras deep and powerful. Lin Ming was surprised. He suspected that before these seven black-clothed martial artists had their cultivations suppressed, they had been at the World King realm.

Although it wasn’t easy to distinguish a person’s cultivation realm because their cultivation was suppressed in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, it was possible to approximate their original cultivations from their auras.

“Seven World Kings…”

Lin Ming was startled. The truth was that he didn’t place any World King powerhouses in his eyes. But, if this young girl could have a retinue of seven World Kings following her around in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, this meant that she had a considerably high status!

Perhaps not even a core disciple of an Empyrean Holy Land would have such a great lineup of guards.

Could she come from a True Divinity Holy Land?

Lin Ming’s heart turned cold. The seven universes of the spiritas was truly a land of crouching tigers and hidden dragons, with masters all around. It wouldn’t be strange if a core disciple of a True Divinity Holy Land were to appear at the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

“If she really is a disciple of a True Divinity Holy Land, I might be able to find out something about Sheng Mei from her.”

Lin Ming immediately developed the thought of befriending this young purple-clothed girl that had come from nowhere.

However, he maintained a vigilant guard.

“My name is Lin Muk. I wonder who this miss is…?”

“Violet Cloud.”

The purple-clothed girl briefly responded. It was impossible to find out anything valuable from this information.

“Good brother, do you plan on going to the Soul Cave?”

The purple-clothed girl looked up and down at Lin Ming, sizing him up. She clearly recognized that Lin Ming was a human. For a human to achieve this level of strength was bewildering.

Moreover, she wasn’t able to distinguish what Lin Ming’s cultivation had been before it was suppressed. This left her even more puzzled.

“Yes.”

Lin Ming didn’t hide anything. This was the road leading to the Soul Cave and he wasn’t too far away right now.

“How about we go together? Not only are there many masters in the Soul Cave but there is also a tremendous number of nightmare beasts. If we cooperate, our combat strength will be much higher.”

Lin Ming originally wanted to get to know this purple-clothed girl and dig out some information about Sheng Mei from her. He readily agreed, “Sure!”

With Lin Ming joining them, the group expanded to nine people.

“Princess, why are you having an outsider join us? And he isn’t a spiritas, nor do we know what his character is like. In this trip to the Soul Cave he might not be able to play any role and yet we will have to split a portion of our treasures to him.”

A black-clothed martial artist asked from behind Violet Cloud.

“With another person that means we are that much stronger. We will have to face many opponents this time, and this human is quite strong if he was able to instantly kill those martial artists. With your cultivation suppressed, you can’t do that, right? He will be greatly helpful to our group… as for treasures, those are things that aren’t even in our hands. If we can’t obtain any harvests then there will be nothing to divide anyways. It's too early to be worrying about something as trivial as dividing treasures…”

As the purple-clothed girl spoke, the black-robed World King could only silently nod.

In all fairness, this human was indeed strong. After these seven World Kings had their cultivations suppressed, they had to admit that none of them were Lin Ming’s match.

“This is a human genius; I wonder what influence he comes from. What a strange sight.”

The wilderness was vast and endless. An infinite swamp stretched to the horizon with tall patches of grass littering the landscape. The occasional roar of nightmare beasts resounded through the skies, making one’s heart race.

“In front of us is the Soul Cave. This is an extremely strange spirit land. In the past, a divine object once appeared within it – the Weeping Blood God Springs.”

The information of the purple-clothed girl was clearly far more detailed than that of the Imperial Beast Sect.

Lin Ming perked up. Weeping Blood God Springs?

He had seen this name on the Emperor God Wall before. It was said to be an incomparably precious divine substance that could be used to refine True Divinity level pills. It was something that could even tempt True Divinities!

“What is the Weeping Blood God Springs?”

Lin Ming couldn’t help but ask. Something that could stir the desires of a True Divinity was no trifling matter.

The purple-clothed girl responded, “This Soul Cave can breed spirit source. In ancient times, because this spirit source was far too dense, it finally gathered together and formed liquid; in other words, a soul springs. As for the Weeping Blood God Springs, it is rumored that in ancient times a peerless God King mixed in his own blood within the soul springs, transforming it into what it is now. But, the Weeping Blood God Springs developed a wisdom of its own and escaped into the earth, completely vanishing from sight. After that, no one was able to find it.”

The purple-clothed girl shook her head. Lin Ming was startled upon hearing this story.

Liquid formed from spirit source? Then, just how rich and pure was this spirit source?

In the past when Lin Ming entered the Asura Road’s final trial, he had experienced spirit source himself. This was an extremely important source strength for all soul forging martial artists.

Lin Ming didn’t doubt that Empyrean Divine Dream’s spirit source was also obtained within the Soul World.

As for the ancient peerless God King that the purple-clothed girl spoke of, could it have been the one who created the Akashic Dream Universe, the mysterious first ancestor of the spiritas?

Chapter 1806 – The Soul Cave

Although the Soul Cave was called a cave, the truth was that it was a massive canyon. It was situated between two mountains that were hundreds of thousands of feet high and filled with a faint purple fog all year round. It was an extremely mystical place.

At this time, outside of the Soul Cave, a massive number of martial artists had gathered.

These people came from influences all over the Soul World. Lin Ming glanced over them and didn’t see anyone from Zenith Palace.

This was just because Zenith Palace was far too weak and didn’t have the qualifications to enter the Soul Cave. To try and venture into the Soul Cave with their level of strength was no different from seeking death.

“Violet Sun Divine Kingdom, hehe… I knew that the Violet Cloud Princess wouldn’t miss such a momentous event.”

In the crowd of people, a strange-looking creature spoke up.

This life form was twice the height of the average person and had golden purple scales covering his body. There was also a pair of curved horns jutting out from his head.

Lin Ming was startled. Just what sort of race was this?

From looks alone, this being seemed to be from the monster race, but Lin Ming could feel that this golden purple being was from a race different from the Divine Realm’s monster race. Rather than monster essence, this creature emitted a dense soul energy.

“This person is…?”

Lin Ming asked with a sound transmission.

“He comes from the spirit race and he is the spirit race’s Purple Chestnut King.”

Violet Cloud briefly explained.

“Spirit race?” Lin Ming repeated. This was the first time he had heard of such a race.

“They are descendants of an ancient race. You’ve never heard of them before?”

The Violet Cloud Princess looked at Lin Ming with puzzled eyes, not caring about it too much. Every universe of the 33 Heavens was occupied by different mixes of races. Besides humans, saints, and spiritas, there were also many other minor races that often only occupied a part of a universe. It wasn’t strange if one didn’t know about one race or another.

The current spirit race was one such example. Even though the spirit race didn’t have many members remaining, they were still a very powerful race that had produced many peak Empyreans in the last billion years. Even now they were being supported by a peak Empyrean.

A peak Empyrean was an existence just beneath a True Divinity. No one in any universe could underestimate them.

The Purple Chestnut King glanced at Lin Ming once and then ignored him. Instead, he called out to his many followers. These followers consisted of powerhouses from other races, but right now they all obeyed the orders of the Purple Chestnut King.

The members of the spirit race had a talent that surpassed that of the humans, saints, and spiritas. It wasn’t an exaggeration to say they were favored by the heavens, and this Purple Chestnut King was a particularly outstanding individual of his race.

Behind the Purple Chestnut King were several powerful influences. Amongst them was a handsome and heroic spiritas youth who led over a thousand disciples here. These disciples all had a beyond average level of skill, and when combined together was able to form a terrifying strength.

They all noticed the arrival of the Violet Cloud Princess.

“We’ve just enough people. Open the array!”

The robed spiritas elite spoke up. Everyone began preparing themselves. The purple fog around the entrance of the Soul Cave was itself a variation of a force field. In order to break this force field, one needed a formidable strength.

Right now, everyone present, whether they were a Great World King or a young elite, all had their cultivations suppressed to the Divine Lord realm. It was impossible to break through the force field with the strength of a single person; everyone had to join forces.

For a time, the many elites present attacked with their followers. Brilliant beams of light cut through the skies and impacted against the purple fog at the entrance of the Soul Cave.

Chi chi chi!

The purple fog began melting away. A moment later, a giant hole was torn in it.

“Let’s go!”

Many elites began rushing in, their followers right behind them. This Soul Cave was extremely broad and could easily fit several thousands of people walking in side by side.

Roar!

As soon as people began entering the Soul Cave, ghostly green eyes began appearing in the darkness; these were the shimmering eyes of the wild beasts that lived here.

“It’s soul beasts.”

Some martial artist said. Soul beasts were also called nightmare beasts, and were the energy life form monsters that existed in the Akashic Dream Universe.

These monsters were divided into the weak and the strong. Those that were stronger even had the strength of a World King. For these martial artists who had their cultivation suppressed to the Divine Lord level, it was impossible to face these creatures.

The howls of wolves filled the air and Lin Ming got a good sight of these monsters. The leader was a gray wolf the size of a giant cow; these were called dream devouring wolves.

Without the need for orders, many of the martial artists directly lashed out. For a time, countless brilliant lights filled the air. Lin Ming was also one of those attacking.

He thrust out spear lights with his fingers, piercing through the heads of several gray wolves and instantly killing them.

And as he killed these dream devouring wolves, Lin Ming noticed that the number of merit points in his token was gradually increasing. Killing these soul beasts also gave merit points.

Without a doubt, the stronger a soul beast was, the more merit points they would give.

The groups of people continued forwards, leaving corpses in their wake.

Some martial artists flushed red, the light in their eyes becoming increasingly bright. It was obvious they could also feel the number of merit points in their tokens increasing and this clearly had an intense stimulating effect on them.

All of a sudden, Lin Ming noticed a strange aura rushing towards him from up front.

Looking up ahead, he could see that at the very front of the group, the Purple Chestnut King and the robed spiritas elite had both paused where they were.

In the increasingly narrow cave, a massive carved copper gate had appeared.

This copper gate seemed to be wet, and exuded a mystical aura that seemed to exist all year round. Carved upon this copper gate were the heads of two fierce ghosts, each with demonic features and vile green fangs.

Strange ghostly sounds passed out from the copper gate, as if 10,000 fierce ghosts were wildly screaming and crying from within.

No one knew why but they all felt their hearts speed up. Even Lin Ming noticed a strange atmosphere falling over everyone.

He noticed that upon arriving here, everyone’s eyes became far more focused and cautious.

“This is the Gate of Ghosts and Gods. It is an extremely bizarre place within the Soul Cave, and the inside is filled with perils…”

Violet Cloud’s sound transmission suddenly popped up in Lin Ming’s mind.

“Thank you.” Lin Ming replied. Out of everyone here, only Lin Ming had an almost nonexistent understanding of the Soul Cave.

“The Gate of Ghosts and Gods has come. After entering, there is a danger that your soul will be torn apart and your main body’s spiritual sea might even be injured… if you don’t want to die then hurry up and screw off!”

The Purple Chestnut King said from the front. An eerie light shot out from his pupils as he traced the contours of the thick copper gate.

The death that waited within also meant that one would be removed from the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Although this wasn’t true death, many of the martial artists present were unwilling to see this happen.

Moreover, the Purple Chestnut King even said that there was a chance that one’s true spiritual sea would suffer damage upon death.

Even so, no one left. Anyone that was able to arrive at this step could be called a hero of their generation. How could they leave so easily?

The Purple Chestnut King gave his warning and didn’t glance back to see anyone’s reaction. Countless runes shimmered in his palm like a galaxy. Slowly, a ten foot high blue palm materialized in front of him, emitting a vast aura of Laws.

Lin Ming’s eyebrow arched up and he gazed at the Purple Chestnut King’s strong and tall back. With Lin Ming’s current comprehension of many different Laws, he could feel just how mighty the power of Laws in front of him was.

He made a rapid judgement in his heart. This Purple Chestnut King should have an amazing level of talent to begin with and his comprehension of Laws even surpassed that of an ordinary World King.

The Purple Chestnut King raised that great blue palm. Then, like a meteor striking the earth, he repeatedly smashed it onto the ghost heads carved into the copper gate.

Pa! Pa! Pa!

Strange sounds rang out. Like something cracked open in the copper gate, the gate began to slowly open.

Bang!

All of a sudden, a black fog so thick that it was substantialized began gushing out, followed by the roars of maddened and fierce ghosts. Within the black fog were the blurry phantoms of countless dead spirits.

These dead spirit phantoms were all cruel and vicious. But among them there were spiritas, saints, humans, and even those from all sorts of different races.

“Kill!”

The crowd roared out together. Without any mercy, the groups of martial artists slaughtered their way forwards.

These groups of dead spirit phantoms were clearly much stronger than the soul beasts.

The Heretical God Tree swayed within Lin Ming. He reached into himself with his mind and drew out a wisp of heavenly tribulation fire into his palm. A flame lotus suddenly erupted around him, rumbling towards a dead spirit phantom.

Beyond Lin Ming’s expectations, the dead spirit phantom had thrust out a hand and summoned turbulent fluctuations of soul force. As this soul force collided with the flame lotus there was a fierce explosion.

“These dead spirit phantoms are from those who’ve wandered in here. The dead martial artists here still have their spirit marks; be careful.”

Beside Lin Ming, the Violet Cloud Princess began to overflow with layers upon layers of mystical purple energy. As the dead spirit phantoms collided with this purple energy, all of them exploded.

Lin Ming remained alert. A light layer of dragon scales covered his fist and his blood vitality surged within him. He punched out at an incoming dead spirit phantom, causing it to burst apart.

As the dead spirit phantom exploded, the Violet Cloud Princess unconsciously glanced at Lin Ming’s dragon scale-covered fist.

Just entering the Gate of Ghosts and Gods, over 10 martial artists had perished.

However, Lin Ming, the Violet Cloud Princess, and her seven World King followers were all safe.

These nine people guarded each other, working in tandem to steadily enter deeper and deeper into the Soul Cave.

As the fierce killing within the Soul Cave became increasingly savage and unbridled, the difference in strength amongst the various groups began to slowly reveal itself.

The Purple Chestnut King, heroic spiritas elite, and Lin Ming and the Violet Cloud Princess’ group of nine pushed forwards at the forefront.

Following 10,000 feet behind them were other groups of people.

As they continued forwards, only then did Lin Ming discover that this Soul Cave was infinitely deep and profound; it wasn’t as simple as a mere cave.

In here, there were even underground rivers and underground volcanoes. All sorts of bizarre monsters appeared, challenging them at every step.

Along the way, Lin Ming plucked a black and shiny monster spirit flower from a giant fallen skeleton. This was said to be a spirit medicine that could help a spiritas break into the Holy Lord realm.

Lin Ming carefully put it away. Although he didn’t have any use for it now, he could definitely trade it with a spiritas in the future for some medicine he could use.

The Violet Cloud Princess and the others also found their own harvests.

“What is that?”

As they continued walking, Lin Ming suddenly saw the peak of an underground mountain in front of him. There seemed to be some great sun shining high in the air, emitting a dim light.

This brilliance was shrouded with layers of dim haze and mist-covered clouds.

Then, Lin Ming froze. He could faintly feel the strength of a mountain pressing down on him, pushing so hard that his spiritual sea shook and his breath caught in his throat.

Chapter 1807 - Spiritual Storm

“What a powerful soul force!”

Lin Ming’s heart raced.

With his own eyes he could see a wild and reckless soul energy violently spinning around, forming a purple storm. Just by approaching this storm, he felt as if his spiritual sea would be shattered by the powerful soul force.

Not too far away, the Violet Cloud Princess, Purple Chestnut King, and the others also stopped where they were, a solemn look on their faces. Their every movement and gesture appeared to be hindered, as if they were mired in some swamp; it was clear that their souls were being suppressed just as much if not more than Lin Ming’s.

“Mm? This is…?”

Although Lin Ming’s soul force was suppressed, his divine sense remained as sharp and formidable as before.

He could feel that at the peak of this mountain, there was a dense rain and dew that contained an intense aura of divinity, making every pore on his body open wide with longing.

He wanted to step onto the peak of this mountain and obtain that rain and dew.

However, just as he took a step forwards, the spiritual storm that enveloped his spiritual sea began to flare up again, becoming increasingly heavy.

Lin Ming flushed red and his breathing turned heavy.

“We’ve reached Limitless God Mountain. This is a famous spiritual mountain located in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. It is said that there was once an unrivalled powerhouse that stepped atop this mountain and left behind an unsurpassed inheritance. However, this mountain is strange. There is a powerful spiritual storm that wraps around it and it can even affect your true body’s soul source… once, there was a powerhouse who tried to forcefully make his way up Limitless God Mountain, but his soul source received a grievous wound and he turned into an idiot…

“If a human were to try and enter, it would be especially perilous…”

The Violet Cloud Princess glanced at Lin Ming. Although she acknowledged that Lin Ming was strong and his comprehension of Laws was outstanding, as a human he simply couldn’t compete with the soul force of a spiritas. In terms of resisting the pressure of this spiritual storm, a spiritas had an immeasurable advantage over a human.

“Thank you for the advice, Princess.” Lin Ming took a deep breath. He sank his energy into his dantian and guarded his divine soul to withstand this massive pressure.

At the same time, the Purple Chestnut King and the heroic young spiritas emitted a dim purple halo of light. They used the power of their spiritual seas to resist this spiritual storm.

As they stepped forwards, excitement began to appear on their faces. It was clear just how eager they were for this soul rain.

The Purple Chestnut King was from the spirit race thus he had a natural superiority when it came to the soul. In this, he even surpassed the spiritas.

On this Limitless God Mountain, he had a nearly unsurpassable advantage!

At this time, Lin Ming took a sudden step backwards. A black vortex rose up in his spiritual sea.

Clang!

Like a divine weapon leaving its sheath, Lin Ming erupted with a soul force and momentum that soared into the heavens. Like a spear that was able to penetrate through the world, he pierced a hole through the leaden pressure of this spiritual storm.

Lin Ming calmly stepped forwards, one foot at a time.

“Eh?”

Seeing this, the Violet Cloud Princess could tell that some sort of change had occurred within Lin Ming. He was now even able to resist the inexhaustible spiritual storm that was being released from Limitless God Mountain.

Weng! Weng! Weng!

From within Lin Ming’s spiritual sea, a blue spear rose up, roaring like a dragon that had awakened from a deep slumber. It howled forwards, carrying with it an overwhelming potential as it smashed into the spiritual storm spinning in the skies.

This blue spear carried an incredible spiritual strength and exuded a matchless momentum. It was the large success blue soul battle spirit that Lin Ming had formed in the past.

In the Akashic Dream Battlefield, the Laws had suppressed Lin Ming’s cultivation to the Divine Lord realm, and even his mental strength and soul force had greatly diminished. Even so, his battle spirit remained just as strong.

A battle spirit could attack soul force; it was an extremely strange and powerful tool. In the past, Lin Ming had used his battle spirit to cut down many powerful foes.

His large success blue soul battle spirit also carried with it grandmist energy; its quality far surpassed other battle spirits of the same level.

Bang!

The spiritual storm cracked open. The pressure on Lin Ming’s spiritual sea also relaxed.

With his blue soul battle spirit cutting a path through his spiritual sea, even though his suppressed soul force was weaker than that of the Violet Cloud Princess and the others, Lin Ming was actually not any slower than them.

One step at a time, the closer he approached Limitless God Mountain the more intense the spiritual storm he faced was.

At the same time, within his spiritual sea, his blue soul battle spirit was engaged in a fierce battle with the spiritual force field, slowly supporting Lin Ming’s steps forward.

In front of Lin Ming, the Purple Chestnut King already had beads of sweat dripping down his forehead. Even so, he maintained his brave and daring demeanor. The only difference was that a sharp light flashed in his eyes as he furiously struggled with the spiritual force field from Limitless God Mountain.

“That human is also following?”

Suddenly, the Purple Chestnut King noticed that just three steps behind him, the white-clothed human youth was following him at a leisurely pace. In fact, there wasn’t even a drop of sweat marring his face.

Although the human was slow, the Purple Chestnut King hadn’t been able to leave him behind.

The Purple Chestnut King’s expression froze as he frowned. How was this possible? A human also arrived at this point?

Although the Violet Cloud Princess was a woman, she was still a proud child of heaven. The Purple Chestnut King recognized her qualifications to walk side by side with him. But now, a human also caught up with his pace.

In surprise, a gloomy light shined in the Purple Chestnut King’s eyes.

He was an incredibly, insufferably arrogant person, and was considered a genius of the spirit race. Even so, he was being followed by a mere human which he felt was simply impossible. A human’s advantage lay in their ability to cultivate energy but they were neophytes when it came to the soul, so why was he able to keep up?

From beside Lin Ming, the heroic spiritas youth also glanced at Lin Ming, an unfriendly light in his eyes.

At this point, only a sparse few people were able to make it to this distance.

The weaklings of the groups also tried to reach Limitless God Mountain, but just as they stepped foot at the base of the mountain, they screamed out loud as they were crushed and swept away by the spiritual force field.

There were also some who feared the spiritual pressure coming from Limitless God Mountain and hesitated in moving forwards. They looked towards the advancing individuals with envy in their eyes but they still didn’t dare to take the risk of going forwards.

Some people could see that at the front of the leading group, there was a human youth.

“How could there even be a human climbing up? That’s really… really…”

The martial artist didn’t know what to say. As spiritas martial artists, they had lost to a human when it came to soul force.

This was like a group of chess masters deciding to play against a checkers master, but the end result was that all those chess masters were defeated by the checkers master. This was an utter shame on their name.

None of them had any face left!

“Don’t worry, in the Soul World there is no space for a human to enjoy glory. He will likely fail halfway, and even if he can reach the end he will inevitably consume a great deal of energy. If this human obtains any lucky chances we can kill him together and steal them away.” Someone indignantly huffed.

Finally, Lin Ming slowly stepped halfway up the mountain.

The scene in front of him had changed.

He had stepped into a hazy pall of light rain.

This light rain was the dim fog he had seen from the base of the mountain.

After being touched by this light sprinkle, Lin Ming felt the rain drill into his body, flooding into his spiritual sea and rapidly restoring his spent soul force. Moreover, it constantly nourished his soul and expanded his spiritual sea.

“What a rich and potent… spiritual strength. This is rain formed from spirit source!” Lin Ming immediately understood just what this light rain was.

Only spirit source so rich that it had substantialized to rain could rapidly supplement his soul force like this.

Even his battle spirit was vitalized by this spirit source; it grew larger, becoming increasingly fierce and powerful.

Lin Ming didn’t hurriedly rush to the top. Instead, he looked around at his surroundings.

He discovered that this light drizzle of rain was formed from a murmuring stream on the side of the god mountain that constantly splashed up.

This stream was magnificent beyond compare. Although it splashed into the skies, it didn’t emit any sound at all.

Wherever the stream flowed, all the mountain stone around it was stained a crystalline jet black and emitted an extremely strong soul force.

“Those are peak quality soul crystals, just a little of that is a priceless treasure.” Lin Ming’s pupils shrank as he saw the soul crystals.

Before long, his eyes moved away from the soul crystals. He sat down where he was and began meditating. Like a whale sucking in water, he breathed in deeply, breathing in the wandering spirit source mist around him, allowing it to flood into his body where he absorbed it.

As he did this, the Violet Cloud Princess, Purple Chestnut King, and the others had almost simultaneously chosen the same action.

After all, no matter how it was said, this spirit source mist was the most important of treasures. It could nourish and cleanse one’s soul force and even enhance one’s cultivation. It was far more important than some external treasure.

After an incense stick of time, Lin Ming slowly opened his eyes.

He noticed that the soul force in his spiritual sea had nearly doubled. A great deal of spirit source mist that hadn’t yet been fully refined hovered above his spiritual sea, forming something akin to a layer of defense.

It cleared his senses, making him feel refreshed. When facing the spiritual force field released by Limitless God Mountain, Lin Ming felt much more assured.

“Humph.” At this time, a cold cough sounded out from in front of Lin Ming.

The tall Purple Chestnut King coldly jeered at Lin Ming, a disgusted light clear in his blood red pupils. This Limitless God Mountain had been formed through the countless years, and a great deal of the spirit source mist had been absorbed by him, Lin Ming, the Violet Cloud Princess, and the spiritas youth.

If this human wasn’t here than the Purple Chestnut King would have clearly been able to absorb more spirit source mist. At the very least, he was unhappy that he had to divvy up a portion of this lucky chance to a human like Lin Ming. He didn’t feel happy about this at all.

However, he didn’t say anything. He faintly felt that Lin Ming was not a peaceful or kind-hearted individual. There was no point in mindlessly fighting Lin Ming right now.

He continued advancing forwards.

“I never imagined that as a human, you would have such attainments in the aspect of battle spirits.” The Violet Cloud Princess’ words echoed in Lin Ming’s mind.

Lin Ming had revealed all sorts of peculiarities the longer she traveled with him, leaving her marveling with surprise every time. She thought that perhaps this human had some great secrets on him; she really didn’t know where he had come from.

“If there is another lucky chance, let’s join together and fight for it. I’m not on good ground with that Purple Chestnut King; we can be considered enemies.”

The Violet Cloud Princess tried to pull Lin Ming over to her side. At this time, because of the spiritual storm, her followers weren’t able to catch up to them. With an ally by her side, that meant her team would be that much stronger.

Lin Ming nodded. Without saying much else, he quickly moved forwards.

Chapter 1808 –Kirin Fruit

The closer one neared to the peak, the more powerful the spiritual storm that was released by Limitless God Mountain.

At the end, even Lin Ming felt some formidable strength pressing down in his spiritual sea and trying to force him down the mountain.

Luckily, he had swallowed a tremendous amount of spirit source mist just a while ago and was able to support the continued use of soul force, allowing him to slowly climb upwards.

Although everyone was trying their best to climb up, they were all within a close distance of each other.

As Lin Ming almost reached the peak, he saw a brilliant light splash down at him as if a sun was rising just up ahead.

As this light fell onto his body, it warmed him and nourished his spiritual sea.

“What light is this? Just by touching me it can nourish my soul force?” Lin Ming was amazed.

He followed the path of the light and saw a rumbling stream of water falling down from the top of the mountain.

Beneath this great flow of water was a giant rock.

In a crevice within the rock, a fist-sized medicinal herb grew. It was covered with dew and emitted a blinding light. Its entire body was crystal bright and dazzling.

That brilliant sunlight had originated from this medicinal herb.

Shua shua shua –

The eyes of the four people here, Lin Ming’s included, completely fell atop that spirit fruit.

They could see shadows wriggling atop the fruit, as if there was a small life being bred within.

“That is a… kirin?”

Lin Ming stared at the shadow in the fruit. Because the light was far too bright, he could see through the walls of the fruit and make out the fine scales and mysterious pattern of Laws within. He could feel that there was a kirin being bred within this fruit.

Was this a hatching kirin fruit?

“What kind of fruit is this? It’s far too mysterious! It actually transformed and is ready to evolve into a living spirit body… the medicinal fragrance is terrifyingly rich.” Lin Ming’s heart began to shake.

Soon, he understood what had happened. The faint traces of spirit source crashing down from the spirit stream had washed over this rock for endless days and nights, slowly accumulating atop it.

Without a doubt, this fruit contained a massive amount of the purest spirit source strength. Moreover, it also possessed a uniquely divine substance; it was incomparably precious.

One after another, more and more people withstood the spiritual storm blowing down from Limitless God Mountain and approached.

As they saw the mystical fruit that was breeding a kirin within, everyone’s breath caught in their throats. A greedy light flashed in their eyes.

A short old spiritas man couldn’t restrain himself. He raised his hands and rushed towards the kirin fruit.

But as his hands reached out, a pair of golden purple arms came drilling out from the center of the old man’s chest.

Afterwards, the old man cried out in pain and sorrow and his entire body was torn in half. Blood, muscles, and pieces of intestines were flung to the floor.

The one who attacked the old man was the Purple Chestnut King. His purple red hair danced recklessly in the air and a severe light shined in his pupils. Spirit race powerhouses almost ten feet tall stood behind the Purple Chestnut King. As his hands dripped with blood, his aura became swift and fierce, arousing fear and alarm like a wandering death god.

“You think you are good enough for this treasure? It seems you don’t know what it means to die.”

The Purple Chestnut King disdainfully said.

“Heh, the treasure belongs to whoever has the skill to obtain it. Purple Chestnut King, do you think you can obtain it alone?”

Those that were able to arrive here were no ordinary martial artists. After the Purple Chestnut King’s ruthless and cruel actions, although everyone remained vigilant they didn’t feel any fear at all. Some considerably strong people almost simultaneously broke through the layers of pressure coming down from Limitless God Mountain and hurtled towards the kirin fruit.

In a moment, everyone further approached Limitless God Mountain.

At this time, the spiritual storm spread out, becoming far fiercer. In this stormy sea, everyone was beaten up and whipped by the wild winds and the world seemed to shake.

Someone cried out in misery as their head exploded. They weren’t able to withstand the violent spiritual storm and died on the spot.

However, those heroes with true foundations were not blocked by Limitless God Mountain’s spiritual storm.

“It seems you all want to die.”

Seeing so many rush forwards at once, a callous light flashed in the Purple Chestnut King’s eyes. He had already seen just how precious this kirin fruit was; it was absolutely a treasure that would even cause Empyreans to relentlessly battle for it. He wanted to possess this treasure alone and considered anyone who wanted to take it his enemy.

On his back, a strange soul force shimmered as millions of runes appeared. These runes grew up and gathered, forming into a pair of light wings that were ten feet long.

Ping! Ping! Ping! Ping! Ping! Ping!

The light wings flapped. The tall and formidable Purple Chestnut King had whipped up a tornado.

At the same time, he sped towards those six or seven people that were rushing forwards and punched out at all of them.

Brilliant purple light shot into the world. Soul force surged and a series of explosions rang out. Some nearby spirit trees and plants were dislodged in the fierce impact, as if they had been cut down by a sickle.

This scene caused everyone to suck in a breath of cold air. After all, these spirit trees and flowers hadn’t even broken at the top of Limitless God Mountain, but in that brief exchange just now they had been torn down by that horrifying strength.

Some people were panic-stricken. The Purple Chestnut King was actually stopping all those who dared to rush forwards and was eliminating them all. In a one on one battle, perhaps no one was his match.

Violet Cloud had also been blocked by the Purple Chestnut King’s punch just now. Her thin eyebrows pressed together as she felt somewhat insulted. After many years of not seeing him, the Purple Chestnut King’s strength had risen even further.

She sent Lin Ming a sound transmission, “Brother Lin, let’s attack together! The Purple Chestnut King is from the spirit race and is a favored pet of the heavens. It is said that he is at the half-step World King realm and even then he is able to jump ranks to defeat a Great World King. In the future he is someone that might become a peak Empyrean! If we join forces we can suppress him together, and after that we can divide the spoils equally.”

Violet Cloud put forth her conditions. However, Lin Ming shook his head, “No need.”

His figure flashed like gods and ghosts. He fluttered over alone to that kirin fruit.

He had been closely observing the kirin fruit all this time and didn’t rush into action, so the Purple Chestnut King hadn’t noticed him.

Seeing Lin Ming’s movements, the Violet Cloud Princess was dumbfounded. She didn’t think that Lin Ming would refuse her reasonable terms and run towards the kirin fruit alone.

Did he think he was stronger than the Purple Chestnut King?

Seeing Lin Ming leisurely move forwards, the Purple Chestnut King fiendishly grinned. Killing intent erupted from his body; he had long been wanting to kill this human brat.

From his body, monstrous ripples of gold spread out, covering the area for hundreds of feet around him. The golden light began to sweep towards Lin Ming like the waves of the ocean.

Every golden ripple contained a terrifying number of shimmering runes.

Feeling the terrifying golden ripples rush towards him, Lin Ming didn’t show any expression at all. He was able to immediately see that this was the Purple Chestnut King’s unique force field. If a weaker martial artist were to enter this force field then they wouldn’t be able to die even if they wanted too. Even then, he wouldn’t be able to display his true combat strength either.

Lin Ming’s thoughts focused. From his inner world, a loud rumbling sound spread out.

In a vast sea of true essence, three vast and boundless palaces floated up, slowly appearing as they were lifted by three massive stars.

Each palace shined with dazzling starlight. As this endless mystic strength was released, mystical lines of the dao appeared, seeming to resemble a mysterious and unreachable goal.

As these three palaces floated in Lin Ming’s inner world, they completely suppressed the force field that the Purple Chestnut King had released.

These three palaces were the three Dao Palaces Lin Ming had opened.

Every Dao Palace possessed the mark of the Great Dao. Although they couldn’t be thrown out towards enemies, they were still more than enough to resist the impact left by the force field in his inner world.

Lin Ming felt the pressure on him lighten up. The Phoenix Blood Spear shot forwards like a dragon swimming through the ocean, running out from his spatial ring and roaring in the air, causing the surrounding soul force to wildly shiver.

Lin Ming’s mind stirred. Endless strength erupted from his body and man and spear became one. The energy within his hand was like thousands of suns imploding together. Waves of spear strikes gathered together, forming a radiant column of light that was unstoppable.

In an instant, Lin Ming pierced out with his spear tens of thousands of time, each spear strike contained a near endless mystic strength, completely crushing the golden ripples to nothing.

The endless golden ripples twisted with the sea of spear light and were then completely submerged.

“W…what!?”

The Purple Chestnut King cried out. By the time he discovered something was wrong, it was already too late for him.

Sou! Sou! Sou!

Infinite howling spear phantoms appeared in front of him, as if they were passing down a summons from the true god of death.

From the back, the Purple Chestnut King felt his scalp tingle with fear. He exploded with a roar and spat out a mouthful of essence energy and blood vitality.

The drops of blood condensed in the void, forming a thick wall of blood.

He cried out pitifully and was forcibly cast back over a hundred feet.

Atop his massive body, endless spear lights had produced bloody holes. Even so, the Purple Chestnut King hadn’t died and was only severely wounded.

Lin Ming’s spear had heavily wounded the Purple Chestnut King but it wasn’t able to kill him. This left Lin Ming surprised. Although he didn’t put his full strength behind his attack, it was still far more than enough. For this Purple Chestnut King to not die left him surprised. It seemed that the spirit race was far more formidable than he first thought.

Lin Ming was only surprised. As for the others still on Limitless God Mountain, all of them were shocked speechless.

“This… this is…”

The Violet Cloud Princess’ eyes widened. She never imagined such a scene would occur.

She originally had a deep grudge against the Purple Chestnut King and was well aware of what his limits were.

She believed that if she and the Purple Chestnut King had the same level of cultivation, she wouldn’t be his opponent. This was because this Purpled Chestnut King was a descendant of an ancient race that existed 10 billion years and also came with a top bloodline.

If there was a race that could exist for 10 billion years and only decline now, then that meant this clan wasn’t as simple as he first thought. Right now, the fact that they had existed for this long was a testament to their strength!

As for the Purple Chestnut King, he was one of the most outstanding individuals amongst the juniors of the spirit race.

Yet such a person had been defeated by Lin Ming’s spear and his entire body marred with blood holes. This difference was too great!

Moreover, the Violet Cloud Princess suspected that Lin Ming wasn’t using his full strength.

“Goodness… what a strong fellow.”

The Violet Cloud Princess’ normally calm expression was replaced with one of shock and disbelief. At this time, Lin Ming no longer spared the Purple Chestnut King a glance. Without slowing down, he plunged towards the kirin fruit. He had to obtain this fruit at all costs!

Chapter 1811 – Mysterious Little Girl

The vast mountain ranges were distant and mysterious. The endless peaks of mountains continued on without end, all of them shrouded in a thick and viscous black fog.

The mountains were barren and without any sign of life. There was nothing but strange rugged stone littering the ground.

The air was cold and grim, deathly still.

From the depths of the distant mountain ranges, horrifying roars would echo out, shaking the world, as if some ancient vicious beasts were awakening from their slumber.

Lin Ming cautiously moved forwards until he found a hidden cave. Only then did he sit down and relax his thoughts.

He immediately pulled out the kirin fruit.

As the kirin fruit appeared, a rich medicinal fragrance wafted out, forming mist as tangible as a white dragon that filled every inch of the cave.

Lin Ming only needed to take a whiff of this medicinal fragrance to feel as if his body was being cleansed by a pure running stream, filling him with comfort.

Chirp! Chirp!

The kirin fruit still wildly struggled. But because it wasn’t able to manifest a form yet, it wasn’t able to escape.

Lin Ming hesitated for a moment. In order to bring out the highest level of medicinal efficacy from this fruit, it had to be used for alchemy; he shouldn’t directly swallow it. But now, he had received heavy wounds and there was some unfamiliar energy pulsing through his body that was influencing him.

In addition, the massive explosions from those inscription symbols had caused his meridians and blood vessels to be broken in numerous places.

All of these things needed to be dealt with. When he was running away he had no time to deal with these problems but now he could rest for a moment to recover from his injuries.

Lin Ming thought for a bit. He pinched off two leaves from the kirin fruit and then swallowed them.

Although it was only two kirin fruit leaves, after swallowing them Lin Ming felt them melt within his body. Then, a moment later, a sun seemed to erupt within him.

A potent extreme strength stirred up rough waves in Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. The monstrous waves surged forwards, reaching into the skies.

“What a strong medicinal efficacy, what a good spirit source strength…”

Lin Ming didn’t dare to delay. He revolved all of his blood vitality and started to coordinate it with the medicinal efficacy of the kirin fruit leaves in his body to heal his wounds.

The blood vitality in his body began to gush like a flooded river…

After two days and a night, Lin Ming opened his eyes. A brilliant flash of light lit up his pupils; his soul force had reached a new peak yet again.

The injuries he had previously sustained had now completely vanished.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but recall the image of that arrogant and scaled Purple Chestnut King. From his heart, a dense killing intent rolled out.

But soon, he immediately dispelled these thoughts. He inspected himself and found it strange upon discovering that there were no changes with his body. The backlash caused by that peculiar energy had been so easily healed?

Thinking about it further didn’t bring him any new ideas. Rather, he pulled out the kirin fruit and looked at it.

In two days and a night, this kirin fruit actually managed to manifest two front hooves. As it appeared in Lin Ming’s hand, its legs began to rapidly twitch as it tried to escape from his grasp.

“This thing, if it were to fully manifest then wanting to cage it would be difficult… I’ll have to completely refine its spiritual wisdom.” Lin Ming grabbed the kirin fruit.

Chirp! Chirp!

After being grasped by Lin Ming, the kirin fruit began to panic. Sounds seemed to come from within it and it seemed incomparably terrified.

“This little thing…”

Such a strange and magical kirin fruit left Lin Ming feeling more and more amazed. It was just no different from a little life form. For a time, Lin Ming hesitated in exterminating its mind.

Then, from deep in the cave, the sound of pattering footsteps echoed.

“Who’s there?” Lin Ming asked, raising his guard. His muscles tightened and his electric eyes focused on the entrance of the cave.

The cave Lin Ming was in was deep and limitless, with tunnels running in all directions. But for the sounds of footsteps to appear here and at this time, this left Lin Ming bewildered.

Why would there be someone here?

At one of the cave entrances, beneath Lin Ming’s eagle-sharp eyes, a timid little girl in a red dress ran out.

This little girl appeared to be around 15-16 years old. She had black hair that fell down like a waterfall and her appearance was exquisite. However, she seemed somewhat dazed. In particular, her eyes attracted the most attention. Her two pupils were profound beyond reasoning, and there seemed to be blood red lights faintly smoldering within them.

At this time, as she looked at Lin Ming, there was clearly a hint of hesitation and dread in her eyes.

As she appeared, she gave off an extremely peculiar feeling as if she were completely in sync with this world, as if she were some being that had emerged from the good fortune of this land.

In Lin Ming’s divine sense, she seemed no different from an ordinary stone or a blade of grass.

“D… d-d-don’t eat it…” The red-dressed little girl said to Lin Ming.

Her voice was beautiful and lilting, but she spoke slowly and stuttered, as if she struggled to speak each word.

“Who are you?” Lin Ming didn’t dare to lower his guard. His eyes remained locked on her body.

He believed that news of him taking the kirin fruit would have already spread out by now. There were likely countless people searching for his whereabouts, but, this little girl was clearly not one of them. It was puzzling just how she managed to show up in this hidden cave.

Lin Ming waved his right hand and extracted a spear. As this spear appeared it quietly trembled, filled with desires of bloodlust.

Seeing the bright spear, the red-dressed girl was scared and pedaled several steps back. She clearly wanted to escape, but as her eyes fell on the kirin fruit in Lin Ming’s hand, she hesitated and stopped.

“Y-y-y-you… if you don’t eat it, I… c-c-can… give you… something g-g-good.” The red-dressed little girl didn’t answer Lin Ming’s question but was instead concerned for the kirin fruit. Her words seemed to be a little faster than before but she still stuttered as if she wasn’t skilled at speaking.

The kirin fruit’s small eyes turned towards the red-dressed little girl, a look of affection and excitement within them. It chirped at the little girl as it tried desperately to escape from Lin Ming’s grasp and into her embrace.

“I-I-I-I can use this to… t-t-t-trade with you.” The red-dressed little girl revealed a worried look as she heard the kirin fruit’s cries.

Her hand opened and a dazzling light burst out, revealing a red crystal the size of a soybean.

Lin Ming’s eyes focused on this gem. But as this gem appeared in the red-dressed little girl’s palm, it melted and became a drop of blood.

Pata! Pata!

As this drop of red liquid appeared, it emitted sound waves that made the heart race, as if it were a beating heart itself.

These fluctuations were mysterious and carried with them a massive soul force. Even Lin Ming could feel his own heart begin to beat in tandem with this red liquid.

“This is…” Lin Ming carefully stared at the drop of red liquid. His intuition told him that this wasn’t blood, but whatever it was, it still contained a titanic life energy as well as spirit source.

A brilliant light burst out from Lin Ming’s eyes, runes shining within them. He wanted to completely understand what this drop of water was.

But this drop of water was deep and infinitely profound. It was wrapped by an enigmatic strength, making it so that Lin Ming couldn’t see through it.

Even so, he could feel that this was a truly terrifying drop of water.

From this drop of water, an incomparably powerful and intensely holy aura gushed out. The spirit source strength contained within it had also reached unfathomable levels.

The value of this water drop was impossible to estimate, but it was undoubtedly a top treasure that stood upon the pinnacle of rarity.

As for whether or not it was more precious than the kirin fruit, Lin Ming wasn’t able to distinguish that with his current eyesight.

“T-t-t-this is spring water… I found… from inside a cave… I… I t-t-took it… and a-a-after that… the spring disappeared. It… should be very precious.” The red-dressed girl hurriedly explained as she feared Lin Ming wouldn’t look at it. She constantly gesticulated with her hand.

“Cave? You mean the Soul Cave?” Lin Ming asked. He naturally remembered the legends. It was said that there was once a spring in the Soul Cave but it had disappeared. Could that have been… the Weeping Blood God Springs?

As Lin Ming recalled these four words his eyebrows flew up. The Weeping Blood God Springs was absolutely the most precious of treasures that could exist in the Soul Cave.

It was said to have condensed the blood of a peerless god king that once lived in times long past. Once, there were even True Divinities who entered the Soul Cave for the Weeping Blood God Springs, but after the springs disappeared, True Divinities naturally wouldn’t visit the Soul Cave.

He suddenly had doubts as to who this mysterious red-dressed little girl was. Just who was she? She had appeared from nowhere like a ghost and she even had a treasure from the Weeping Blood God Springs. Moreover, she was clearly familiar with the kirin fruit, and from how things were it seemed that the kirin fruit was intimate with this little girl and the little girl was also concerned about it…

Chapter 1812 – Hidden Treasure

Lin Ming’s eyes focused on the red-dressed little girl’s bare feet. Even though the path here was covered with jagged rocks, incredibly as she moved she appeared to be walking across the surface of smooth water, completely in tune with her surrounding environment.

“Who are you?”

Lin Ming asked once more. However, the little girl only flushed red. She gripped her fists, not saying anything else.

Lin Ming slightly frowned; he was completely unable to see through this little girl’s boundary. She felt like a mortal, but his intuition told him that the truth wasn’t so simple. She must possess some sort of mystical ability and he couldn’t see what the limits of her strength were.

Lin Ming’s silence caused the little girl to tense up. She parted her lips and said, “Is… i-is… it not enough?”

The little girl also felt that the thing she took out wasn’t valuable enough. At least, it wasn’t enough to satisfy Lin Ming. He still might eat the kirin fruit.

She thought about it for a moment and then said, “I… I-I-I-I… know of a place where treasure is hidden. I can t-t-tell you, but you can’t e-e-eat it.”

It was clear just how dear the kirin fruit was to her.

“What place with hidden treasure?” Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred.

“I-I-I… can’t say it clearly… if y-y-y-you come with me… you’ll see…” The red-dressed little girl seemed to have not spoken any words for an extremely long period of time. Her words lagged behind her thoughts as if she needed time to consider what they were.

Lin Ming deeply peered at the little girl. With his cautious personality, he shouldn’t go to such an unknown place. But, this little girl really didn’t seem to have any evil intentions at all.

“Lead me to this hidden treasure area. I won’t eat the kirin fruit.”

Upon hearing Lin Ming say he wouldn’t eat the kirin fruit, the red-dressed little girl finally seemed to relax. The kirin fruit also chirped out loud, clearly happy.

The red-dressed little girl brightly smiled as she saw how happy the kirin fruit was. Two deep dimples appeared on her cheeks, making her look lovable.

“G-g-g-great, I will l-l-lead the way.” The little girl vigorously nodded as if she were afraid Lin Ming would back out of his promise.

“No need to hurry. Before we go I’ll absorb that drop of god springs.” Lin Ming said. He looked towards the red-dressed little girl, “Help me stand guard outside so that no one enters here.”

Lin Ming was still vigilant against this mysterious little girl. After all, when he absorbed the drop of god springs his defense would be in a weakened state.

“A… alright.” The red-dressed little girl nodded.

After the little girl walked a distance away, Lin Ming laid down a simple protection enchantment and stepped into it. Then he directly swallowed that drop of god springs.

Soon, Lin Ming was covered in an endless blood light.

Traces of the blood light seeped into his skin, completely enveloping him.

The blood light became increasingly thick, rushing towards Lin Ming more and more as it wrapped him up.

Pata! Pata!

This blood light seemed to form a giant translucent cocoon of blood that beat like a heart.

With every beat, it was like a god king was striking a drum, the sound like a rolling thunderclap.

The cave as well as the entire mountain began to shiver.

Like this, Lin Ming closed up for over 20 hours.

Outside, night fell and then the sun rose yet again. But in the cave, it was utterly dark throughout.

At this time, beams of light shot out from the blood cocoon, slowly tearing it open.

Lin Ming appeared from within, a strange blood strength permeating his body. Countless faint runes shimmered upon his skin, seeming to shine and dim along with his heartbeat.

This bodily phenomenon occurred for some time before disappearing.

“What a great treasure! My soul has become 50% stronger and there is also a great deal of strength I haven’t been able to absorb but was saved in my inner world! Even my boundary has increased… it is close to the middle Holy Lord realm. In fact, if I wanted to I could make a breakthrough right now!”

Lin Ming discovered that there was a great strength rushing through his inner world like a raging river.

The kirin leaves from before as well as this drop of Weeping Blood God Springs had caused a tremendous amount of excess power to be stored within him. Since he couldn’t absorb it yet, all he could do was compress this energy within his inner world and slowly absorb it.

With this, it would become increasingly difficult for him to keep suppressing his cultivation so that he didn’t make a premature breakthrough.

His cultivation was more than high enough. Right now, what he lacked was time. If he had another 100 years, then that would be ideal!

After absorbing the drop of Weeping Blood God Springs, Lin Ming could faintly feel as if he became more familiar with the surrounding environment. It was like the drop of blood within him was the same as the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

“This sort of familiar feeling… should be because I absorbed that drop of god springs…” Lin Ming suddenly realized.

And at this time, his complexion changed. He felt that the red-dressed little girl had returned.

He waved his hand and a wisp of heavenly tribulation fire flew out from his palm, turning into endless flame runes that slowly settled on his body and turned into a robe.

As for the red-dressed little girl, she was curiously looking at Lin Ming, a dazed look on her face and without any fear or suspicion at all. It was clear she didn’t know of the differences between men and women.

“You said there was a hidden treasure somewhere?” Lin Ming asked the red-dressed little girl.

“I-I-I remember…”

The little girl quickly waved her hands. She was ready to go at any time.

Bang!

Lin Ming left his cave and turned into a beam of light as he rapidly flew over the mountains. He followed the red-dressed little girl’s instructions and flew towards the hidden treasure area.

As he passed by an underground river that was surging with black waters, he saw a red wild cow galloping through the river, its entire body awash with blazing red flames.

Its entire body sparked with flames. As its hooves struck the ground, the water around it all evaporated due to the high heat and even the river mud was melted into a dark yellow sludge; it was a bizarre sight.

Lin Ming was considerably startled. This soul beast’s strength was about as strong as the soul beast he encountered at Limitless God Mountain.

Such a powerful soul beast was actually engaged in battle with someone in the river. The soul beast’s opponent was an old man that possessed a terrifying blood vitality and intense soul force. The old man was releasing an endless power of Ice Laws, enough to freeze massive tracts of the river to suppress the cow. On the side of the river, several white-robed youths had set up an array.

“Half-step Empyrean? Or…”

Lin Ming was careful; he didn’t arouse the attention of these people. On the Akashic Dream Battlefield, there was an endless number of masters! Those he fought in the Soul Cave had only been a miniscule portion of them. There were also many half-step Empyreans and Empyreans still wandering about.

He continued forwards. Strangely, the red-dressed little girl who was following him had disappeared. But he could clearly feel an intense fluctuation of energy emit from beneath his feet, closely following behind him.

In the Soul Cave, Lin Ming’s divine sense was blinded by a strange dark power. It was hard for him to detect what was occurring beneath his feet.

Yet, he was completely aware that the energy fluctuations beneath him were definitely those of the mysterious red-dressed little girl.

Could it be…

At the Soul Cave when he first picked the kirin fruit, a strange energy had rushed into his body, severely wounding him.

This energy, could it have been this red-dressed little girl?

Lin Ming had this idea before. This was because after he took the kirin fruit’s leaves to heal himself, the strange energy within him had disappeared, inexplicably vanishing without a trace.

Originally, Lin Ming felt that this strength wasn’t simple at all and shouldn’t have disappeared so easily.

And what followed right after that was this little girl suddenly appearing from nowhere in his secret cave. This was also a reasonable explanation.

Thinking of this, Lin Ming’s heart began to beat faster. If this little girl had any evil intentions when he had been trying to heal himself, he definitely would have suffered some miserable fate.

Luckily, this little girl’s thoughts were pure, without any hint of malice.

Just who was she?

And at this time, from the far off distance, a tremendous roar erupted. The nearby mountains shook and beams of essence energy emerged from the far off mountains that pierced through the void.

Lin Ming’s thoughts focused. This was definitely a battle between powerhouses. He had to be more careful… after all, any hidden treasure here must be extremely precious and he didn’t want to attract droves of people who wanted to come and struggle with him.

This hidden treasure area was located deep in the Soul Cave. Lin Ming cautiously continued forwards. To his amazement, he discovered that there were far more powerhouses in the Soul Cave than when he had first come here.

Finally, Lin Ming came upon a stretch of forest that was covered in a thick mist.

The ancient trees towered high into the air.

Incredibly, each tree was as great as a mountain and he wasn’t able to see the top of them at all. This left Lin Ming whistling in awe at this breathtaking sight.

“Mm?”

Suddenly, Lin Ming discovered that brilliant fireworks had appeared above him.

These fireworks were purple gold in color and exuded a familiar aura. Soon, the fireworks slowly shifted into a face in the void – it was Lin Ming’s own face!

Lin Ming frowned. For something like this to occur now, he already guessed just what had happened.

Like this, Lin Ming’s complexion darkened.

Chapter 1814 – Blood Stains the Forest

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Although they were separated through the dense forest by a thousand feet, Lin Ming was still able to rely upon his sense to clearly see each martial artist that was rushing to his location. Most of them were spiritas but there were also a number of races he had never seen before.

In the next moment, a horrifying fluctuation of energy ravaged through the forest. Massive trees cracked apart and shattered. The surrounding dense forest was nearly flattened and all that was left over were rows of large stumps; the towering trees had all been sent flying away!

The newcomers had blown apart the forest. They were afraid Lin Ming would use the forest as cover to escape.

Shua! Shua! Shua!

Instantly, over 20 divine senses locked onto Lin Ming. Those that were able to reach this area did not possess low cultivations.

After all, the rumors said that Lin Ming had suppressed the Purple Chestnut King and was a genius in his own right.

“29 people…”

Lin Ming observed his situation. He drew out the Phoenix Blood Spear. With a keening cry, spear wind recklessly lashed out.

“Just turn into merit points already!”

Without further speaking, Lin Ming shot forwards!

His actions startled the 29 martial artists who had just arrived. What was happening here? They had so many people encircling him, so shouldn’t this human be trying to run?

Yet not only had the human waited for them to arrive, but he even said he wanted to turn them into merit points; this was simply ridiculous.

“Attack! Get rid of this madman!”

“Kill him first. As for his treasures, those will belong to whoever has the ability to seize them!”

No one went easy on Lin Ming. Even though Lin Ming was a junior and most of the newcomers were middle aged men or even old men, none of them had the martial arts spirit of fighting one on one. After all, rumors said that Lin Ming could even suppress the Purple Chestnut King.

Piki paka!

Lin Ming emitted crackling sounds from all his joints. Nine stars appeared high in the skies, and three Dao Palaces shined brightly within him. His feet stepped on the ground and he rushed out.

His first target was a middle-aged man who had pushed his way to the front. Lin Ming could feel that this middle-aged man was the strongest of those present. This meant that before this middle-aged man’s cultivation was suppressed by the Laws of the Akashic Dream Battlefield, his boundary might have been that of a World King.

The middle-aged man demonically grinned. He grasped a heavy sword and chopped. A dazzling sword light slashed out, tearing through the skies.

“Pathetic human, I’ll chop off your head!”

The middle-aged man shouted out. But in the next moment, thunder and fire wove together into a sea of purple and red in front of him. With a loud rumbling explosion his sword light was swallowed up by the sea of energy and the power of thunder and fire detonated in front of him. He vomited a mouthful of blood and was sent flying away, his body charred completely black.

He had been violently and instantly killed!

“What!?”

The others didn’t even have time to respond. At this moment, Lin Ming swept out the Phoenix Blood Spear, killing in a circle around him. Seven or eight people were brutally killed as their heads were sent soaring into the air, blood erupting from their severed necks like water fountains!

A massive number of merit points flowed into Lin Ming’s token. He felt his body heat up, as if he were stimulated by the intense smell of blood. Killing! Killing to his heart’s content!

Then, Lin Ming realized that more and more people were catching up!

This was because the spirit race martial artist from before had cast out a signal flare, and this signal flare seemed to utilize a marvelous inscription technique. Before it dissipated it rose higher and higher into the air, turning brighter and brighter, catching the attention of more and more people.

This also meant more and more challengers were arriving.

The ruckus Lin Ming had stirred up in the Soul Cave was too great. In addition to the Purple Chestnut King deliberately spreading news of what happened, many people had learned of Lin Ming.

At this time, several dozen people had gathered. As they arrived, they witnessed with their own eyes as Lin Ming’s spear totally annihilated everyone around him, cutting off the necks of seven or eight people and causing their blood to drench the world.

They naturally recognized Lin Ming’s appearance; he was completely similar to the fireworks in the sky. This meant he was the human that had obtained the kirin fruit.

For a time, all of them were shocked speechless. They unconsciously slowed down, stopping several miles away and not daring to approach.

These people had only come here to adventure and temper themselves. They weren’t too strong to begin with and didn’t think they could obtain the kirin fruit anyway; they just wanted to join in on the liveliness. And as they arrived, they saw the scene of Lin Ming slaughtering everyone around him.

“That blue-robed old man who just died… isn’t that the Blue Cloud Sect’s Elder Bai… I remember he had a half-step World King cultivation…”

A martial artist who had just arrived trembled as he spoke, his voice faltering. He had extremely good eyesight and could clearly see that one of the heads that had been soaring into the air was that of the Blue Cloud Sect’s Elder Bai. On the planet that the Blue Cloud Sect was located on, Elder Bai was absolutely an overlord of the land!

When Lin Ming had swept out his spear and killed so many people, they had subconsciously thought that he had only slain cannon fodder and useless minions. But now, it seemed that Lin Ming was actually slaying peerless powerhouses!

To Lin Ming, these peerless powerhouses were no different than chickens or dogs. He killed them by the batch.

This was just far too terrifying!

From what they could see, Lin Ming wasn’t old at all, and even seemed to be younger than the Purple Chestnut King, so how could he be so strong?

And what was even more incredible was that he was a human.

In the Soul World, the human race that had been suppressed on all sides was synonymous with ‘weak’.

“All of you, die.”

Lin Ming attacked again and again, his speed as phantasmal as ghosts and gods. The 20 some martial artists that arrived were systematically killed by Lin Ming. Their heads were blown off or their hearts were pierced. Their blood rained down to the earth and their organs flew out!

Some people were scared silly and tried to run away.

However, Lin Ming simply stepped forwards and space shrank beneath his feet, instantly bringing him behind those that were running away. Without expression, he thrust out his spear!

Puff!

His spear pierced through a martial artist’s chest, causing blood to fly out. Out of the 29 people, 22 of them had been killed already!

The remaining seven had ashen complexions. They all used their best techniques to flee this execution ground.

But at this time, a boundless force field covered the surrounding space, sealing all seven people within.

This was the grandmist force field.

The star-heavy grandmist energy immediately locked down their movements.

“Damn it all!”

“No!”

The seven people madly roared out. They attacked the grandmist space with everything they had, but all of their efforts failed.

They watched as Lin Ming’s spear light was soon about to swallow them all up.

“Stop!”

At this time, someone shouted out loud as more and more martial artists arrived. Of these people, some shared the same types of robes that some of the seven soon-to-die martial artists wore. It was clear they originated from the same sect.

However, Lin Ming remained indifferent, completely disregarding this shout.

The Phoenix Blood Spear slashed out.

With a loud slicing sound, blood shot out. After Lin Ming swept out his spear, the seven people had all been cut in half at the waist.

“How vile!”

The dozen plus people who just arrived had uncertain and gloomy expressions. They hadn’t figured out just what had happened yet, but as they looked at the scene around them they could see that Lin Ming had already killed many people!

Many of the dead had torn up corpses, their blood flowing out in streams.

Lin Ming’s head immediately swiveled like a hawk spotting its prey, locking onto those people who had shouted out for him to stop just now.

As his eyes blazed at them, the courage of these people nearly broke apart. Just what kind of eyes were these? The killing intent and hostility gushing out from them was terrifying to behold, as if they were the eyes of a people-eating demon.

“We… should…”

Several of these dozen plus people already formed thoughts of drawing back and escaping. But at this time, Lin Ming was like a death reaper hunting the night. He stepped forwards, rushing towards these newcomers on his own initiative!

“It’s too late! Attack!”

The dozen plus people were shocked. They all drew their weapons.

However, what they didn’t notice was that just several miles away, those people that were too scared to do anything were looking at them with fear and pity in their eyes.

In the opinion of these distant people, these dozen plus newcomers were dead because they hadn’t been here to see just how brutal Lin Ming had been in his actions, or how impossibly fierce he was. If gods stepped in his way he would kill gods, if buddhas blocked his path he would cut down buddhas!

The Blue Cloud Sect’s Elder Bai was a half-step World King, and yet he had died no differently than some chicken, instantly killed where he had stood!

This was a horrifying demon. Anyone that dared to look down upon him with disdain just because he was a human would be killed until they couldn’t die anymore.

It could be said that the moment those dozen plus people had shouted out ‘stop’, their destiny had been sealed – they would undoubtedly die!

………………

“Junior-apprentice Sister, there seem to be some signaling fireworks in the distance…”

On a vast grassland, a troop of several hundred people was crossing over mountains and rivers. After experiencing a war that had lasted for several months already, they were all exhausted.

These people all wore similar icy blue robes – they came from Zenith Palace.

Zenith Palace was only a World King influence and because their World Kings were far too old, it was impossible for them to make another breakthrough in their lifetimes. Thus, they didn’t enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

The fiercest martial artists Zenith Palace were able to send to the Akashic Dream Battlefield were only several half-step World Kings. Thus, the disciples of Zenith Palace were aware of their own limits and didn’t think about trying to wander their way into a danger zone like the Soul Cave.

They knew that with the abilities of Zenith Palace, entering such a place meant they would be eaten up without any bones remaining.

Chapter 1815 – Kill Them All

Zenith Palace had extremely clear goals. The reason they came to the Akashic Dream Battlefield was to hunt down the trial challengers from some smaller influences and gather merit points so they could exchange them for sect rewards later.

Of course, if Zenith Palace obtained a high number of merit points then that would also be proof of their strength. At that time, Empyrean Heavencore would naturally bestow rewards upon them.

This was their final goal.

Now, after passing through several months of battle, Zenith Palace had already lost 40% of their disciples.

There were still more than two years remaining until this session of the Akashic Dream Battlefield ended and yet they had lost 40% of their disciples. This caused the Zenith Vice Palace Master to have a gloomy complexion for the last several days.

Their luck had been poor. As soon as they entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield they had run into several formidable opponents, and had suffered serious losses in the massive battles that occurred.

Without a choice, the Zenith Vice Palace Master was forced to divide the remaining sub 6000 disciples into groups depending on their strength. The strongest disciples were taken out and put together to form an elite squad. Like this, they wouldn’t be burdened and their combat efficiency would also be higher.

Now, this squad of around a hundred people consisted of the outstanding elites from Zenith Palace. This included the Vice Palace Master, Jaderiver, Yi Fan, and many others.

Yi Fan was somber. Zenith Palace had met so many powerful enemies and lost so many disciples. To him, the reason they suffered so much must have been because Lin Ming had betrayed them and given out their information.

His speculations were all baseless, but the truth was that he didn’t need proof nor did he need to find out whether or not this was truly Lin Ming’s fault.

This was because Lin Ming had once beaten up Yi Fan under the gaze of everyone and this caused Yi Fan to hate Lin Ming to the core. Thus, he didn’t mind taking advantage of this moment to make sure Lin Ming’s name was pushed into the gutter.

Moreover, Lin Ming had quietly separated from the main group as soon as he had entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield and hadn’t been seen since. This caused many people to suspect that Lin Ming was actually the ‘spy’.

Lin Ming appearing at Zenith Palace was strange to begin with and he also came from some unknown origin. Above all, he was a human, someone that the spiritas would never consider one of their own!

For these past days, Yi Fan had constantly attacked Lin Ming. Due to this, Jaderiver also appeared ill. She was the one who had brought Lin Ming into Zenith Palace, so all of these accusations were the same as saying she had brought a traitor into their ranks.

Even so, Lin Ming’s actions inevitably aroused Jaderiver’s suspicions and she didn’t have any energy or rationale to explain them.

In this situation, they continued passing through the barren mountains and rivers. The small influence that was Zenith Palace, who didn’t know much of what was happening right now, suddenly saw the brilliant fireworks that stained the skies.

By the time they saw the fireworks, the fireworks had already risen up very high into the air and had spread far and wide. Anyone could make out that these fireworks were in the design of a person’s face. As for who this face belonged to, they weren’t able to immediately distinguish.

“What is happening up there? Should we go take a look?”

A disciple suddenly proposed.

Jaderiver frowned. She didn’t want to cause any problems, but as she looked at the face in the far off fireworks, a familiar feeling came to her.

“How come this face looks a little like… Lin Muk?”

Jaderiver muttered to herself with doubts in her heart.

The Vice Palace Master shook his head, “It should only be a coincidence that they look alike. There is no reason that Lin Muk would have someone cast a signal flare into the sky because of him. This sort of signal flare is activated with inscription techniques and it is considerably difficult to create as well as prohibitively expensive. The signal can spread to a wide range and the one launching it should be someone from a large influence. As for the person depicted by the signal flare, it should be one of their most wanted criminals…”

The Vice Palace Master explained. In his opinion, if a large influence were to place a bounty on someone and in this manner, that person was likely some extraordinary figure. No one in the ranks of their Zenith Palace was capable of receiving such treatment.

“Bounty? Now that Vice Palace Master says that, I actually recall something. Just several days ago, the spirit race was issuing out news that they had placed a bounty on someone, and this person seemed to have stolen some sort of precious spirit medicine from the Soul Cave and caused an uproar in the Akashic Dream Battlefield.”

Although Zenith Palace had been engaging in guerrilla warfare in the wild mountains and plains for these past several months, because they had many people there were always some disciples that managed to obtain news passing through the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

“Oh? Precious spirit medicine…”

The Vice Palace Master’s thoughts stirred. He glanced at the other high level figures from Zenith Palace and then finally said, “Let’s go take a look from afar and see what the situation is like. If there is any danger then we’ll immediately leave.”

In the Akashic Dream Battlefield, many people had the same idea as Zenith Palace.

Their total war strength was weak so it was impossible for them to even think of obtaining some top spirit medicine that could tempt an Empyrean or even a True Divinity.

They only wanted to join in on the fun and see just what was happening.

Of course, there were also some people hoping to come and pick up some easy advantages. They didn’t think they could obtain these precious spirit medicines, but if they ran into any corpses of powerhouses they would be satisfied with sifting through them.

Thus, underneath the incitement of the great fireworks in the sky, more and more martial artists arrived at the razed forest area.

These people only stood at a distance, not daring to go forwards.

And at this time, in a giant circle that everyone was standing on the side of, the center was filled with countless scattered bodies.

Every corpse was mutilated and torn apart; their deaths had been miserable.

Because there were too many martial artists that had come, the corpses formed a thick layer over the ground!

Their blood had gathered into flowing streams. As for Lin Ming, he grasped his spear and floated in the air above the pile of corpses. Killing intent surged out from his body, making him seem like an unrivalled asura!

His merit points had already reached 10 billion!

Of course, these merit points had to be divided by his age. In truth, he had less than a hundred million. With this amount he couldn’t even exchange for a tenth of the golden page.

From this alone it could be seen how difficult it was to obtain a golden page!

Woosh!

At this time, Lin Ming hurtled forwards. He rushed in a direction and swung his spear. Spear light swept out and a divine brilliance radiated into the skies. Several heads immediately rolled to the ground!

“You!!”

The companions of these dead people were enraged. They had originally come to steal the precious spirit medicine, but the Lin Ming in their eyes was far too ferocious; they didn’t dare to attack him. They only watched from a far off distance as spectators, but even so they never imagined that they would be sucked into this mess!

“Why do you kill us?!”

Someone angrily shouted, unable to do anything to Lin Ming.

“Those who kill should expect to be killed. You cannot hide your killing intent so don’t bother making excuses about your intentions!”

As Lin Ming spoke, the grandmist force field came shrouding down. The entire group fell to the ground, completely trapped in this force field!

For a time, blood red light flashed in the air as howls and screams filled the force field. No one was able to contend with Lin Ming!

This wasn’t even a battle but a massacre. The disparity was too great!

The surrounding martial artists saw the bloody lights flashing in the force field and felt a cold chill crawl down their backs. They had all heard Lin Ming speak. Lin Ming had sensed that those people had thoughts of killing him, thus he attacked them.

This was what he meant when he said those who kill should expect to be killed.

In other words, even though Lin Ming was engaged in a titanic battle that had continued for a long time, his sense had already thoroughly locked onto everyone nearby. None of their movements had escaped his eyes!

Just how terrifying was that!?

“Run!”

Some people who held killing intent towards Lin Ming immediately began to run away. Their confidence had utterly collapsed!

But at this time, Lin Ming flicked his fingers. Spear lights shot out and a massive number of martial artists were pierced to death!

This moment had become their lives’ most unforgettable scene!

They had encountered a demon, a demon who they had no strength to resist!

A tremendous number of merit points merged into Lin Ming’s token. Lin Ming felt the token in his inner world heat up, as if it would start to combust on its own.

This was a situation that rarely appeared in the past, where one’s merit points increased so dramatically and rapidly!

It had to be known that the people Lin Ming killed were not weak. Besides the merit points that they had themselves, they also had merit points they plundered after killing others.

Now, all of their points belonged to Lin Ming.

At this time, from outside the completely unrecognizable jungle, the sound of rustling footsteps drew close.

A hundred plus martial artists were rapidly making their way here.

In this area, many influences had gathered.

But, this squad of martial artists wasn’t worthy of attention at all. The size of their group was small and there weren’t any masters in their ranks. All they had were several half-step World Kings and peak Holy Lords to stand out.

As for the others, a great number of them weren’t even at the Holy Lord realm, but just the Soul Lord realm.

A Soul Lord realm martial artist showed their true strength in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, where one’s cultivation was restricted to the Soul Lord realm. Because of this, the strength they displayed was similar to what it was in the real world. Without the increase in their strength brought about by their comprehension of Laws and cultivation methods, they simply didn’t possess much combat strength here.

As this squad appeared, Lin Ming felt them approach. He looked towards them with surprise.

This was because he had recognized several familiar people. This squad was the ‘top’ squad of Zenith Palace and had gathered all of their elites. Lin Ming naturally remembered who they were.

As Lin Ming glanced at them, the martial artists from Zenith Palace were all stunned.

Jaderiver, Yi Fan, the Vice Palace Master, as well as the several Zenith Palace Elders, all of them stared back at Lin Ming with eyes as wide as full moons. They froze where they were, completely unable to respond to what they saw.

Wasn’t this… Lin Muk!? It was really him!

Chapter 1816 – Brilliant Fireworks

The many disciples of Zenith Palace hadn’t responded to what they saw yet.

But at the next moment, a thick smell of blood flooded their senses.

Lin Ming floated in the void. Beneath his feet, a massive pile of corpses was stacked up in thick layers!

Blood, torn flesh, dismembered corpses, this was an indescribably ghastly scene.

This was…

Jaderiver froze.

Beside her, Yi Fan had also paled. The many Elders of Zenith Palace were panic-stricken; they didn’t know just how this had happened.

Jaderiver’s wide eyes stared at the blood still dripping down Lin Ming’s spear, unable to find the words to say.

All of these people, had they been killed by Lin Muk?

From these dead martial artists she was able to feel a strong force field. This was because those that had died had been too strong in life, and after dying, their strength had gathered together instead of dispersing.

Yet such a group of powerhouses was piled up like a heap of dead dogs!

Lin Ming didn’t greet those people from Zenith Palace. Zenith Palace had only been a small springboard he used when he first came to the Soul World in order to obtain information on Sheng Mei and enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield. He had deliberately distanced himself from Zenith Palace because of this. Moreover, right now he had caused too great a stir in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. If others knew about his connections to Zenith Palace, then a World King influence like them wouldn’t be able to suffer the consequences.

Lin Ming fell on the ground and swept out his divine sense. He found a spirit race martial artist and then reached down to grab a spatial ring from their finger.

People looked at Lin Ming, unsure what he was trying to do.

With such formidable strength, he likely had plenty of lucky chances and treasures. But by all reason, he shouldn’t be interested in the wealth within a spirit race martial artist’s spatial ring.

Lin Ming probed the ring. After several breaths of time, he found some inscription symbols from within it.

Lin Ming scanned these inscription symbols and soon understood how to use them.

Everyone was dumbfounded. Were these inscription symbols so special? Why would this death god care about them?

And at this time, Lin Ming suddenly flung out his hand and the inscription symbols flew into the air. Not just that, but Lin Ming had also flooded them with his true essence as well as fusing the Asura Road’s divine runic arts into them, making them even more potent than before.

With a loud explosive sound, the inscription symbols completely exploded. In the next instant, a mind-boggling sight occurred.

These inscription symbols recklessly released dazzling fireworks into the skies, all of them brilliantly burning as they gathered into an image of Lin Ming.

With the strength of several inscription symbols gathered together as well as Lin Ming’s strength flowing through them, this caused the image of Lin Ming to be dozens of times larger than before and higher than before. It was absolutely an eye-catching sight!

Everyone watching felt their jaws drop, unable to say anything.

These were the signal flares used by the spirit race martial artists that had been chasing Lin Ming.

The previous signal flare had already burnt away by now and the fireworks had dimmed down. Thus, Lin Ming had decided to cast more up for another round!

And these were even more brilliant than before!

For a time, Lin Ming’s appearance reappeared in the dark skies. His dashing and heroic face, his sharp and fierce aura, it was like he was taunting all the elites of the world!

What was he trying to do?

He wasn’t satisfied with these numbers of people and wanted to kill more, to kill to his heart’s content!

Lin Ming’s intentions were now clear to everyone. He wanted to tell all the nearby martial artists that he was waiting here for them. No matter how many people came, he would kill that many!

Was he some inexhaustible killing puppet? He had slain so many people and battled for such a long time, and yet he wasn’t tired at all?

The people from Zenith Palace were already completely dazed. This scene also made them understand what had happened.

Before, Jaderiver thought that the image formed from fireworks in the sky looked similar to Lin Ming.

This meant that Lin Ming was the person who the spirit race had placed a bounty on. In the Soul Cave, he had obtained a precious spirit medicine that could even tempt the heart of a True Divinity. Moreover, not only was he not captured, but now he was standing here not running, waiting for people to come hunt him down so he could kill them all one at a time and gain merit points while doing so!

This method was simply frightening!

And in the next moment, Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He looked into the distant horizon.

Through the layers of bloody mist and red clouds in the skies, Lin Ming could clearly see what was happening in the distance.

Two groups were rapidly approaching.

The group in front was led by a tall and sturdy spirit race martial artist. This martial artist was covered in purple scales from head to toe.

He was a king of the spirit race’s younger generation – the Purple Chestnut King.

And not too far away from him was the heroic spiritas youth.

Accompanying them were masters of their various influences, all of them hurtling towards Lin Ming at a breakneck pace. And amongst these masters were many Great World Kings!

As Lin Ming saw these two groups of people, he viciously smiled. He had been waiting for such a long time and now two big fish were finally approaching the bait.

They must have a great deal of merit points.

“Brat, you’re dead!”

After the Purple Chestnut King received the signal, he didn’t immediately chase after Lin Ming. Rather, he sent his own men after Lin Ming while he gathered powerhouses from his people.

He knew just how strong Lin Ming was. After that defeat at Limitless God Mountain, some martial artists had spread out news about his strength so he had risen to fame.

Indeed, it was true that many people learned Lin Ming had obtained the kirin fruit. At the same time, the Purple Chestnut King’s defeat had been vividly recounted.

The Purple Chestnut King was an extremely arrogant individual. He already disliked the spiritas martial artists of the Soul World, and now with these people endlessly mocking him, it left him choking on his rage.

Thus, this time, he had to kill Lin Ming in order to recover some of his honor.

Even if he had to win in a disgraceful manner by relying on the strength of his sect, he couldn’t care too much about this. He fully realized that he wasn’t Lin Ming’s opponent.

“Elder Feng, in a bit make sure you all attack with everything you have. This brat is not easy to deal with!”

The Purple Chestnut King growled, his chest burning with hate.

“Your Highness, rest assured we will not underestimate the enemy!”

This Elder Feng was one of the Great World Kings of the spirits, moreover he was a peak existence amongst Great World Kings.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

The Purple Chestnut King had caught up and had brought five Great World Kings along with him, as well as a good number of ordinary World Kings. In addition, many Holy Lord followers were right behind them.

This was a terrifying force.

And not too far behind the Purple Chestnut King, the heroic spiritas youth had also brought a formidable force. His squad consisted of four Great World Kings and seven or eight ordinary World Kings.

It had to be known that these two martial artists originated from peak Empyrean level influences. The direct disciples of an Empyrean influence would mostly reach the World King level.

As these two terrifying teams arrived, their aura caged in the entire audience, leaving everyone shocked.

When had the martial artists from small influences ever experienced such a scene?

Even though these two teams had their cultivations suppressed, the auras emanating from their bodies were still those of top powerhouses. As these auras exuded out into the world, it left the low level martial artists reeling.

Without a doubt, any single one of these newcomers could easily eliminate one of the weaker sects present without any chance of revolt.

This was the same for Zenith Palace.

And all of these people had come for Lin Ming!

The disparity in these lineups – wasn’t it just too great?

At this time, Lin Ming was standing atop the wind. His body wasn’t stained with too much blood, and he seemed rather relaxed. Behind him, an inexplicable gray strength was gathering.

The Purple Chestnut King wanted to find a hint of fear on Lin Ming’s face but he was left disappointed. Lin Ming was a shard of ice, completely unmoved by what was happening around him.

This caused the Purple Chestnut King to become even gloomier. He didn’t think Lin Ming was a fool. In other words, if Lin Ming was calm, then Lin Ming must be far stronger than he originally anticipated!

Lin Ming was already confident in his skills to the point where he completely disregarded a circle of Great World King level powerhouses besieging him!

“Assemble!”

The Purple Chestnut King roared.

The five spirit race Great World Kings didn’t show off. Facing this junior that was countless years younger than them, they began to stand with the Purple Chestnut King, lining up shoulder to shoulder.

Soul force surged out like rivers from their bodies, forming into a massive phantom giant made of soul force.

This phantom was almost large enough to reach the heavens and contained an incredible amount of soul force.

“Human boy, go die!”

As the array formation finished gathering, the Purple Chestnut King shouted out loud. The massive phantom giant they summoned was one of the supernatural powers of their spirit race.

They could gather the soul force of several people together to multiply their strength and form an incomparably formidable soul form.

This giant soul form sent its mountain-like palms crashing down upon Lin Ming.

As Lin Ming saw this, he instantly formed millions of seals.

The gray strength behind him suddenly rose up. Countless runes sparkled. Between the heavens and earth, they formed a three-headed and six-armed figure, a titanic asura warrior phantom.

This asura warrior was slowly pushing a massive wheel.

The wheel had countless howling demons and weeping ghosts. Their cries and hisses were strange and chilling.

Lin Ming glared at the Purple Chestnut King, his slaughter energy soaring to the heavens.

In the void, two titanic figures violently struck each other.

This strike was astonishing.

The giant demon wheel pushed by the asura warrior began to grind down on the soul form. Black energy filled the air, emitting a humming sound. The void shivered and the earth shook; the potential behind their strikes was extraordinary.

As for that soul form, its fists rained down like a storm. Every time they crashed down it was like a falling mountain wrapped in soul force, with enough momentum to break through a world. Everyone was bewildered upon seeing this.

Rumble rumble rumble –

Countless runes shimmered like stars. They were struck and then annihilated.

A storm of energy spread out in all directions, cutting massive fissures into the earth.

Some spectators standing relatively close were swept up by the storm, many of them crying out in pain and misery as they were sent tumbling away.

But as the fight continued, the Purple Chestnut King’s fierce expression began to fade away, instead replaced by wide eyes of disbelief.

The complexions of the five Great World Kings with him also changed. They understood just how powerful the soul form giant they summoned was. In the past, they had even used it to block a 50% strength attack from a sovereign of the spirit race. Yet now, their soul form giant was equally matched by this strange asura warrior in front of them?

Wait, something was wrong! Their soul form giant was actually disintegrating!

Five spirit race Great World Kings had joined together with the Purple Chestnut King in a formation, and yet they were being suppressed by a single Lin Ming. The asura phantom that Lin Ming summoned was also more formidable than that soul form!

Chapter 1819 – Fighting an Empyrean

“Human, do you think you are undefeatable in this world just because you defeated several Great World Kings?”

From the skies, a dark cackling voice spread out. The one speaking clearly felt that there was a considerable number of Great World King corpses scattered on the ground.

“The disparity between an Empyrean and a World King is not what you could hope to imagine! Do you think a Great World King is just a single level away from an Empyrean?”

Although there was still a half-step Empyrean level between a Great World King and an Empyrean, this half-step Empyrean was not considered a full boundary but half a boundary. In other words, half a step.

If one had to truly state it, there was indeed just a single level separating a Great World King from an Empyrean.

But, this single level was a monumental difference!

This was because an Empyrean often had to cross heavenly tribulation and would be reborn in the process. The Laws of an Empyrean were on a completely different rank from those of a Great World King, and the power of these Laws stood on equal ground with the Heavenly Dao. They could even be brought into the Akashic Dream Battlefield!

This difference was the same as the heavens and earth.

Bang!

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s aura erupted, filled with a matchless arrogance, one that looked down upon everyone in this world. As he spoke, a massive pressure came pressing down, shocking many of the martial artists present and making them nearly fall to the ground!

And this was a situation where Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s cultivation had been suppressed. If Empyrean Myriad Ghost was in his peak state, it was hard to imagine just how oppressive this pressure would be.

This was how terrifying an Empyrean was!

For a time, everyone had to shoulder the burden of this Empyrean pressure. Everyone retreated together, but their eyes remained vivid with fear. Most of those present had never seen an Empyrean fight before and as they saw Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s momentum at this time, they couldn’t help but shiver with fear.

With everyone at the Divine Lord level, just who could block such an attack!?

Everyone’s eyes fell on Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s actions within the Akashic Dream Battlefield had indeed been far too rampant. Originally, with his strength, if he were to remain a little more low profile then he could have continuously hunted down World Kings and Great World Kings in secret. At the end, it wouldn’t have been hard for him to obtain first place in merit points. Moreover, he even had the kirin fruit. He could return home with riches and glory!

But it seemed he wasn’t satisfied with this. He actually took out the kirin fruit to taunt those around him, finally causing an Empyrean to move!

Once Lin Ming was killed by an Empyrean, he would lose the kirin fruit as well as his merit points. This would be a tremendous loss!

“Even if he defeated nine Great World Kings he still can’t defeat an Empyrean. Even the weakest of Empyreans can easily kill nine Great World Kings without allowing them any chance to escape.”

“That’s right, and this Empyrean Myriad Ghost isn’t too bad, he seems to be an intermediate Empyrean.”

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s Yellow Springs Temple was located in a great world within the Soul World – the Yellow Springs World. Empyrean Myriad Ghost was a renowned and infamous individual, and Yellow Springs Temple was an Empyrean influence he had established by himself. For many years, countless individuals had dreamed of entering Yellow Springs Temple, and the name of Empyrean Myriad Ghost reverberated like a thunderclap through the Yellow Springs World.

Then at this time, Empyrean Myriad Ghost suddenly attacked.

He stood still himself, but above his head, snow white bone claws came crashing down from the dark clouds, lit by endless motes of grave lights. The grave lights crackled around the white claws as they pierced through the void.

Roar - !

A terrifying dragon’s roar shook the earth. From those billowing black clouds, there was actually a giant bone dragon hidden within!

Even for an Empyrean it was difficult to subdue a God Beast. But, finding the complete skeleton of a God Beast was relatively much easier. Now, this giant bone dragon hiding in the clouds was a murder weapon that Empyrean Myriad Ghost had refined himself, and the material used to make it was the complete skeleton of a True Dragon!

This bone dragon’s claws carried with them an overwhelming potential as they came rumbling down at Lin Ming.

Of course, this bone dragon’s strength was also suppressed by the Akashic Dream Battlefield’s Laws.

Lin Ming fiercely looked up, an electric light racing through his eyes. From beneath his feet, waves of wind spread out in a circle.

Within his body, three Dao Palace opened wide their gates. Lin Ming’s body began to release the sound of deafening thunderclaps.

Waves of blood essence and blood vitality were wildly stimulated.

Lin Ming stood tall and straight like a spear. Then, an overbearingly tyrannical aura gushed out from him, followed by a dreadful blood energy.

Without evading or dodging, he shot up into the skies with his spear, violently colliding with those mountain-sized bone claws!

Lin Ming’s spear light was incomparably small when compared to the mountain-sized bone claws, but as the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace were opened within his body, his profound bodily potential erupted, giving him an incalculable level of strength.

In the outside world, Lin Ming’s strength was calculated with the power of dragons. This was a true dragon-subduing level of strength!

Like a meteor, Lin Ming’s spear light crashed into the bone claws.

Ka ka ka!

With an explosion that seemed to tear apart the heavens and earth, the bone dragon wailed in misery. Atop the seemingly unstoppable bone claws, countless runes shimmered. These runes were inscribed onto the junctions of the dragon bones and were the work of Empyrean Myriad Ghost. But under Lin Ming’s tremendous impact force, these runes began to radiate a blinding light as they started to visibly disintegrate.

Then, even the parts of the dragon bones connected to these runes began to crack!

A massive dragon bone claw was thus broken by Lin Ming. The joints shattered and bones came flying off!

Although Lin Ming hadn’t truly shattered the dragon bone and had only caused it to break apart, to the many people watching from below, it appeared that Lin Ming had crushed the giant bone dragon with a single strike!

Even though there was such a disproportionate difference in their bodies, this sort of mind-boggling scene had occurred. Everyone was left utterly shocked!

Was this the strength that a Divine Lord realm martial artist was supposed to possess?

Rahh!

The bone dragon howled out in agony. Lin Ming’s eyes flashed like lightning. He stepped forwards with the Space Laws and hurtled forwards. First he needed to deal with this bone dragon!

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s mind quaked. He thought that even if the bone dragon alone couldn’t defeat Lin Ming, it was still enough to suppress him. But, he never imagined that the bone dragon would be defeated in front of Lin Ming!

The cracks rapidly expanded and more and more bones came flying off. Lin Ming was fast and unstoppable!

His entire body was covered with purple Asura Law runes. The bone dragon’s runes were constantly destroyed and the dark clouds around him dispersed.

Finally, Empyrean Myriad Ghost moved.

He naturally wouldn’t watch helplessly as the bone puppet he refined with difficulty was reduced to a pile of broken bones by Lin Ming.

His bent body was covered with a dense and mystical black gas. Every inch of his skin that was exposed to the black gas had numerous malicious ghosts crawling and roaring out loud.

Shua!

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s speed was like ghosts and gods. He shot towards Lin Ming.

And in this moment, Lin Ming looked down. Blazing fire stars seemed to burn in his eyes. His sword-sharp divine sense immediately locked onto Empyrean Myriad Ghost!

At the same time, his aura became even more terrifying. All of the strength within his inner world erupted out together!

From the start, his goal had never been the bone dragon but Empyrean Myriad Ghost!

Woosh!

With a wave of his hand, the Phoenix Blood Spear was placed into his inner world. Then a black spear appeared in its place – the Black Dragon Spear.

As this spear appeared, space and time seemed to be cut apart by it, making everything come to a pause.

And what was also cut apart was Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s fierce and arrogant expression.

This spear!!

As Empyrean Myriad Ghost looked at this spear, he didn’t know why but an inexplicable sense of fear and alarm surged in his heart. His intuition told him that this spear carried with it an extremely terrifying aura! Perhaps in ancient times, this spear had cut down True Divinities!

This brat, just how could he have such an unrivalled weapon!?

Empyrean Myriad Ghost had no time to think about these thoughts, because at this time, Lin Ming attacked him!

Lin Ming wielded the Black Dragon Spear. The dreadful spear light carried with it star-like runes as it shot forth like a river of stars.

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s complexion turned cold. Although he was surprised, he wasn’t panicked. Seeing this spear light continuing to expand in front of him, he pushed out his left hand and began to grind space within it.

His entire palm changed as it was covered with black lights.

Every black light had skeletons floating within it. His palm was like a grinding pan that contained 10,000 ghosts, completely crushing the overwhelming spear light.

“Suppress!”

Empyrean Myriad Ghost shouted out loud. Not just that, but he also raised his right palm, bringing it together with his left palm.

As two palms gathered together, even space shattered as endless black fog spread out.

In the midst of this black fog, there were the sounds of rumbling thunderclouds as well as endless ghost towns looming in the fog.

The Yellow Springs River appeared, bleached bones rising high in its tide.

In this river, deep ghost temples floated up and down. 10,000 ghosts cried out from within, as if the Yellow Springs themselves had been brought here.

All strength in the surrounding area was completely swallowed up by this darkness.

Green grasses as well as the surrounding towering trees were tainted by traces of this black gas and rapidly dried up before decaying.

“Yellow Springs Ghost World!?”

A surrounding martial artist cried out in panic. This martial artist flew back several thousand feet further away, lest he be contaminated with even a tiny bit of the black gas.

This Yellow Springs Ghost World was the one of the peak comprehensions of Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s Ghost Laws. It could manifest a small world to suppress an enemy. Even though Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s cultivation had been suppressed, he could still use this Yellow Springs Ghost World technique!

The fiercest aspect of this Yellow Springs Ghost World was not in its ability to suppress enemies. Rather, its fiercest aspect was the fact that it could refine the suppressed enemies and make them a part of the Yellow Springs Ghost World.

Like this, the Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s Yellow Springs Ghost World would become increasingly perfect, increasingly powerful.

Lin Ming rushed towards Empyrean Myriad Ghost. Facing this Yellow Springs Ghost World that covered such an incredible range, it was impossible to try dodging it. Rather, he grasped the Black Dragon Spear and raced directly into the Yellow Springs Ghost World like an arrow.

Bang!

The darkness was blown apart. Lin Ming’s figure was completely swallowed up by the Yellow Springs Ghost World.

“He raced into the Yellow Springs Ghost World!”

Many people cried out in shock. To enter Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s domain was the same as seeking death. In particular, Lin Ming’s original cultivation boundary had been far weaker than Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s.

Seeing Lin Ming’s figure swallowed up, Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s face didn’t show any signs of relaxing. He slowly closed his hands, wanting to draw back in these Yellow Springs Ghost Laws and completely roll over Lin Ming.

But at this time, his entire body shook and his complexion changed.

He could feel a strength that made his mind shake erupting from the Yellow Springs Ghost World.

“…What?”

In the middle of the Yellow Springs Ghost World, the countless ghosts that had been climbing over Lin Ming and gnawing him, wanting to eat him up, had all disappeared without a trace.

Then, that black spear shot forwards, carrying with it an unknown and unstoppable power of Laws that seemed to annihilate all of existence.

And, this black spear was wrapped with numerous arcs of lightning. The arcs of lightning also spun around Lin Ming, exterminating any ghosts that came near him.

Every trace of lightning carried with it a vast and profound aura. This was the power of the top grade Thunder Source that Lin Ming had obtained from Empyrean Thunder Punishment.

Empyrean Thunder Punishment had been a superior Empyrean. Now that his power of thunder had been completely absorbed by Lin Ming, Lin Ming was able to display the potential of this power to its peak!

And the power of thunder was the ultimate nemesis of ghosts and spirits!

Chapter 1821 – Exterminating Myriad Ghost

As the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone and Soul Springs Divine Embryo joined forces, their strength multiplied to incredibly powerful levels. Moreover, Lin Ming’s two avatars did not fear death and their defensive abilities were astonishing. When attacking an enemy, they only went on the offensive, without any thoughts of defending.

The void was torn apart like rags and endless ghosts were annihilated. Empyrean Myriad Ghost felt his blood vitality tumbling within his body even as an intense pain struck his spiritual sea.

And in this moment, Lin Ming’s main body also attacked. His speed reached extreme levels. He shot through the energy storm that surrounded Empyrean Myriad Ghost and thrust out his spear!

Bang!

Lin Ming had poured the entirety of his strength into this strike.

Within his body, the Asura blood boiled over! Infinite Asura Laws erupted from within him, roaring like 10,000 God Beasts!

“Damn it!”

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s face twisted into a grotesque image. He thrust out his palm, and from it a hand-sized ghost streamer flew out. This ghost streamer rose through the wind, quickly growing to ten feet in size. From the ghost streamer, countless ghosts wailed together.

This was the billion ghost streamer that Empyrean Myriad Ghost had personally refined. There were a billion ghosts sealed within it!

The Black Dragon Spear smashed into this ghost streamer like an endless bolt of thunder. Innumerable ghosts instantly died within the ghost streamer!

Chi-la!

The sound of ripping fabric filled the air.

The Black Dragon Spear continued with overwhelming force; it pierced right through the ghost streamer!

A violent surge of energy washed out. The billion ghost streamer was torn apart by the Black Dragon Spear!

“What!?”

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s eyes turned red. Lin Ming’s mighty strength had completely surpassed his imagination.

He watched as the Black Dragon Spear was about to pierce through his body. And because of Lin Ming’s two avatars attacking him, Empyrean Myriad Ghost had already used up his moves and was yet to recover. It was impossible for him to resist this attack.

In this critical life or death moment, Empyrean Myriad Ghost gave up all thoughts of avoiding. Rather, he stretched out a demonic claw and slashed at Lin Ming’s chest!

“Junior, if you want to kill me then I’ll crush your heart!”

Lin Ming’s eyes were cold and resolute. He ignored Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s threat and welcomed the ghastly claws. His spear stabbed forwards without hesitation!

In that instant, the Asura blood surged within him. The power of Asura gathered at his chest, forming a layer of solid black scales.

Puff!

Lin Ming’s Black Dragon Spear thrust through Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s protective spirit essence as if it were tofu. Then, it penetrated through his chest, causing blood to spew out!

At the same time, Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s sharp claws also crashed into Lin Ming’s chest.

The black scales shattered and blood flew in all directions. Lin Ming’s chest was torn up by Empyrean Myriad Ghost, with several ribs breaking!

“How…”

Although Empyrean Myriad Ghost had torn apart Lin Ming’s chest, his eyes still filled with an incredulous light. His demon claws were the pinnacle of sharpness. Moreover, the corrosive power of the Poison Laws also coated his claws. In the outside world in a situation where his cultivation wasn’t suppressed, if his claws struck something then even an ordinary Empyrean spirit treasure would lose a great deal of its spiritual power and be severely damaged.

And even though this claw was suppressed by the Laws, it still possessed a heaven-defying attack power. Yet, Empyrean Myriad Ghost hadn’t been able to thrust his claw into Lin Ming’s chest and grab his heart. Lin Ming’s mortal body was as hard as divine iron.

“You’ve already used your moves and it’s impossible for this hasty attack of yours to break through my defenses.”

If this were Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s all out strike, then Lin Ming wouldn’t have been able to resist it with his body even if he revolved the Asura blood to its limits. But, this hasty attack was something he could defend against.

“You’re finished!”

Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear, pouring a wild amount of strength into it. For a time, above Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s body, the wound caused by the Black Dragon Spear suddenly began spinning, becoming a dark black hole.

Within this hole, a massive vortex shined with a black light, emitting a strange mystic strength that swallowed all.

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s face distorted. He revolved his energy to the limit to resist the corrosion of this black light and force the Black Dragon Spear out from his body.

But as soon as he tried, his body violently shook. He turned around.

Behind him, two figures had appeared like ghosts and gods. The dense cold light of their weapons reflected on his body; it was too late to dodge!

Puff! Puff!

Two sharp weapons pierced through flesh. Behind Empyrean Myriad Ghost, the black-clothed Lin Ming and purple-clothed Lin Ming had attacked together. A golden spear and a purple sword thrust out, piercing through Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s body!

Blood gushed out. Empyrean Myriad Ghost had been simultaneously struck by three weapons, and these three weapons were all held by three different Lin Mings.

This scene was truly alarming!

“I… I…” Empyrean Myriad Ghost vomited a great mouthful of blood. The endless Ghost Laws on his body fluttered out, trying to resist that horrifying black light. But no matter what he tried, it didn’t matter. Beneath the corrosion of the black light, his body began to slowly disintegrate.

In the Akashic Dream Battlefield, the feeling of dying was the same as in reality. As an Empyrean, when would Empyrean Myriad Ghost have experienced such a feeling? As he stared at Lin Ming, his eyes clouded over with disbelief.

He had been defeated beneath the hands of a junior! How could he accept this!?

“I hate you! If my cultivation hadn’t been suppressed, I would have slaughtered you like a dog!”

As Empyrean Myriad Ghost spoke, blood spewed out from between his lips. Lin Ming coldly poured more energy into the Black Dragon Spear. Fissures began to appear all over Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s body, dripping with blood.

Ka ka ka!

Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s body continually broke down. Soon, with a loud explosive sound, Empyrean Myriad Ghost’s body burst into an endless cloud of blood that rained to the ground.

After several breaths of time, in the place where Empyrean Myriad Ghost had existed, all that remained was a hazy blood mist as well as the tattered remnants of ghost energy…

Like this, an Empyrean of his generation had disappeared from the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

Watching from the sidelines, the entire audience of martial artists fell silent.

This human had killed an Empyrean!

In the Akashic Dream Battlefield, the strongest existence was an Empyrean. To kill an Empyrean proved that Lin Ming was invincible within the Akashic Dream Battlefield!

Who was he!?

“Devil!”

Some people cried out in fear, as if no one in this world was a match for this human.

The disciples of Zenith Palace had already lost all ability to speak. The strongest Highest Elder of Zenith Palace was only an ordinary World King, and amidst ordinary World Kings he was amongst the weaker ones. Even so, to them, a World King was a lofty and unattainable existence.

As for a Great World King, that was no different from a spiritual god to them. And an Empyrean… that was something they could not imagine. With a wave of a hand, an Empyrean could destroy a trillion lives.

Yet such an existence had been killed by this human junior! Even in the Akashic Dream Battlefield where cultivations were suppressed by the Laws, they simply couldn’t wrap their minds around this.

In their impression, an Empyrean should never be defeated.

In particular, what they couldn’t accept the most was that not too long ago, Lin Ming was still in their Zenith Palace. Many people had shouted at Lin Ming and Yi Fan had vowed to take revenge against him.

As they recalled that scene, the disciples of Zenith Palace suddenly developed ugly complexions. Why had this human appeared at Zenith Palace?

“I suspect that… the space storm at the Great Desolate Glacier… was likely caused by this Lin Muk…”

The Zenith Vice Palace Master suddenly said, causing the several Elders of Zenith Palace to shrink their necks and a cold chill to crawl up their backs. That terrifying space storm had sheared off a million glaciers and all of this was because of this junior…

Thinking about it, this was extremely likely. Otherwise, how could there be such a coincidence that he would appear there and at that time?

“No matter what, he is only a traveler. He should have been severely wounded and temporarily rested at Zenith Palace. In truth, he has no feelings towards Zenith Palace and will eventually depart on his own…”

Jaderiver suddenly said, a hint of sadness in her voice. She was a woman whose heart was higher than the heavens. But as she saw Lin Ming who was destined to leave them and who also possessed such incredible achievements, she couldn’t help but develop a sense of inferiority...

……

At this moment, Lin Ming grasped the Black Dragon Spear, his entire body stained red with blood. Countless scattered ghost spirits wound around him, continuing to emit their last sobs and howls. Standing in the midst of all this, Lin Ming resembled a death god. For everyone present, this was a sight that they would never forget in their lifetimes.

“It’s over. I’ve killed an Empyrean!”

At this time, Lin Ming held his token, feeling it grow hotter and hotter. All sorts of emotions surged in his body.

This was the first time that Lin Ming had struck down an Empyrean, and he was also a middle ranked Empyrean!

Although his cultivation was suppressed, killing him had made Lin Ming excited to the point of trembling.

He desired strength far too much!

With the great calamity imminent, Lin Ming needed the ability to at least contend with an Empyrean. Only then would he be able to play a minor role in the great calamity.

And even this goal seemed extremely distant for Lin Ming.

The token grew increasingly hot, as if it would melt down.

The merit points grew at a mind-boggling pace!

Lin Ming watched as his merit points rapidly rose. In a short time, they almost doubled in number!

After killing an Empyrean, the merit points Lin Ming obtained were equal to the sum total from everyone else he had killed so far!

Lin Ming took a deep breath, a fervent light in his eyes.

At this time, his chest was also bleeding. But the blood vitality had already gathered there, slowly regenerating the wound caused by Empyrean Myriad Ghost.

As those below watched this, they had no idea what to say.

Not only did this human have incredible combat strength, but his recovery abilities were also dreadful. He was simply a God Beast in human form, perhaps even more abnormal than a God Beast!

In the future, once he grew, just how terrifying would he become?

At this time, Lin Ming swallowed a pill. The reason he had taken an attack to kill Empyrean Myriad Ghost was in truth to force the battle to a quick end. To him, suffering some injuries wasn’t much at all, because his regenerative capabilities were amazing.

Rather, consuming a massive amount of energy was the most dangerous scenario for Lin Ming.

He didn’t want to be exhausted of energy in such a dangerous environment. After all, there was still an existence in the Akashic Dream Battlefield that could threaten him.

If he retained his strength, then even if he couldn’t defeat the enemy he could still escape. But if he exhausted all of his energy and was killed by this person, then that would be the same as gifting himself to others.

“An Empyrean is truly formidable…”

Lin Ming recalled the battle. In terms of Laws alone, he was slightly inferior to Empyrean Myriad Ghost. He had relied on other aspects to win.

“If I wasn’t facing Empyrean Myriad Ghost but Sheng Mei, then even if our cultivations were suppressed to the same boundary, I could not face her…” Lin Ming quickly judged his own strength. Just because he had been able to crush the Undying Polar Ice’s frozen egg didn’t mean that he was equivalent to Sheng Mei at the same cultivation boundary.

Chapter 1823 – Hidden Treasures

News of Lin Ming killing Empyrean Myriad Ghost and forcing Chaos Demon God to retreat soon spread throughout the entire Akashic Dream Battlefield.

The two Empyreans had originally entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield to duel each other, but their battles hadn’t been seen by anyone, nor had they gone all-out. Rather, they had only exchanged a few initial probing strikes. But now, they were both ruined by Lin Ming. One had been directly killed and the other had fled in the eyes of all present.

This was a simply unimaginable situation!

For a time, the terrifying name of Lin Muk spread throughout the entire Akashic Dream Battlefield. This was news that came from Zenith Palace.

The young disciples of Zenith Palace couldn’t help but brag about their relationship with Lin Ming, thus they naturally used the name he had given them – Lin Muk.

On the Akashic Dream Battlefield, people felt fear and awe upon hearing this name. This was especially true for the World Kings and Great World Kings here. They were afraid that they would accidently bump into Lin Ming and wouldn’t even have any hopes of escaping, eventually becoming a part of Lin Ming’s merit points.

However, none of this news spread outside the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Once the Akashic Dream Battlefield was sealed up, no one would know what occurred within until the full three years had passed.

However, Lin Ming simply didn’t care about any of this at all.

Alone, he trod deep into the vast desolate woods. Not too far behind, a little girl followed.

She wore a bright red dress and her rosy feet were bare as she stepped upon the wind. Her snow white toes were like ten pearls, glowing with a crystalline light.

In this forest there were countless giant ancient vicious beasts, in other words, soul beasts. These soul beasts were particularly fierce and would launch continuous ambushes, creating a good deal of trouble for Lin Ming.

However, what surprised Lin Ming was that the little girl simply fluttered forwards, unnoticed by these soul beasts.

No matter how formidable the soul beasts were, they would just run past her without sparing her a glance.

From deep within the ancient forest, there was a mystic and formidable aura that emanated outwards.

Lin Ming also discovered the existence of this aura. He grew increasingly sure that the hidden treasure the red-dressed little girl spoke of was this existence.

This ancient forest seemed to have existed for countless billions of years. Each leaf was as large as a house.

Any rays of light that shined down were blocked by layers of thick leaves, filtering out to a dim haze that left mottled shadows on the ground.

“What is that?”

Lin Ming suddenly paused. In the forest, his figure flashed, instantly travelling hundreds of miles.

Soon, he reached the edge of the ancient forest. What he suddenly saw in front of him was a vast outcropping of rocks, a stone forest that towered in an open space for hundreds of miles.

This stone forest was vast. As Lin Ming leapt up to the canopy of the trees, he looked down and saw that the shape of this stone forest resembled that of a hand.

The five fingers were represented by five massive towering stone formations.

The way that the central region was set up resembled a palm.

This stone forest was covered in a dense blanket of brilliant light that dazzled the eyes.

Waves of strange runes shot up from the stone forest, rising up like a river of stars.

A bird soul beast that had a wingspan of over 30 feet flew out from the forest and into the broad skies. However, it carefully avoided the stone forest, as if there was something terrifying within it.

This caused Lin Ming’s mind to chill.

The stone forest should be the hidden treasure trove that the little girl spoke of. However, this hidden treasure area contained a horrifying aura.

Lin Ming frowned. He drew back his gaze from the stone forest and slowly turned around.

Behind him, atop the ground that looked like rocky sand, the red-dressed girl was calmly floating.

“You said that the hidden treasure area is in this stone forest?” He knew that this little girl was extremely timid, thus he tried to keep his voice as gentle as possible.

“Mm.” Looking at the stone forest, a strange and lonely look crossed the red-dressed little girl’s face, followed by confusion. Then, she looked towards Lin Ming and rapidly nodded.

Chirp chirp!

The kirin fruit cried out, revealing a horrified look as it stared at the stone forest. It was unknown just what it was afraid of.

But why would Lin Ming care about whether this little fruit was scared? He put away the kirin fruit and said, “Let’s go!”

Lin Ming called out to the little girl. Then, he cautiously approached the mysterious stone forest.

But before long, he suddenly stopped, a look of amazement crossing his face.

All he felt was an invisible, mountain-like atmosphere enveloping him. A tremendous pressure fell upon every inch of his skin, pressing down on his shoulders. Even though he had billions of jins of strength, he still found it onerous to move.

Every joint in his body emitted popping sounds. However, he was still 10 miles away from the stone forest.

But what startled him the most was not this formidable and invisible aura, but the fact that within this aura, there was a familiar feeling.

It was because this aura was not just simple soul force. Rather, it contained the power of ‘energy’, from the essence gathering system.

This was a simply unthinkable matter. The Akashic Dream Battlefield was only a small part of the Akashic Dream World. The Akashic Dream World itself was a treasure left behind by the first ancestor of all spiritas, an existence that surpassed the realm of True Divinity.

Everything inside should be formed from the purest soul force, so how could such a pure and rich power from the essence gathering system have appeared here?

Lin Ming was puzzled. He let out a deep breath and his blood vitality began to surge within his body, flowing like an endlessly raging river.

From every pore of his body, an invisible astral energy shot out, forcefully resisting the strange pressure that was everywhere around him.

Hu - !

Hu - !

After energizing the blood vitality essence energy within his body, he forcefully split apart the potent pressure like a river, causing it to flow around him.

Step by step, he slowly approached the mysterious stone forest.

“Mm? What is this power? This… power is clearly one of the 33 Heavens’ Great Daos.

“This is also another Great Dao power of the 33 Heavens…”

The closer Lin Ming came to the stone forest, the more shocked he became. He began to feel more and more Great Dao systems as he approached the stone forest.

Moreover, what was most peculiar of all was that even though these powers didn’t belong to the Akashic Dream World, they weren’t suppressed, weakened, or even repelled.

This completely subverted Lin Ming’s understandings of the 33 Heavens’ Great Daos.

“To leave behind such a tremendous aura that contains the Great Daos of the 33 Heavens… could this stone forest have been left behind by a True Divinity level character? No… even a True Divinity level character shouldn’t possess the power of so many Great Daos from the 33 Heavens… as far as I know, the only one who has managed to grasp the power of so many Great Daos, through the endless ages, has only been the Asura Road Master…”

As Lin Ming was thinking about all of this, he reached less than a mile from the stone forest.

Even though his body was as intense as an ancient vicious beast, at this time, he was being suppressed by the Great Dao aura of the 33 Heavens. His skin and his bones constantly distorted as wave-like ripples passed over him. Even his face twisted beneath the unimaginably huge pressure, continuously changing.

Every inch of Lin Ming’s body felt as if it were being grinded by a pan; the pain was agonizing.

Lin Ming took another step forwards –

Hum! Hum! Hum!

From his originally quiet dantian, the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram began to quietly tremble and hum. The array formation that was fused into his flesh and blood began to emanate waves of the Asura Heavenly Dao’s strength.

The Asura Heavenly Array Diagram was left behind by the Asura Road Master and was formed by combining the three source energies of ‘essence, energy, and divine’. It could reform an image of the Asura Road within his body, so that the power he obtained from the Asura Road wouldn’t be suppressed and repelled by the Great Daos of the 33 Heavens. This array diagram that fused into Lin Ming was one of the ultimate rewards he received from the Asura Road’s final trial.

In ordinary times, as long as Lin Ming didn’t use the power of the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws then the Asura Heavenly Array Diagram would remain dormant, without any movement at all.

But at this time, it actually resonated with some strange force and was opening on its own.

Even the numerous divine runic symbols that Lin Ming had on him didn’t remain calm. The Asura Heavenly Dao Laws within them also began to emit keening cries.

“This is… the aura of the Asura Road Master!?”

Lin Ming’s sharp senses perceived the aura of the Asura Road Master. Moreover, it was from the mysterious stone forest.

This vast and boundless aura seemed to contain a momentum that could swallow the universe. Even as Lin Ming was shocked, he still felt an intimate familiarity with it.

Moreover, as this aura appeared, the auras of the 33 Heavens’ Great Daos were suddenly weakened. The pressure on Lin Ming lightened by a great deal.

More and more suspicions appeared in Lin Ming’s mind. Why would the aura of the Asura Road Master appear here?

This was the Akashic Dream World.

Did the Asura Road Master… also step into the Akashic Dream World before?

This thought suddenly flashed through Lin Ming’s mind, leaving him feeling inexplicably astonished.

Chapter 1824 – Ancient Ruins

Lin Ming looked towards the red-dressed little girl. The little girl’s vacant look confirmed that he wouldn’t be able to obtain any valuable information from her, such as why the aura of the Asura Road Master was kept here.

The two slowly approached the stone forest. For a time, the entire stone forest seemed to come alive with movement. Flower petals formed from the Great Dao began to fall down from the skies, turning into strange runes that blocked out the world.

Lin Ming and the little girl were also blocked out. It was an incomprehensible defensive array formation.

“Wah!”

The little girl cried out in surprise. The soul force she emitted seemed to come into conflict with this aura and was bounced back by the array formation, nearly causing her to be injured.

However, the little girl surprised Lin Ming yet again. Her body seemed to be weightless. As she was pushed back by this strange energy, she fluttered backwards like a piece of cotton.

Like this, she flew backwards several dozen feet before gently landing.

“What’s wrong?”

“T-t-this place is a b-b-bit strange. Every time I come I will be b-b-bitten by something strange… b-but last time it wasn’t so s-s-strong…”

After being with Lin Ming for such a long time, the little girl’s voice seemed to smooth out, as if all her previous speaking problems were because she hadn’t spoken with anyone for far too long a time.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but look at her and ask, “How old are you?”

The red-dressed little girl revealed a dazed expression. After a while she shook her head and said, “I d-d-don’t know… I s-s-seem to have slept for a long time, b-but for some reason, I woke up afterwards and I ended up h-here… and then… I… o-often see outsiders come h-here and try to catch me… as well as my friends…”

The red-dressed little girl spoke with a frown, as if these were memories she didn’t want to remember.

Lin Ming was dumbfounded. This little girl’s life experiences were far too strange.

According to what she said, she had likely lived for a long time already and had been deeply slumbering for most of the time.

And as for the outsiders, they were naturally the trial challengers that came to the Akashic Dream Battlefield. When these people searched for treasures in this mystic realm, they undoubtedly disturbed the rest of the little girl, and the spirit medicines they tried to take were similar to spiritual medicines like the kirin fruit who were able to manifest themselves.

“No wonder this little girl was guarded when she saw me, and seemed to fear me. Just who is she? Why does she seem like Fishy…?”

Lin Ming suddenly recalled Yan Littlefish. Although Fishy seemed like an ordinary little girl on the outside, she was actually an enigma that could eat violet sun stones and nine sun jades as if they were candy.

She also didn’t remember how long she had lived. But, her age didn’t match her mindset. It seemed that her thoughts had stayed at the level of a little child, always a bit dull and silly.

Her appearance had also never changed. She always resembled a little girl in her early teens, never growing, never aging.

“This array formation… is naturally formed by the 33 Heavens’ Great Dao, it is not made by mortal hands. In order to enter, one has to follow the Great Dao Laws of the 33 Heavens.” Lin Ming thought for a moment. His eyes focused on the array formation in front of him. Within his pupils, tens of thousands of runes were reflected, weaving together in the skies like endless stars, vast and profound…

There were similarities between this array formation and divine runic symbols.

He had studied divine runic symbols for many years and had absorbed the memories of many divine runic masters. His background was deep and he was confident that he could solve this array formation.

For some time, he began making innumerable deductions in his mind.

Slowly, he found a vein of the defensive array formation. Spear light flicked out from his fingertips, loudly smashing into a node of the array formation.

Like a giant stone falling into a calm lake, strong ripples began to spread outwards.

The entire array formation suddenly collapsed.

This incomparably dense stone forest began to decay and collapse at a speed visible to the eyes.

This was an erosion produced by endless years of weathering. Lin Ming was shocked to see this.

The earth beneath his feet began to violently shake. The surrounding space started to change. In an instant, the stone forest in front of him had disappeared.

Hu - !

An ice cold wind howled above him.

The world in front of him turned into an incredibly bleak and desolate wasteland. The rugged stones in the ground emitted a chilling aura.

Not too far away, a hellish black abyss was exposed to the air, emitting a boundless mystic strength.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. His figure flickered and he appeared hundreds of miles away. As he arrived at the edge of the black abyss, he peered inside.

His entire body shook. The black abyss was fathomless, without anything visible at all. Rather, he felt two auras that caused his heart to tremble.

One of these auras was an incomparably pure black energy, one that released an unspeakable oppressive feeling, as if all living beings to exist had to bow before it.

It was vigorous and powerful.

This was a mass of soul force that had reached the pinnacle of purity, and even contained the feel of the Great Dao.

Without a doubt, this was the limit of soul force. The purity and depth of this soul force far surpassed even that of Soul Empress Sheng Mei.

As this soul force surged, there were infinite changes within.

Just by glancing at it, one’s heart would race, feeling as if their divine soul would be swallowed up.

As for the other aura, it was one that Lin Ming was familiar with – the aura of the Asura Road Master.

This aura carried with it the strength of the Asura Heavenly Dao, as deep as an endless ocean. It was majestic and daring, with a killing intent that soared into the heavens, seeming capable of crushing the universe itself.

These two auras had existed in this space since time immemorial, faintly struggling with each other and colliding with each other, with no distinction of rank between them.

“Who is this person? They can contend with the Asura Road Master on the same level?”

Lin Ming was surprised. He discovered that this soul force that fought with the Asura Road Master’s remnant aura was not any worse.

Because of the peerless array formation here, this soul force as well as the Asura Road Master’s aura had been sealed in an independent world, not dissipating even after billions upon billions of years. Rather, it faintly formed its own Heavenly Dao system and continuously grew.

Countless runes spun out, vividly dancing in the darkness of space.

Lin Ming revolved the power of the Asura Laws and looked at these runes with rapt attention. Even though his eyes became a little sore, he made a bewildering discovery. These runes that danced in the air were like history books, recording unimaginable scenes within them.

Lin Ming discovered that at the end of the abyss beneath him, there was yet another abyss, one that was deep and without end.

Within that abyss, a grand aura also surged outwards.

That abyss was incredibly dense, riddling this entire world like a honeycomb.

“Could this be an ancient battlefield from when the Asura Road Master was fighting with someone else?”

Lin Ming thought, dumbfounded. The Asura Road Master had lived billions of years ago. Such a broken world could only appear if struck by a great strength.

Just as he thought this, the black clouds of energy that camouflaged the void began to fade away.

Stars twinkled in space, distant and cold in the endless void.

Trillions of stars continued without end, even hanging above his head. Looking up, he could make out strange stones and inexhaustible mountain ranges.

These stars emitted a boundless mystical power of stars.

Lin Ming was standing on a star, but amongst the boundless stars in the universe, it was only an ordinary one.

Taking a broad look around, he could see that the innumerable stars around him were tattered and riddled with holes, verging on the point of collapse.

Even further away, at the center of the galaxy, there were massive wreckages of annihilated stars burning there.

At the center of the galaxy, there were no more stars or dust. Rather, there was only a pitch black and burning red light shining endlessly from within.

These two lights were like two universes. With just a single glance, Lin Ming’s chest violently trembled, as if he had been struck by some large invisible hand.

Strong. These were two absolutely strong forces.

Time passed. Even the erosion of time wasn’t able to cause these two groups of power to disappear.

Instead, they formed the Laws of the heavens and earth, becoming like yin and yang, mutually elevating and constraining each other, growing together.

They were like infinite suns exploding. An incomprehensibly powerful mystic strength was imprisoned, seeming to exist for eternity.

“Mm? This is?”

Lin Ming could vaguely see an image…

The Asura was standing in the pitch black cold of space. He wore black armor and his pupils shined with a terrifying light.

He was fighting a man with a similarly terrifying aura. This man walked the distant end of the galaxy where they began to fight each other.

The Asura’s fist shadows were vigorous and vast, each fist shadow strike tearing apart the universe. Endless stars cracked apart, swallowing up the man that walked in from the other side of the galaxy.

In these endless shadows, the man pulled out a strange ancient black book.

He began to recite scriptures. The scriptures turned into ancient words that spread out from the Asura’s rain of fist shadows.

Every ancient word changed into columns of soul force in the void. They tore through the galaxy and collided with the Asura’s fist shadows. Terrifying fluctuations of energy spread out, tearing apart large tracts of space and destroying millions of stars…

This battle continued for a mind-boggling period of time. It was unknown how many years they fought or how many billions of stars were crushed.

In the end, the mysterious man’s forehead was scratched by the Asura Road Master’s fist shadows. His star-heavy blood fell down, crashing into the boundless space below.

With this, a mysterious page from the ancient black book in the man’s hands also fell down…

After this scene, all illusions collapsed. Lin Ming reappeared at the edge of the giant abyss. Asura runes shimmered in front of him.

What Lin Ming saw just now were the records contained within the runes born from the Asura Heavenly Dao Laws…

Lin Ming took a deep breath – the mysterious man that fought with the Asura Road Master was naturally the ancient first ancestor of the spiritas.

The center of the galaxy had been their final battlefield.

In the Asura Road’s final trial, at the end of the mysterious blue stone road, Lin Ming had seen the Asura Road Master fight with this mysterious man.

But the outcome of that battle had been unknown.

However, Lin Ming now knew the final result – the ancient king of the spiritas had lost to the Asura Road Master!

But, the Asura Road Master had also been injured.

Moreover, the incomparably ancient and mysterious book had a golden page fall out from it, making it incomplete.

Chapter 1828 – The End of the Battlefield

“Senior… Senior Solitude!”

The fat man’s face turned ashen. In his opinion, the One-legged World King was a god-like existence, yet he had been killed like a chicken?

He felt as if he were living in some bizarre dream.

Lin Ming’s spear seemed average and simple, so why hadn’t the One-legged World King been able to avoid it?

Rather, in the fat man’s thoughts, even if the One-legged World King decided not to dodge, that spear still shouldn’t have been able to harm him at all.

Not only was the fat man in a daze, but so was everyone else. With their eyesight, they naturally weren’t able to discern the mysterious Laws within Lin Ming’s spear strike, nor were they able to judge how fast Lin Ming’s spear had been. Because of the confusion brought by the Space and Time Laws, Lin Ming’s spear gave off the feeling of an endless illusion, making it seem incomparably slow.

“You… you’re that human from Emperor City!”

The fat man remembered Lin Ming. At Emperor City, Lin Ming’s status as a human had left an impression on him. However, his complexion now changed, as if he seemed to recall something horrifying.

He wasn’t an idiot; he instantly thought of who Lin Ming might really be!

However, before he could even say anything, the Phoenix Blood Spear was also piercing towards his throat!

As the fat man saw this spear coming towards him, he wanted to move away. But in that moment, he felt his body locked down by an inexplicable power of Laws, rooting his every action in place. All he could do was stare haplessly on as this spear came shooting towards him.

“This is the reason why Senior Solitude wasn’t able to avoid that killing strike?”

This was the fat man’s last thought in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. With a light popping sound, the spear penetrated through his throat.

The fat man’s life had been instantly severed.

Two people had continuously died, included among them a top master like the One-legged World King. Even so, Lin Ming didn’t erupt with any aura at all, and he didn’t even seem to take a single step anywhere.

Such a scene was truly frightening.

“Death God Lin Muk…”

Someone sputtered out. They weren’t ignorant when it came to the news that was being spread around. They knew there was a horrifying youth who had slain Empyrean Myriad Ghost and had been hunting down World Kings and Great World Kings.

To them, a Great World King was an unreachable existence. But to Lin Ming, they were only walking merit points.

They recalled what Lin Ming had said when he killed the One-legged World King.

“A billion merit points… I finally have it.”

With this, how could they not know who Lin Ming was?

“He’s killed enough to reach… a billion merit points.”

Everyone found this hard to imagine. The merit points that Lin Ming mentioned must be after his skeletal age was factored in. The original amount must be an astronomical figure.

Lin Ming turned his head and looked at the gathered people, causing them all to be scared witless.

“Screw off!”

Lin Ming harshly said. Towards these weaklings, he couldn’t be bothered to kill them.

With this, people scattered in droves, fleeing in all directions.

However, the many disciples of Zenith Palace remained. This was because their Senior-apprentice Sister Jaderiver hadn’t moved.

Jaderiver looked at Lin Ming. She wanted to speak but hesitated.

Lin Ming looked at Jaderiver. During this trip into the Akashic Dream Battlefield, Lin Ming had crossed paths with the disciples of Zenith Palace twice; they could be considered as sharing a strand of fate. Moreover, when Lin Ming entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield, he had used a token from Zenith Palace to do so.

“The profound spring lotus is yours.”

Lin Ming had already heard the name of this spirit medicine from Zenith Palace and the other influences here. As a spirit medicine that was worth less than a transcendent divine pill, Lin Ming had no need for it at all.

If he gave this spirit medicine to Zenith Palace, it could be considered as completing their cycle of karma.

“Lin Muk…”

Jaderiver seemed to want to say something, but just as she parted her lips, Lin Ming’s figure had already disappeared into the endless skies. The only thing left was his voice that echoed through the mountain valley.

As time passed, the name of Death God Lin Muk experienced an unprecedented peak, but afterwards, talk of him began to die down. He appeared a few more times until finally he completely vanished.

However, at this time, most of the masters within the Akashic Dream Battlefield, not including Chaos Demon God who was still hiding somewhere, had already perished.

As for Lin Ming, he returned once more to the mystic realm where the Asura Road Master and the ancient spiritas king had fought. He began to peacefully meditate on the Laws in that ancient ruin once more.

His cultivation had risen far too quickly; he needed time to stabilize himself.

Time slowly passed. Lin Ming calmly meditated at the edge of the abyss. As for the red-dressed little girl, she hovered like a ghost in that mystic realm, often wandering in a daze around Lin Ming. She would sit on a pitch black cliff and look into the stars shining in the distance, as if remembering something that had occurred in times long gone.

Lin Ming didn’t know what the red-dressed little girl was recalling, but he could feel that during these past days her speaking had become increasingly smooth, and she didn’t stutter as much as she used to.

With this, the three year deadline arrived…

………..

Outside the Akashic Dream Battlefield, at Emperor City –

A powerful aura surged into the skies.

The clouds in the sky were torn apart like pieces of cloth.

A magnificent palace emitted a sun-bright light, dazzling as it floated in the void, exuding a sense of awe and power.

Standing outside the palace were a number of maids. All of them had their auras restrained; it was clear they had amazing cultivations.

There was also a mountain-sized golden chariot that emitted a boundless light. It faintly struggled with the floating palace, making others unable to look directly at it.

There was also a powerful figure standing high in the clouds, shrouded in shadows. It was impossible to see his appearance, but he exuded a vast aura that was as deep as a sea. He was definitely some absolute powerhouse, and no one dared to underestimate him.

These were great influences from all over. They came here to meet the proud children of heaven who had entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

“The Akashic Dream Battlefield will close soon. My descendants certainly must have shined with glory, suppressing all the other heroes.”

“Purple Chestnut will certainly have brought honor to my spirit race.” A tall king of the spirit race said.

“Hehe, just being a genius isn’t enough to rise to prominence. There are some old monsters in there. This time, I wonder just how many so-called geniuses of their sects must have been defeated within.” Someone said. Indeed, a genius was terrifying, but compared to those old monsters that had been cultivating for a long time, they were naturally of a lower level.

If these old monsters disregarded their status to attack these young elites, then those young elites would suffer serious losses.

The scene became increasingly grand. Many influences had entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Now, they all rushed to Emperor City to greet the opening of the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

The Akashic Dream Battlefield was only a tiny part of the Akashic Dream Universe. The Akashic Dream Universe was far too broad and encompassed the seven Heavens of the Soul World. There was more than one Akashic Dream Battlefield, and these different Akashic Dream Battlefields opened at different times.

Wanting to enter the Akashic Dream Universe was easy, but wanting to enter the Akashic Dream Battlefield was different. One required tokens, and even large influences had limited numbers of tokens.

High in the skies, a limitlessly large purple gate exuded a glorious light, blinding to the eyes.

An inexplicable strength flowed outwards.

This gate had been closed for three years, and now it was finally opening. This also signaled the end of the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

“They’re coming out.”

Someone excitedly shouted from the crowds of people. There were some ordinary influences who were particularly concerned about their results. They hoped that their disciples were able to pressure their rivals and gain some face for their sect.

For many disciples, the results from the Akashic Dream Battlefield concerned the future development of their sect. How could they not be nervous!?

In that moment, the purple gate rumbled open. Horrifying air waves burst out, following by innumerable figures that whizzed by.

A powerful scent of blood and iron filled the air.

Many influences moved forwards to greet these people.

A youth flew in front of an old man and took out a token. The old man chuckled happily.

“My good child, you’ve done well. Hehe, you’ve truly brought a smile to grandpa’s face.” The old man lovingly patted this youth’s head. He could sense the light shining from the merit points token and could tell that his grandson had killed many people. He was extremely proud of his grandson’s achievements.

“Wonderful, it seems my Blood Tree Clan did quite well. You’ve killed five or six people each… mm… and this also includes a peak Holy Lord powerhouse? Good, I am very satisfied.” The Blood Tree Clan Elder said, looking towards the several Blood Tree Clan youths. They had strange turbans wrapped around their heads that exuded a mystical strength; it was quite bizarre.

“What? Our sect only has you remaining? Who did this!?” Another Elder howled out in sorrow. As he looked at the scarred disciples in front of him, his slaughter intent soared to the heavens.

“The Deep East Family… actually plotted against you all… good, very good, I didn’t think they would be so vicious!” Another sect master said through a clenched jaw.

All of the various influences began to vigorously search for their own disciples in the throngs of people.

Some influences were pleased to see their disciples have outstanding results. Some influences gnashed their teeth, preparing to retaliate against their enemies.

For a time, the scene was bustling with activity.

In front of the Emperor God Wall, masses of people milled about.

Chapter 1829 - Fall of an Empyrean

The boundless Emperor God Wall had stood tall for countless hundreds of millions of years.

The pressure that rolled off the Emperor God Wall was as oppressive as a cage. No one dared to approach too close. As for those people with poor cultivations, their spiritual seas would be directly crushed to smithereens if they were too near.

Suddenly, in front of the Emperor God Wall, a dazzling light shined out.

From the crowds of people, several hundred robed youths raised up their tokens together.

Their tokens began to erupt with a glorious brilliance.

Each ray of light shined upon the Emperor God Wall and was intercepted by a rune.

These runes turned into a number in the void.

As more and more beams of light shined out from the tokens, all sorts of numbers formed in space, finally becoming a numerical value.

“93,420 merit points!”

In front of many disciples, a sect Elder with a snow white beard shivered with excitement as he read this number.

This was the total number of merit points obtained by everyone in their sect.

“Wonderful!” A Sovereign from a small sect wearing an embroidered robe smiled brightly. This result had far exceeded his expectations.

It was considered a good result to have a hundred disciples emerge from the Akashic Dream Battlefield, but this time, there were several hundred people leaving. This was an event worth celebrating.

These merit point would provide their sect with many advantages.

The sects and various influences gathered in front of the Emperor God Wall, using their tokens to exchange for merit points.

Those from the same sect could combine their tokens together so that their merit points would become the total merit points of the sect.

Some smaller sects were ecstatic. They discovered that the number of people who survived this round of the Akashic Dream Battlefield was far higher than before.

Some of these smaller sects even managed to obtain several tens of thousands of merit points; this was far too lucky. These merit points also indicated that their sects were quite strong. The sect leaders all grinned from ear to ear, bursting with joy.

In front of the Emperor God Wall, all sorts of voices rose up.

The proud children of heaven from many influences appeared together, meeting those who waited for them.

But there were also some influences that were extremely gloomy, the expressions of their people dark and somber.

These influences discovered that their people actually didn’t appear.

“The entire spirit race together only has 890,000 merit points?” In front of the Emperor God Wall, the spirit race influence’s merit points were displayed for all to see.

This immediately caused a loud disturbance and intense discussion.

“How is that possible? The spirit race is such a large clan so it’s unbelievable that their total merit points are less than 3 million. But this time they actually have less than a million.”

“Hey, did you all notice that the Purple Chestnut King hasn’t appeared? Did he die inside?” Some influences were beyond shocked as they saw this.

“Aish…”

A spirit race Elder was enraged, his voice rising like a billowing thunder cloud, causing the air in front of the Emperor God Wall to violently ripple.

“Who killed the Purple Chestnut King of my people? Who killed my spirit race’s five Great World Kings?”

“Hmm? How come the shaman hasn’t appeared?”

“Where did Elder Duanmu go? Was he killed inside?”

From the camps of some large influences, angry roars began to sound out.

In front of the Emperor God Wall, embarrassing scenes began to take place. There were some large influences that couldn’t even obtain a million merit points.

In comparison to the harvests of the smaller influences, the contrast was far too sharp.

Many people were startled to discover that from those large influences that couldn’t reach a million merit points, their shamans or Great World Kings had perished.

The truth was that because of their age, these Great World Kings couldn’t provide many merit points to the sect to begin with. However, they could play a great deterring role; they were considered the protective talismans of these sects.

With a Great World King accompanying these groups, the situation would be completely different. But if these Great World Kings died, the sect teams might be eaten up by others without anything remaining.

Soon, the relative disparity in merit points increased by several times.

“…What did you say? The Purple Chestnut King and the five Great World Kings were all slain by a human called Lin Muk?”

From the spirit race camp, a lion-like old man roared out loud, angrily shouting at a spirit race youth.

The youth trembled as he responded. Death God Lin Muk brought far too great a pressure to him.

“The geniuses I taught were… all killed by Lin Muk? Who is this Lin Muk?”

Many sects listened, startled. They didn’t know who Lin Muk was.

“How arrogant! Thoroughly investigate that person’s status for me, I will make sure he regrets being born!” A Great World King influence’s sect leader shouted out in a rage, his eyes flashing with a cold killing intent.

And at this time, some influences above the Great World King level were having their own suspicions.

“How come the old ancestor hasn’t emerged yet?”

The Yellow River Palace was slowly floating in the sky.

Those who stood above the palace walls were half-step Empyreans or Great World Kings. Their strengths were outstanding. However, each one was covered in dense ghost energy and followed by ghostly phantoms that endlessly howled. It was hard to tell if they were people at all.

These people were from Yellow Springs Palace, a sect created by Empyrean Myriad Ghost.

“Could it be that the old ancestor is still engaged in a massive killing spree within?”

“It shouldn’t be. The reason the old ancestor came here was for an ancient rival of his. He shouldn’t be interested in these juniors, and in any case the Akashic Dream Battlefield will be closing soon. The old ancestor should have come out by now.”

“Maybe that old scumbag Chaos is bothering the old ancestor.” A Yellow Springs Palace disciple guessed.

A number of divided opinions rang out as more and more Yellow Springs Palace disciples chimed in. Slowly, they began to suspect something had happened, and faintly felt an unlucky premonition approach.

“Did Empyrean Myriad Ghost perish? Was he killed by Chaos Demon God?”

A large influence couldn’t help but wonder as they watched this all happen.

“Empyrean Myriad Ghost is the domineering and rampant kind of person. If he won then he should already be swaggering his way out. Now the Akashic Dream Battlefield is closing soon and he still hasn’t appeared, that might mean he was killed by Chaos Demon God.” Someone boldly suggested.

As many people heard this, they felt this was the most reasonable explanation.

As the people from Yellow Springs Palace heard these discussions, they became angry and even more worried.

“Something’s wrong, even Chaos Demon God hasn’t emerged!”

Someone discovered that across from them, Chaos Divine Palace was also floating up and down, the people within keeping their auras restrained. Chaos filled the air around them as they quietly waited for their Empyrean to appear.

Facing the glowering gaze from those of Yellow Springs Palace, the people from Chaos Divine Palace stared back, their eyes just as fierce and filled with a thick slaughter energy.

As the great purple gate was about to close, a vast chaos aura as deep as a sea enveloped everyone present.

“It’s the old ancestor, the old ancestor has come out!” In the camp of Chaos Divine Palace, someone began to cheer out loud.

They saw an old man in jade green robes appear, his entire body covered with chaos energy.

This old man’s pupils emitted a terrifying chaotic light that shot out in all directions.

As he appeared, everyone was alarmed.

“Haha! My Chaos Divine Palace’s old ancestor has emerged!”

“Truly worthy of being our old ancestor, he even slew that old thief from Yellow Springs Palace! My Chaos Divine Palace is truly above all else!”

“That’s right, how could Yellow Springs Palace possibly hope to compete with my Chaos Divine Palace?”

Everyone was watching as Chaos Divine Palace began celebrating. As for those from Yellow Springs Palace, their faces turned as purple as frozen eggplants. All of them were agitated; it was obvious that their previous guesses appeared increasingly true.

Many disciples from Chaos Divine Palace moved forwards to greet Chaos Demon God. But as they approached, they were all sent flying away with a thick air wave summoned by Chaos Demon God.

“Old ancestor!”

A disciple cried out in panic. However, Chaos Demon God didn’t seem to hear this at all, not even bothering to glance in the direction of these disciples. Without even going to Chaos Divine Palace, his face darkened, becoming incredibly dreadful. His figure flashed and he flew off into the distance at an incredible speed.

The people from Chaos Divine Palace looked helplessly on as Chaos Demon God flew far away. All of them were left in a silent daze.

“Where did old ancestor go?”

“Old ancestor seems to be in a bad mood…”

“What do we do now?”

“Hurry up and chase after him!” The people from Chaos Divine Palace were frightened. The higher level disciples began to quickly activate the palace and break through the void, chasing after Chaos Demon God.

Crowds of confused outer court disciples were left floating in the air, all of them dumbfounded. They had absolutely no clue as to what had just happened.

“What’s wrong with that old geezer Chaos Demon God? If he truly won the battle then he shouldn’t be so quiet. Could he have been defeated? If so, then what about our old ancestor?”

The people from Yellow Springs Palace saw Chaos Demon God fly away without a single word. Each of them looked at his vanishing back, their thoughts even more confused.

“What… what did you say!?”

As the many disciples of Yellow Springs Palace were stunned, a loud surprised voice suddenly echoed out.

The cry came from a Great World King Holy Land. And, the one who shouted out loud was this Holy Land’s shaman, who had just said he would make Lin Muk regret being born in this world.

“You… say that again?” The old Great World King had a look of utter disbelief crossing his face.

“Yes… yes… what this disciple said is that Empyrean Myriad Ghost started a battle not long after entering the Akashic Dream Battlefield, but… he was killed by Lin Muk. Lin Muk was also severely wounded, and at that time Chaos Demon God had arrived. But, Chaos Demon God didn’t dare to attack Lin Ming. After that, Chaos Demon God went missing for the rest of the three year timeline and only appeared today…”

Because of the Holy Land shaman’s shout, many people had turned towards him. As they heard what this disciple was saying, all of them were left speechless.

Empyrean Myriad Ghost, an Empyrean level powerhouse, had been slain by Lin Ming. How was this possible!?

As for Chaos Demon God, according to what the disciple had said, he undoubtedly feared Lin Ming, thus he had hidden for all this time and had only appeared today.

An Empyrean had been scared by a human to the point where he didn’t dare make an appearance in the remaining three year timeline. Just how could this happen?

The remaining disciples of Chaos Divine Palace all glared at this disciple, but they had no way of refuting this. Their old ancestor leaving in an angry rage without saying a single word was the best proof of what had happened.

As for the shaman who had threatened Lin Ming, he was at a loss for words.

He knew that his disciple wouldn’t rashly speak about such important matters. Moreover, the many survivors who had come out from the Akashic Dream Battlefield were all nodding with terrified expressions, confirming what had happened!

The shaman remained silent as the people from Yellow Springs Palace came rushing down from the skies. This time, the only person who entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield from their Yellow Springs Palace had been Empyrean Myriad Ghost. Yellow Springs Palace had no other disciples enter, thus they had no idea what the situation was inside.

“What is his cultivation!?”

The people from Yellow Springs Palace asked.

“I’m not sure.” The Great World King influence disciple shook his head. “It shouldn’t be too high, and his skeletal age wasn’t too old either. He is also a human. Besides Empyrean Myriad Ghost, around 90% of the Great World Kings that died in the Akashic Dream Battlefield were probably because of him…”

Chapter 1830 – Guru Kunyuan

As the disciple spoke he gulped at the same time. He knew that after mentioning that this person had a low skeletal age and was also a human, it would cause a great reaction.

And indeed, as soon as he finished speaking, the noisy crowds fell silent.

A human had struck down Empyrean Myriad Ghost but had also killed numerous World Kings. Even Chaos Demon God had been forced to patiently hide away for three years in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Just how could this be!?

The human race had far too many of their inheritances severed and many of their transcendent divine mights and higher grade cultivation methods were controlled by the various large spiritas influences. And on the road of martial artists, understandings of the Heavenly Dao Laws were slowly accumulated generation after generation. A single person had a limited ability, and no matter how talented they were, without inheritances it was impossible to have high achievements.

“He couldn’t have found the ancient ruins left behind by some ancient human supreme elder, right…?”

“That’s possible… but just where did this Lin Muk come from? No one knows anything about him?”

Many disciples who safely came out from the Akashic Dream Battlefield were forcefully interrogated.

However, they all unanimously shook their heads.

At this time, the disciples from Zenith Palace were all terrified.

When Lin Ming was slaughtering his way through the Akashic Dream Battlefield, the young disciples couldn’t help but brag to everyone and anyone about Lin Ming and how Lin Ming was related to Zenith Palace.

Luckily, the Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master, Jaderiver, and the others had discovered this and had promptly put an end to it.

In Jaderiver’s opinion, Lin Muk had shown graciousness to Zenith Palace. But as the matters about Lin Ming grew increasingly large and dangerous, it was best that a small fish like Zenith Palace pretend as if they didn’t know Lin Muk in order to prevent any accidents from occurring.

Otherwise, with Zenith Palace’s background, it wouldn’t strange if they were completely exterminated in a slightly large storm.

“What do we do…” The Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master muttered, a bitter expression crossing his face.

He was afraid that these influences would decide to vent their rage and frustrations on them.

Jaderiver was also at a loss of what to do. Paper couldn’t be used to wrap fire. As these various large influences probed Lin Muk’s background, they would eventually find that it led back to Zenith Palace.

“We can only state the facts. That is that we aren’t truly related to Lin Muk and only encountered him by chance. Don’t mention that we saved Lin Muk. For such a terrifying character, even if we didn’t bump into him he still would have awakened sooner or later…”

“I hope so… they won’t involve us just because we met Lin Muk… right?”

As Jaderiver was speaking to the Vice Palace Master, they heard a resounding beast’s roar spread through the air. Jaderiver looked up to see a giant ancient vicious beast pass over the skies of Emperor City, releasing an endless pressure. It stopped right in the open fields before the Emperor God Wall.

This vicious beast was a roc. Its wings spread for a hundred miles wide and its dread-inducing aura covered everyone like a mountain.

The roc opened its beak, and a thick spiritual energy gushed out.

A tall old man with a square jaw and wide shoulders slowly walked out from within the roc.

Following behind him was a team of elite martial artists with sharp appearances.

The old man’s eyes emitted a brilliant light. This light slowly swept over those present.

“Guru Kunyuan!” Jaderiver said, startled.

Compared to the numerous influences at Emperor City, Guru Kunyuan’s arrival was considered relatively common. But to Zenith Palace and those influences around Zenith Palace, Guru Kunyuan was a top master!

This was because these influences were located at the Cardinal Sky World and were subordinate to Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace.

As for Guru Kunyuan, he was a direct disciple of Empyrean Heavencore and possessed a half-step Empyrean cultivation. It was said that he had a chance of breaking into the Empyrean realm in the next million years. Although this was only a faint hope, it still allowed Guru Kunyuan to be a highly revered figure within the entire Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace.

This person had a short-fused temper and was not known to be friendly at all.

Seeing him, the people of some small influences from Cardinal Sky World ran up to respectfully greet him.

“Greetings, Guru.”

“Zenith Palace salutes Guru Kunyuan.” A crowd of people bowed with reverence.

“What are your harvests this time?” Guru Kunyuan didn’t bother exchanging niceties; he went straight to the point. The reason he came this time was to inspect the harvests of those that entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield. To the small influences that were attached to Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace, this inspection was extremely important.

According to the merit points they earned, these small influences would be able to obtain rewards from Empyrean Heavencore.

“Guru, our sect brought 9000 people to the Akashic Dream Battlefield and we have 820 who survived. Our merit points are 87,000.”

“Guru, our Incense Mountain brought 8000 disciples into the Akashic Dream Battlefield and we have 670 who survived. Our merit points are 56,000…”

After listening to Guru Kunyuan’s words, the Sovereigns of some small influences began speaking out the merit points their sects earned.

As Guru Kunyuan heard this, he pleasantly smiled. It was a bit surprising. These small influences had harvested a number of merit points much better than in the past. Could the overall strength of Cardinal Sky World’s sects have increased?

“Zenith Palace, how come you aren’t speaking?” Guru Kunyuan suddenly saw that the Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master had a strange complexion on his face, as if he were hesitating to speak.

It wasn’t just the Vice Palace Master who had an awkward expression, but even the core disciple Jaderiver seemed a bit terrified.

The other influences had already finished reporting, and now only Zenith Palace was left dawdling. Guru Kunyuan’s eyes were like sharp blades as he looked at the people from Zenith Palace.

“Our Zenith Palace has obtained 186,500 merit points…” The Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master said as everyone looked at him.

After this trip into the Akashic Dream Battlefield, Zenith Palace had just around a thousand people remaining. From the elite squad that Jaderiver was in, 30 people had survived. And these 30 people contributed nearly half of these merit points.

“Mm?” Guru Kunyuan was amazed. He recalled that during the last trip into the Akashic Dream Battlefield, Zenith Palace had only harvested several tens of thousands of merit points. Yet, this time they had obtained around 180,000. They had made considerable progress from the past.

“Not bad. Honorable Master Heavencore will be happy to hear this. When the rewards are handed down, your Zenith Palace will enjoy great benefits.”

Guru Kunyuan said with satisfaction.

As the high level figures of Zenith Palace heard that Empyrean Heavencore would bestow upon them great rewards, they all looked at each other, not sure of what to say.

The Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master ambiguously said, “The truth is that our Zenith Palace obtained far more merit points than this…”

“Oh? Zenith Palace has even more merit points? You should have said so earlier!”

Guru Kunyuan was startled to hear this. The Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master had said that their Zenith Palace had obtained far more merit points, but 180,000 merit points was around the limit for a small influence. Just how many more could they possibly have obtained?

“If Zenith Palace has more than 200,000 merit points, then I shall take responsibility and grant you even more rewards!” Guru Kunyuan promised. He thought that Zenith Palace would be excited upon hearing this, but he didn’t think their complexions would twist and they would seem worried.

“What? Are you suspecting that I don’t have the ability to fulfill my promise?”

Guru Kunyuan coldly said, clearly unhappy!

Chapter 1831 – Rapidly Rising Merit Points

“No… that’s not what I mean… it’s just that the situation is a little special so our merit points might not be as simple as just 200-300 thousand.” The Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master said with a constipated expression, finding it hard to explain. If possible he didn’t want to mention their relationship with Lin Ming, but it seemed things wouldn’t go their way.

“What are you being so wishy-washy about! If it’s more than 200-300 thousand, then could it be 500 thousand or even a million? That’s about the same as a Great World King influence!”

Guru Kunyuan frowned. Some unlucky Great World King influences might not even have a million merit points.

As Guru Kunyuan was unhappy with the Vice Palace Master’s attitude, suddenly, on the Emperor God Wall, Zenith Palace’s merit points began to rise once more.

“Mm?”

Guru Kunyuan was startled. It seemed that what the Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master said was true; Zenith Palace had more merit points to be countered still!

The merit points rapidly grew, breaking past 200 thousand in the blink of an eye.

“Great!”

Guru Kunyuan nodded. His originally disgruntled expression softened.

In the end, all that mattered were results. If Zenith Palace had good results, then Guru Kunyuan was willing to forgive Zenith Palace for any mistakes they made.

In several moments, the merit points rose to 250,000. Moreover, they continued to quickly increase without slowing down, soon breaking past 300 thousand.

Guru Kunyuan looked at those from Zenith Palace and said with a deep sense of satisfaction, “Well done, your results have truly not shamed you. Rest assured, I will follow my previous agreement and reward Zenith Palace well.”

However, before he finished speaking, Zenith Palace’s merit points had risen to 350 thousand.

With this, Guru Kunyuan was a bit surprised.

Around 180 thousand merit points should have been the limit of an ordinary World King influence. He never thought they would also reach 350,000 – that was something worth celebrating.

“Old Lao, you fellows didn’t do badly at all! I didn’t expect you to be hiding something like this! Could you have prepared some secret weapon?”

Guru Kunyuan stroked his beard, the smile on his face becoming ever brighter. When he shouted at the Zenith Palace Vice Palace Master and called him Old Lao, that was an extremely intimate name.

As Guru Kunyuan said, there were indeed some sects that would prepare top secret weapons to bring to the Akashic Dream Battlefield. For instance, Zenith Palace had gone to the Great Desolate Glacier in order to subdue the hornless ice dragon.

As the Vice Palace Master who was called out in such a close manner by Guru Kunyuan, he didn’t seem flattered at all. Rather, his expression appeared a bit bitter.

He knew what was happening. Zenith Palace’s merit points were rising so quickly because Lin Muk must have finally poured the merit points from his token onto the Emperor God Wall.

Following that, Zenith Palace’s merit points would grow, and this speed would become increasingly fast as the growth rate rose exponentially.

“400 thousand! Zenith Palace has truly amazed the world this time!”

Behind Guru Kunyuan, there were some Elders who had followed him here. They were also disciples of Empyrean Heavencore and were all congratulating Zenith Palace together.

“Old Lao, how come you have such an ugly expression? Are you worried that my Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace won’t fulfill the promised rewards? I must say Old Lai, you are being too petty about this. Do you think our dignified Empyrean Heavenly Palace would be so stingy about some rewards? Even if you obtained 500-600 thousand merit points we would still be able to reward you with more than enough.”

However, as this disciple spoke, he slowly fell quiet. This was because Zenith Palace’s merit points already reached 500 thousand.

Seeing this number continue to rise, a look of doubt crossed his face.

“How come it’s still rising? It’s already at 500 thousand.”

“Unbelievable. Zenith Palace has defied the will of the heavens this time. Soon they’ll catch up to some less fortunate Great World King influences.”

“For an ordinary World King influence to surpass a Great World King influence, that is a rare feat!”

“Mm, something like this hasn’t occurred too often since ancient times. Normally this sort of thing would only happen when an astonishing genius is born into an ordinary World King influence.”

As the disciples of Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace were discussing, they were looking over the disciples of Zenith Palace, trying to identify if there was some unrivalled genius amongst their ranks.

“600 thousand… no, it will soon reach 700 thousand!”

Several Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace disciples were left bewildered. 700 thousand… that would soon surpass the spirit race!

The large spirit race clan only had just over 800 thousand merit points. It was said that they didn’t send out too many disciples and many amongst their ranks had been cut down by some ruthless individual. Even so, no one would suggest that their merit points would be lower than those of Zenith Palace!

“Something’s wrong here…”

Guru Kunyuan frowned.

“It is a bit exaggerated, but still something worth celebrating. If there truly is a peerless genius with astonishing combat strength that is also young enough, they would be capable of affecting the balance to such a degree.”

Behind Guru Kunyuan, some Empyrean disciples chuckled as they spoke.

However, these smiles quickly faded. This was because Zenith Palace’s merit points broke past a million.

One million! Wasn’t this just too ridiculous!?

By all common sense, no matter how fierce Zenith Palace was they still shouldn’t be so incredible. If there was some unrivalled genius that appeared at Zenith Palace, then their name should have been heard throughout Cardinal Sky World by now.

“1.5 million, heavens!”

As Zenith Palace’s merit points broke past a million, the rate of increase suddenly sped up. Before it rose by 100 thousands, now it rose by 200 thousands.

This left many disciples in a stunned shock.

“Something’s definitely wrong!”

The Empyrean disciples of the Cardinal Sky World all rose to their feet, their eyes like perfectly round circles as they stared unblinkingly at the Emperor God Wall.

“3 million, isn’t this just defying the heavens?”

People soon discovered that the larger the merit points value, the more terrifying the speed of increase. According to the previous rate, if the speed continued to rise it would soon reach 8 or 9 million.

But at this moment, they realized they were mistaken; the result was far more monstrous than they guessed.

20 million!

Many Empyrean disciples felt their eyeballs nearly pop out of their heads.

And at this time, the other influences also noticed the changes occurring on the Emperor God Wall. The merit points of a small influence were crazily rising!

“What… what’s going on!?”

Everyone looked towards the Emperor God Wall. 20 million! Even for an Empyrean Holy Land that sent out their brightest team of elites and achieved the limit of what they could, it would still be hard to reach this number of merit points!

Then… 30 million… 40 million… 50 million…

Guru Kunyuan’s face had already turned blue. Just how high would these merit points go?

As for his previous promise of granting rewards to Zenith Palace no matter how many merit points they had, that was a nightmare. Zenith Palace already had 50 million merit points. If it rose any more, then wouldn’t the entire Cardinal Sky Heavenly Palace be bankrupted?

“A hundred million! Heavens!”

The chins of many Empyrean disciples nearly fell to the floor.

This situation was beyond all comprehension.

This definitely wasn’t caused by Zenith Palace. There must have been some change within the Akashic Dream Battlefield!

After reaching a hundred million, the merit points began to rise by nearly 20 million at a time.

Seeing the number wildly surge up as if it were trying to knock all other numbers out of the way, many people’s lips twitched, none of them able to speak.

200 million… 300 million… 400 million…

“How is this happening?”

A Great World King sect leader angrily shouted. This number was far too extraordinary!

“It must be that Lin Muk, it has to be him. Besides him, there is no one else.”

“Lin Muk, either he must come from that small sect or he was borrowing their token!”

Many disciples who just emerged from the Akashic Dream Battlefield soon understand what was happening. Although this terrifying merit points value was shocking, it wasn’t out of the realm of disbelief. Rather, they thought it was quite normal.

“How many merit points will he have?”

As everyone began clamoring out loud, Zenith Palace’s merit points soon reached 800 million.

“A billion, it’s definitely going to hit a billion!”

Someone suddenly realized. With a billion points, they could exchange for one of the top tier rewards on the Emperor God Wall!

“That Lin Muk hunted down and slaughtered so many masters all to obtain a top tier reward! Heavens, he actually managed to gather a full billion merit points! Could he be wanting to exchange for the golden page? How horrifying!”

As everyone was shouting out loud, the Zenith Vice Palace Master was startled upon hearing this. Just before they entered the Akashic Dream Battlefield, Lin Ming had asked him about the conditions for exchanging for the golden page. Back then, the Vice Palace Master had been impatient with his questions because he thought it was an impossibility. But now, it seemed that Lin Ming might actually succeed in obtaining it!

If so, then the reason he caused such a tremendous commotion in the Akashic Dream Battlefield and widely publicized his possession of the kirin fruit was all in order to lure countless powerhouses to him so he could kill them!

What a terrifying young man!

And as everyone thought, Lin Ming’s merit points finally stopped at 1.07 billion. This was just enough to exchange for the golden page.

“Where is Lin Muk?”

Someone asked out loud. For a time, everyone’s eyes panned over the crowd.

However, there were too many people standing in front of the Emperor God Wall. With all of these large influences gathered together, it was an extremely messy and chaotic scene. Wasn’t wanting to look for a single person in this sea of people easier said than done?

Moreover, this Lin Muk had most likely hidden his identity, and had probably changed his appearance!

After all, Lin Muk had offended far too many people in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Moreover, with him wanting to do something so attention-grabbing like exchanging for the golden page, it would be impossible for him to show his true appearance to those here.

As everyone was looking for Lin Muk, the entrance to the Akashic Dream Battlefield closed. If one didn’t leave the Akashic Dream Battlefield before the entrance closed again, then all martial artists within would die. Of course, their true bodies wouldn’t die, but their merit points would be erased.

“Lin Muk is among us!”

Someone shouted out in a bass voice. But, no one knew where he was.

This was a ruthless youth who could even kill an Empyrean at the same cultivation level. If he wanted to hide, wasn’t finding him easier said than done?

Moreover, out of the martial artists present, the one with the highest cultivation was only a half-step Empyrean. After Chaos Demon God left, there were no true Empyreans here.

Who could find Lin Ming?

“That human, the small influence he came from is…”

Many people suddenly thought of looking for the small influence that Lin Ming had entered through. They soon found Zenith Palace!

For a time, the Zenith Vice Palace Master and Jaderiver’s complexions turned gray.

What should have come had now come.

Their Zenith Palace had no place to hide.

But luckily for them, they only had a passing relationship with Lin Ming. If they were honest, then they wouldn’t be sucked into this mess.

“No wonder, so that youth who killed Empyrean Myriad Ghost was brought by you…”

Guru Kunyuan said with realization. Only now did he understand the Vice Palace Master’s constipated expression.

Soon, Jaderiver and the Vice Palace Master were taken away to be questioned. As for Guru Kunyuan, he didn’t stop them from being whisked away. After all, there were no consequences to dying in the Akashic Dream Universe, and fighting in Emperor City was forbidden to begin with.

Chapter 1833 – Golden Page

After carving the title of Polar Ice Lin into the Emperor God Wall, Lin Ming felt that his mind had become connected to it. All sorts of thoughts crossed his mind and some things seemed to be within his reach.

“Golden page…”

Lin Ming meditated in his mind. He thrust out a hand and his entire hand sank into the Emperor God Wall. As he pulled it back, a thin golden piece of paper appeared in his grasp.

This was the golden page that was exchanged with a billion merit points!

Lin Ming was excited. He found that this golden page was different from what he had thought.

He originally thought that the golden page would be a heavy piece of gold paper, around the size of a normal tome.

But, he never thought that the golden page in his hand would be as soft as gauze. As he grabbed it, he felt just how large it was. After unfolding it, it was almost three feet long, just like a small kasya worn by a monk.

The golden page was extremely soft, as smooth as silk. When it was placed against the sun, it was nearly transparent.

However, it was extremely heavy. In Lin Ming’s impression, if he held something so heavy in his hands it should hang down due to its own weight and would be difficult to shake. But the truth was that as he held this golden page in his hands, it had an airy feel to it, seeming as if it would flutter in the wind.

“What a mysterious object…”

Lin Ming could feel that this golden page was extraordinary. As he looked at it he could see thick lines of runes engraved into it. Among these runes, two particularly large ancient characters stood out, illuminating the page like two dark golden moons, shining with a sacred light.

These two characters spelled – Holy Scripture!

Holy Scripture, only two words but containing an incomprehensibly domineering momentum. With just these two words as its name, there were no other embellishments. This was enough to prove just how powerful this golden page was.

It contained unsurpassed mysteries and endless true meanings!

“Holy Scripture, is this the so-called Spiritas Holy Scripture?”

Lin Ming could feel that the golden page in his hands was a remnant of the Spiritas Holy Scripture, however its name was not Spiritas Holy Scripture but instead only Holy Scripture. This caused Lin Ming to suspect whether or not the word Spiritas had been added to the front of Holy Scripture afterwards.

In truth, was the creator of the Spiritas Holy Scripture even the first ancestor of all spiritas? This wasn’t necessarily the truth, but only the history that had been created by the spiritas. As for whether or not it was correct, that was another issue altogether.

What Lin Ming could confirm was that the creator of the Holy Scripture was an existence that had arrived at the pinnacle of the soul forging system. In terms of cultivation systems, it was similar to that of the spiritas.

Lin Ming continued to look through the cicada wing-thin golden page. He found that there were far too many tiny runes covering the page, and each rune was incredibly difficult to discern clearly. In fact, if one focused too much, an unknown force would pierce into one’s spiritual sea, causing a stabbing pain to the eyes and soul.

Was this a remnant spirit mark left behind in the Holy Scripture, or perhaps even a bit of soul force?

Lin Ming was amazed. This golden page was far too strange. Even with his current strength he found it incredibly difficult to read. Just looking at a single rune made him feel as if he would overdraw his soul force.

At this time, a flow of information passed into Lin Ming’s mind. His thoughts stirred as he perked up to attention.

This information was vague, but it gave Lin Ming an approximate feeling. Although he had exchanged for the golden page, the truth was that he had only been able to ‘borrow’ it. As for the borrowing duration, that was actually Lin Ming’s lifespan.

As long as Lin Ming was alive, this golden page would be lent to him. But if he died, the golden page would be reabsorbed into the Emperor God Wall.

“This is…”

As this information passed into Lin Ming’s mind, all sorts of thoughts raced through him. There were likely many of these golden pages, but because of the restrictions of the Laws, no matter how much time passed it would be impossible to exchange for all the golden pages of the Emperor God Wall.

If so, then the so-called original Spiritas Holy Scripture might not be the original copy after all.

Instead, it was a replica slowly formed over the billions of years of history of the spiritas, with people exchanging for golden pages throughout time and making copies of them.

But this replica was incomparably far from the true authentic work. One could even say that they couldn’t be compared at all.

That meant that even someone who possessed the Spiritas Holy Scripture would covet the golden page in his hands.

As these thoughts passed through Lin Ming’s mind, he sucked in a deep breath. It was impossible for him to hide the news that he had exchanged a billion merit points for the golden page. Now, he would become the focus of the public.

Luckily, this was the Akashic Dream universe. If Lin Ming were in the real world, things would undoubtedly become far more dangerous for him.

“I can’t read this here – I have to leave first.”

Lin Ming didn’t need to turn around to realize that there was a massive commotion occurring behind him. As he floated in front of the Emperor God Wall, an innumerable number of people had gathered behind him, all of them wanting to shred him to pieces and steal away his golden page.

Unfortunately for them, the Emperor God Wall’s terrifying pressure meant that these people couldn’t even cast their divine sense towards him.

Even so, they had already transmitted this news through various means.

Currently, it had only been half an hour since everyone had emerged from the Akashic Dream Battlefield, and powerhouses had yet to catch up. But as time passed, more and more masters would arrive here.

In the incomparably massive Akashic Dream Universe, there were undoubtedly many Empyreans and possibly even True Divinities.

Lin Ming didn’t want to wait at the Emperor God Wall until an Empyrean arrived. By that time, he wouldn’t be able to leave at all.

After putting away the golden page, Lin Ming shot into the sky, instantly soaring up hundreds of thousands of feet. Then, like a sparrow, he flew directly over the mountain-like Emperor God Wall and vanished over the other side.

“He ran away!”

“He’s crossed the divine mountain! We can’t chase after him!”

In Emperor City, three of the city walls were over a thousand miles long. However, on the north side where the divine mountain was located, that mountain range stretched for countless tens of thousands of miles, acting as a natural moat that no one could cross unless they had the qualifications to approach and carve their name.

As many people looked at Lin Ming, flames nearly spewed out from their eyes. They had been forced to watch on as Lin Ming left his name right next to Sheng Mei’s on the Emperor God Wall, took his reward, and then pompously flew away.

“I hate him!”

Old Green roared out, stamping his feet on the ground. He beat his fists against his chest, so angry that his liver and gallbladder hurt. Ignoring the secret that Lin Ming had on his body, just the value of that golden page was incomprehensible!

Yet, no one in their sect was capable of obtaining it. Even asking for a tenth of the required merit points was completely impossible.

“That is the treasure of us spiritas, yet it was taken by a human!”

“Debased human, he’s stolen away what belongs to us! The most sacred treasure of my soul race! How could it have fallen into the hands of a human!?”

“We must kill him and take it back!”

At this time, the animosity between the spiritas and Lin Ming had extended far past the Great World Kings and Empyrean that he had killed in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. Now, he had touched upon the reverse scale of many large spiritas influences and had even taken away a treasure that True Divinities would be jealous of!

As these various great influences spread this news, Lin Ming had already crossed the Emperor God Wall and flown into the vast depths of the Akashic Dream Universe.

His flight speed was extremely fast. As he flew, his body emitted crackling sounds as his form changed. He shrank, becoming shorter and thinner, and his looks became increasingly ordinary. His eye sockets deepened. If he were thrown into a crowd of mortals, it would be impossible to notice him.

Lin Ming’s application of the Bodily Rebirth Technique had reached an extremely high boundary. In addition to his deep cultivation and strength, even an Empyrean might not be able to see through his camouflage.

But if Lin Ming were to meet a True Divinity, he didn’t have any confidence that he would be able to fool them. However, what sort of character was a True Divinity? In the seven Heavens that comprised the Soul World, there were likely not more than a handful of True Divinities, so Lin Ming didn’t worry about them at all.

Lin Ming thought about it. He folded up the golden page and placed it near his chest, against his heart. His body became a series of afterimages as he vanished into the horizon.

Although the war in the Akashic Dream Battlefield had ended, Lin Ming didn’t plan on leaving the Akashic Dream Universe just yet. He had come here to adventure and also to find Sheng Mei.

In the seven universes of the Soul World, Lin Ming didn’t even know which one Sheng Mei was residing in. For him to find Sheng Mei like this was far, far too difficult.

Thus, the best way to do so would be to cause a massive disturbance in the Akashic Dream Universe and force Sheng Mei to seek him out on her own initiative.

Lin Ming already anticipated that the matter of him leaving behind his name on the Emperor God Wall and right next to Sheng Mei’s would soon enter into the universes of the spiritas, and subsequently pass into her ears.

This was the reason Lin Ming deliberately left behind such a title next to Sheng Mei’s name.

Chapter 1834 – Seventh Revolution Sheng Mei

The main universe of the Soul World was also the largest universe of the Soul World’s seven Heavens. This universe had 4800 great worlds and their martial arts civilization had been inherited continuously for over 8 billion years.

The so-called inheritance that continued for over 8 billion years meant that for the last 8 billion years, there had been no great calamities that ruined them. Rather, they only developed to higher heights without ever being destroyed.

This allowed this universe’s martial arts civilization to reach an inconceivable degree of glory.

And the background of the spiritas’ main universe had reached depths so great that it was almost impossible to imagine!

From 5 billion years ago, after the spiritas’ main universe had existed for over 3 billion years, True Divinities began to appear amongst the ranks of the spiritas martial artists. The birth of a True Divinity required not only the accumulation of inheritances but also a deep background and the support of a great destiny.

For a shallow universe like the Divine Realm, it was hard for enough threads of destiny to gather together to nurture the ascendance of a True Divinity.

Generation upon generation of True Divinities would also leave behind their own inheritances that accumulated over time. These were the enlightenments of existences that stood above Empyreans. It was a mind-boggling level of wealth.

The spiritas possessed more than seven universes, and over half of the entire soul race’s strength was concentrated in their main universe. In this universe, the most bustling first-order world was also the hub world of the spiritas. Here, ordinary World Kings had only average statuses. Here, Empyreans numbered in the double digits and above Empyreans there was even a True Divinity.

This True Divinity was none other than the Soul Emperor, the ruler of the Soul World’s seven Heavens. He was the highest existence amongst the spiritas.

The Holy Land he established was called the Soul Rapture Holy Lands. Without a doubt, it was the largest influence of the spiritas!

The Soul Rapture Holy Lands occupied over half the land of the great world’s central continent. There were broad smelting trials and innumerable mystic realms. The training conditions here were so rich that geniuses of other influences could only hope to live here.

At this time, within the Soul Rapture Holy Lands, in a small world filled with the atmosphere of spring –

This small world was warm and pure.

The morning sunlight sprinkled down, scattering upon the floor like golden yarn. All sorts of spirit grasses and flowers grew, and spiritual dew condensed on these plants. A single drop of this dew, if it fell into the outside world, would be considered the water of a divine spring and stir up a storm of blood and chaos.

But here, this was only the most common of flower dew. It would gather every morning and then evaporate as the sun rose.

In this immortal fairyland, there was an ordinary table, and in front of this table was a chair carved from white jade, not seeming special at all. A pair of pale feet casually stepped atop the green grass in front of this chair, the toes like pearl drops.

These were the feet of a magnificent woman. She wore purple clothes and her legs were straight. Her curves and her face were perfectly molded, like the most exquisite forms of art.

A blue bird fluttered on her shoulder. This bird was gorgeous and its feathers were dazzling. Its eyes were like twin sapphires.

At this time, the woman was completely entranced. As the sunlight fell upon her pitch black hair that fell like an inky waterfall, it reflected a purple gold gloss.

In her hands and lying on the table was a thin piece of golden paper, nearly invisible in the sun.

Countless tiny runes were written atop this golden paper. She carefully read through the mysterious principles of these runes. Sometimes, her nose would wrinkle and her eyelashes would move, and she would even sway about, leaving behind faint shadows that were beautiful to behold.

If Lin Ming were here he would naturally recognize what this was. The golden paper that this woman was looking at was one of the golden pages from the Holy Scripture.

As for this woman, she was Soul Empress Sheng Mei.

The bird on her shoulder was her contract beast – The Deep Blue Ice Phoenix.

After many years, the Sheng Mei of today was different from before. She gave off a feeling as if she had broken free from her cocoon and had been reborn. Her temperament became increasingly perfect, like she was an immortal from the highest heavens, making all mortals beneath her feel naught but inferiority.

This was because…

Sheng Mei had finally completed the seventh revolution of her Grand Reincarnation Art. Like a phoenix through nirvana, she had obtained a new life!

And all of this was also partly thanks to Lin Ming.

Because of Lin Ming’s help, Sheng Mei had obtained an even greater lucky chance from the Asura Road’s final trial. With this lucky chance, she had been able to use it to complete the seventh revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art.

Currently, Sheng Mei was deeply perceiving the Spiritas Holy Scripture, in preparation for attacking that mythical eighth revolution.

She had a faint premonition that the eighth revolution would be incomparably hard. It would cost her a massive amount of time and require an incomprehensible amount of energy and effort to complete.

And the most mysterious ninth revolution that only existed in legends, even Sheng Mei didn’t have the slightest bit of confidence in completing it.

This was because the spiritas’ Soul Emperor was also stuck at this step, unable to cross it.

Although the Soul Emperor hadn’t succeeded, Sheng Mei still wanted to try attacking the ninth revolution. In her road of martial arts, she desired to stand at the peak of all martial arts and see what the scenery there was like.

Just as she was about to put away the golden page and set out, at this time, not too far away, there was a light tinkling sound in the spirit springs not too far from her.

A beautiful rainbow fish leapt up from the springs, jumping in front of Sheng Mei. It put out a token and then swished around before splashing back into the spirit springs.

“Mm?” Sheng Mei’s eyebrows pressed together. She picked up the token. “What happened?”

During her seclusion, no one was allowed to disturb her. To be delivered a token now likely meant it was some serious matter.

She swept her sense through the token and thoroughly investigated the contents. A surprised look flashed through her eyes.

“Polar Ice Lin, that is the title someone carved on the Emperor God Wall, right next to my name. Moreover, he has a golden page and he is even a human…”

In the entire 33 Heavens, there was only a handful of people that would be able to carve their names into the Emperor God Wall. In addition, this person was surnamed Lin and was also a human. With all these factors added together, Sheng Mei suddenly recalled someone.

And that name Polar Ice Lin. This Polar Ice… it was likely that…

Sheng Mei unconsciously thought back to the final trial’s Undying Polar Ice. Polar Ice Lin – could it be Lin Ming?

Otherwise, it was impossible to explain such coincidences in the world.

A human had chosen to carve the name Polar Ice Lin right next to her own. It was extremely likely that Lin Ming wanted to tell her something – that he had come to the Soul World.

“Lin Ming…”

Sheng Mei stood up, a thoughtful look on her face. “He wants to see me?”

Towards Lin Ming, Sheng Mei couldn’t quite describe just what she felt. They could be considered enemies as well as friends. But what a pity – he was not a spiritas.

“The golden page in his hands should be the second wood page. For this page, I should see him at least once.”

Like this, Sheng Mei flew out from the small world.

……………

At this time, in a remote mountain deep within the Akashic Dream Universe, Lin Ming had opened up his own cave dwelling and was quietly reading through the golden page.

Scanning this golden page placed an enormous burden on his eyes, often making his eyes and mind hurt. It was like countless needles poking at his thoughts. He couldn’t help but put the golden page down periodically and take a rest before starting reading again.

Reading this golden page required a strong soul force. With Lin Ming’s current strength, he was just barely able to do it.

However, Lin Ming discovered that even though there was a piercing pain to his spiritual sea as he read through the page, as he read through it day after day, he also noticed that his soul seemed to be constantly tempered throughout.

The direct manifestation of this was that he could read the golden page for longer and longer periods of time with each attempt.

The more Lin Ming read, the more he discovered that the writer of the Holy Scripture was also an era-shaking peerless character.

But, it was unknown just why he had engaged in a life or death struggle with the Asura Road Master.

Like this, Lin Ming used an entire month to read through the golden page.

He also finally knew just what was recorded within the Holy Scripture.

The Asura Heavenly Dao could be called, in a way, a comprehensive summary of the Laws of the 33 Heavens, a way of standing on par with the Great Dao of the universe.

And, this Holy Scripture was the exploration of a martial artist, the excavation of their complete life potential.

“Law of Reincarnation…”

“Art of Eternal Life…”

Lin Ming was amazed.

The Law of Reincarnation was the Grand Reincarnation Art that Sheng Mei cultivated; it was one of the most essential parts of the Holy Scripture. However, besides the Law of Reincarnation, there was an even more terrifying arcane technique within the Holy Scripture, something that could truly be described as defying the will of the heavens.

Its name was – the Art of Eternal Life.

Eternal Life. That sounded like an unbelievable concept. If a martial artist could achieve immortality then as long as they lived, their strength would constantly increase. If they could live for 10 billion years, just how strong would they become? What level would they reach? It was impossible to imagine!

A mystic stone, after experiencing the infinite washing of time, could eventually become an Essence Spirit Embryo Stone. So, if a pig were to experience the infinite tempering of years, even it could eventually accumulate the good fortune of the world and obtain enlightenment, becoming a monster, and then a monster emperor, and sooner or later rule a world.

The Art of Eternal Life complemented the Law of Reincarnation. But, in order to cultivate the Art of Eternal Life, one needed an Eternal Soul. And this sort of mythical soul had already vanished for billions and billions of years.

As for the Art of Eternal Life, it became nothing but a story…

“Eternal Soul…”

Lin Ming’s thoughts chilled. He certainly remembered that in one of his encounters with Sheng Mei in the past, Sheng Mei had said that his soul was similar to the Eternal Soul.

In the past, Lin Ming believed that this was because of the Magic Cube. The existence of the Magic Cube had caused some sort of fundamental mutation to Lin Ming’s soul.

Lin Ming couldn’t help but think – was his soul the Eternal Soul?

“With my soul, can I succeed in cultivating the Art of Eternal Life?”

According to the records of the Holy Scripture, it was nearly impossible to cultivate the Art of Eternal Life. In fact, it wasn’t a perfect cultivation method. Even the creator of this cultivation method, the author of the Holy Scripture, had only completed a part of this Art of Eternal Life in the past.

Even the one who wrote the Holy Scripture hadn’t been able to eventually obtain eternal life.

Eternal life – it was a curse upon the Heavenly Dao, something that the Heavenly Dao would never allow.

Even universes would eventually perish, much less life.

“I wonder if I can see the boundary of eternal life after surpassing a True Divinity…”

Lin Ming inexplicably thought. He had no idea whether the Asura Road Master was alive or dead.

“This Holy Scripture is a peerless treasure. Unfortunately, I only have a single page. If I can obtain other pages, then my understandings towards life will reach new heights. If I can cultivate the Grand Reincarnation Art, then let alone the seventh, eighth, or ninth revolution, as long as I can complete six revolutions my strength will greatly increase!”

As Lin Ming thought of this, he became increasingly excited. It had to be known that a good portion of Sheng Mei’s strength was due to the Grand Reincarnation Art!

The Asura Sutra and Holy Scripture were both peerless cultivation methods that spoke of the true meaning of the Great Dao. One explored the limits of the universe and the other explored the limits of a martial artist. If both could be gathered together, just what would that be like?

Chapter 1837 – Jade Lifestone

“There are many elites here…”

Lin Ming stood on the cliff, sweeping his divine sense around him. He discovered that there were many peak Empyrean descendant level geniuses.

Whether it was in size or number of masters, the Soul World far outstripped the Divine Realm. Thus, they also naturally had numerous times more peerless geniuses than humanity did.

With so many elites gathered together, this was a truly grand scene!

There were even people that stayed here for a dozen years or dozens of years. There were even people who casually stopped by to cultivate at the Fallen God Mountain Range.

However, cultivating at the Fallen God Mountain Range wasn’t necessarily the wisest choice. This was because the Laws here were extremely volatile, and without an absurdly high level of perception it was impossible to make sense of these Laws.

“The spiritas are really formidable. They are likely even stronger than the saints…”

Lin Ming couldn’t help but acknowledge that the disparity in strength between humanity and the spiritas was greater than he had imagined.

Lin Ming firmly believed that the reason the spiritas were able to develop to such a scale was linked to the existence of the Akashic Dream Universe. This was a land of unimaginable wealth, inheritances, and other such buried treasures. The Divine Realm simply had nothing they could compare with this.

But for some reason, the saints were reluctantly able to compare with the spiritas. So, what advantage did the saints possess?

To Lin Ming, great strength didn’t come without reason, and decline didn’t come without reason either.

The saints had stood tall for such a long time and still remained as glorious as they were; there had to be a reason for this.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

From beneath the cliff, in the pitch black abyss, people constantly flew out.

Those that flew out all had despondent expressions and seemed extremely tired.

They had servants waiting for them atop the cliff, all of them running forwards to greet their masters.

“That is the Vice Hall Master of Blood Dragon Hall. In the past, he was one of the proudest sons of heaven of the Daydream Skyworld. His skeletal age is just over 1200 years. I wonder if he managed to grasp any enlightenments beneath the Phantom God Spirit Cliff!”

Someone said as they discovered this top character.

Although there was a skeletal age restriction of 3000 years here, in practice, it was mostly those that were around a thousand years old who came here to attempt attaining enlightenment. The 2000-3000 year old peerless geniuses had already come to the shrine platforms numerous times in the past and didn’t want to waste any more time here. After all, the Fallen God Mountain Range had a very poor cultivation environment.

“Mm? Isn’t that Golden Sun Temple’s Young Master Wanyan? He is also one of the greatest geniuses of his generation at Golden Sun Temple. There are far too many amazing elites here today!”

Someone cried out in praise. Even though there were outstanding people all over Fallen God Mountain Range, people with Young Master Wanyan’s talent were still rare.

“White Bloodjade, he is also a proud son of heaven.”

Another person said in hushed whispers. The crowds of people began discussing these extreme talents that had flown up from the shrine platforms.

Still, so many peerless characters had failed one after another. Even so, there wasn’t any shame or surprise, nor were there any regrets – this was because failure was the norm!

In fact, no matter how great one’s reputation was or how over-exaggerated and blown out of proportion one’s talent was, no one believed that one could truly gain enlightenment on the shrine platforms.

It was simply impossible!

Even Soul Empress Sheng Mei had been forced to give up. If others could succeed where she failed, wouldn’t that be a joke?

Who was Soul Empress Sheng Mei? Without any refutations, she was known as the number one junior amongst the spiritas. Whether it was in strength, foundation, comprehension of Laws, cultivation method inheritances, or anything else, no one was able to compare with her.

“Even Soul Empress Sheng Mei failed. I suspect that there really is nothing here. Maybe whatever is here has already vanished because far too long a time has passed…”

Someone muttered with suspicion thick in his voice. In fact, many people already had this idea circling in their minds.

“In the past, how long did the Soul Empress stay here for enlightenment?”

As everyone was speaking, a large fellow with a dragon beard walked over and asked out loud with a booming voice. This large fellow was Lin Ming. Because he used the Bodily Rebirth Technique to create an illusion of a spiritas martial artist’s spiritual sea, no one was able to sense he was a human.

Many people rolled their eyes at Lin Ming. For outstanding elites, when their cultivation speed reached the extreme and far surpassed their speed in their old age, then even being 2000 years old seemed young.

As for Lin Ming… he simply really wasn’t worth a second glance. If he were in the mortal world, most people would think he was some conman selling pork on the street.

This sort of person also came to the Fallen God Mountain Range to join in on the fun?

“I must say old uncle, you shouldn’t come to this place to play around. This Fallen God Mountain Range is already crowded as it is.”

No one was able to see Lin Ming’s skeletal age; the effects of the Bodily Rebirth Technique were far too realistic.

“I’m just casually looking around. I wonder how long the Soul Empress spent trying to gain enlightenment here in the past?” Lin Ming asked once more. This was a crucial point for him.

If Sheng Mei spent a short period of time here then Lin Ming had some hopes of succeeding. But if Sheng Mei spent eight years or 10 years here without any results at all, then things became a great deal more troublesome. He didn’t have that much time to waste here.

Many people weren’t sure why Lin Ming asked the question he did. But at this time, a white-robed youth said, “108 days! Not one hour more or one hour less. During these 108 days, the Soul Empress tried to gain enlightenment 72 times and managed to light up the third soul sea!”

The white-robed youth accurately listed these numbers. As for what lighting up the third soul sea meant, Lin Ming had no idea.

At the eight-sided pagoda, he only asked for information about the golden pages, and didn’t ask about the special circumstances related to the Fallen God Mountain Range.

Lin Ming looked at this white-robed youth. This youth had a handsome appearance and a dashing aura. From a single glance, one could see that he came from an amazing background and had considerable achievements.

“A character whose talent surpasses White King…” Lin Ming secretly noticed. Empyrean Vast Universe’s direct disciple was White King. Although this wasn’t considered much to Lin Ming, not everyone was able to surpass White King in terms of talent.

“Soul Empress Sheng Mei is so fierce!” Someone cried out in praise. “108 days to light up three soul seas! Some people can’t even light up two soul seas in 10 years! I wonder why Soul Empress Sheng Mei didn’t continue meditating; perhaps she might have grasped more of the principles.”

Many people asked out loud. They also didn’t know the particulars about Sheng Mei’s attempt.

“The Empress said that three soul seas is only the start; it becomes far more difficult afterwards. But even the Empress didn’t have confidence she could succeed. Moreover, her time is precious and there were many other matters she had to attend to…”

The white-robed youth who spoke seemed to be extremely knowledgeable about Sheng Mei. The others couldn’t help but ask him, “How come you know the details so clearly? It sounds like you personally heard of it in the past.”

The white-robed youth proudly said, “Of course I know what I’m talking about. I’m from the Soul Rapture Holy Lands, so why wouldn’t I know? I have even seen the Soul Empress in person before!”

As the white-robed youth spoke, his words were like stone splashing into a calm lake. For a time, everyone looked at him, some of them with dazed expressions.

This white-robed youth came from the Soul Rapture Holy Lands, the same Holy Land as Sheng Mei! Moreover, he had even seen Sheng Mei with his own eyes!

“I remember him, he is a core disciple of the Soul Rapture Holy Lands, Jade Lifestone!”

Someone said, recalling the white-robed youth’s identity. Then, many people cast envious gazes at this white-robed youth. He actually came from the same Holy Land as Sheng Mei! For a heroic young elite like him, his future achievements would be limitless.

“Senior-apprentice Brother Jade, how did you see the Soul Empress?”

“Senior-apprentice Brother Jade, have you seen the Soul Empress fight before? What is it like?”

Many people asked Jade Lifestone in droves, some of them extremely zealous. To the spiritas, Sheng Mei was akin to a living goddess.

Many of the spiritas worshipped Sheng Mei. This was a deep reverence that came from the heart. Although many of these young outstanding elites admired Sheng Mei to the extreme, none of them had any impure thoughts towards her. This was because Sheng Mei was far too holy and perfect, to the point where no one dared to profane her image.

Jade Lifestone was also one of Sheng Mei’s adoring fans. With a slightly haughty tone, he began to narrate how he saw Sheng Mei.

As Lin Ming saw Jade Lifestone speak with such fervent enthusiasm he was left speechless. After a while he asked, “Where is the Soul Empress now?”

He wanted to see Sheng Mei. Having a general idea of where she was would be a good start.

Jade Lifestone frowned upon being interrupted. He looked towards the person asking the question and discovered it was that large and plodding dragon-bearded fellow.

To someone who was born handsome like Jade Lifestone and who was also picky about others’ appearances, he naturally didn’t have a favorable impression towards Lin Ming who currently looked like a perverted uncle who slaughtered pigs for a living.

In addition, Lin Ming interrupting his words had brought Jade Lifestone’s impression of him even lower. Even if they were both fans of Sheng Mei, Jade Lifestone still disliked Lin Ming.

“Why do you care where the Empress is? Are you thinking of going to see her?”

Lin Ming traced his beard, hiding a smile. He chuckled and said, “I’m just a little curious about where the Soul Empress would be. This little brother, you wouldn’t happen to know, right?”

“Humph, of course I know, there’s no point in you trying to rile me up. I’ll tell you that the Soul Empress is currently deep in seclusion within the Soul Rapture Holy Lands as she completes the seventh revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art. Moreover, she will finish soon; this isn’t a secret at all. However, there is no need for you to care about where she is, as it’s useless whether you know or not.”

Lin Ming was startled to hear this. Soul Empress Sheng Mei was completing the seventh revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art. If so, then her strength would rise yet again!

Just what boundary would she have reached?

Lin Ming counted the cards that he could bring out in front of Sheng Mei. He had to admit that even though he was looking for Sheng Mei to negotiate with her, he was in far too disadvantageous a position.

This disadvantage originated from the decline of humanity. It was hard for a single man to change this.

“If the Soul Empress left seclusion would she come to the Akashic Dream Universe?”

Lin Ming asked once more. Jade Lifestone slowly said, “The Soul Empress can naturally come to the Akashic Dream Universe if she wants, because this is a trial land for the spiritas! However, don’t go around thinking you can see her here. Wherever the Soul Empress goes, let alone you, not even I can follow her!”

Lin Ming didn’t bother with Jade Lifestone’s attitude. He asked again, “And about lighting those three soul seas that this good brother just mentioned, what is that exactly?”

Lin Ming’s last question not only caused Jade Lifestone to frown, but everyone else also rolled their eyes once more.

This person asked so many useless questions.

Jade Lifestone carelessly said, “Although we all came to the Fallen God Mountain Range to test our luck or experience it for ourselves, the least you could do is try and learn some of the most basic knowledge before coming here. The shrine platforms have soul sea marks carved into them. The more enlightenment you can grasp, the more soul sea marks light up. If you can light them all up then that is the sign that you have successfully gained enlightenment. However, these are only legends. Only in ancient times were there people able to succeed.”

Chapter 1838 – Enlightenment on the Shrine Platform

Through a simple conversation with Jade Lifestone, Lin Ming had a much higher understanding of what this ‘enlightenment’ was.

Even though Jade Lifestone and the other martial artists didn’t like Lin Ming too much, they didn’t look down on him. Although Lin Ming didn’t look like an elite of any kind and he clearly came to take a look for the fun – weren’t they the same? There wasn’t a point to people who all never reached the finishing line laughing at each other.

Almost all those at the Fallen God Mountain Range had come to experience what attempting enlightenment on the shrine platforms was like. Very few of them had true confidence in themselves that they would succeed.

Of course, even those that were confident in themselves only had disappointment as their harvests.

Seeing Lin Ming fly towards the shrine platforms beneath the cliff, these people only teased him several times before no longer bothering with him.

Every year, countless individuals came to the Fallen God Mountain Range.

Perhaps they were ordinary martial artists and perhaps they were peerless geniuses. But in the end, all of them were only temporary travelers who never accomplished anything.

Lin Ming stepped on the wind. A light mountain breeze wafted up from the abyss, mixed with a refreshing light mist.

In the sea of spirit fog, countless shrine platforms stood tall.

These shrine platforms all seemed forged from jade. They were square-shaped with sharp corners and edges.

The shrine platforms were only three feet long and wide, but they stood tens of thousands of feet high. They were cut into the cliff and marked with strange runes. From afar, it seemed as if they were rooted into the depths of the earth, like tall and slender totem poles that were thrust into the ground.

Lin Ming soon saw the soul sea marks atop the shrine platforms. They were pieces of clouds carved atop the cliff; beautiful and exquisite.

Some of these clouds had already lit up, symbolizing the results of some martial artists that were sitting in meditation on the shrine platforms.

Although there were many shrine platforms, there were even more martial artists. Every shrine platform was already occupied.

Lin Ming patiently waited, but he didn’t plan on blithely waiting for a random person. He swept out his divine sense and searched for someone whose aura was a little chaotic.

These types of people mostly didn’t possess much patience. Hopefully they would leave soon.

Lin Ming noticed a purple-clothed woman with a pair of small horns rising from her forehead. It was unknown what race she was from but her cultivation was only at the Soul Transformation realm; she was a true junior. She was likely not much older than Frost Dream when she had participated in the Divine Realm First Martial Meeting.

She was clearly overdrawing her soul force trying to grasp the principles atop the shrine platform and was suddenly pushed away.

Lin Ming’s eyes and feet were fast. His figure flickered and he immediately occupied the shrine platform that the purple-clothed girl fell off from. Because he had a large figure, this small shrine platform was suddenly mostly taken up by him.

This sudden movement caused many of the waiting martial artists to roll their eyes.

“You…”

The purple-clothed girl looked at Lin Ming. She saw an overly tall and large dragon-bearded fellow suddenly rush onto the seat that was still warm from her body heat, and she flushed red with anger.

“What about it?” Lin Ming traced his thick beard.

The purple-clothed little girl couldn’t find the words to speak. She could only give up on the shrine platform and fly up from the cliff in a huffy rage.

Like this, Lin Ming started attempting to grasp the principles. In order to do that, he needed perception as well as luck. Even though so many years had passed, no one had succeeded. Some people even suspected that the Dao here had changed without them knowing it.

Lin Ming was also curious about what ‘enlightenment’ here really meant.

Lin Ming opened the Eight Inner Hidden Gates’ Gate of Opening. The Gate of Opening enhanced one’s perception. Moreover, Lin Ming’s Gate of Opening was not normal. He had perfectly opened the Gate of Opening, and this had provided Lin Ming with a terrifying enhancement to his perception.

When this was combined with Lin Ming’s understanding of the Asura Sutra and its countless and complex Asura runes, as well as his studying of the divine runic arts, his comprehension ability had reached a mind-boggling level.

At the same time, Lin Ming entered a perfect ethereal state. He focused his heart and released his mind. Three fused martial intents appeared, and behind Lin Ming a Bodhi tree appeared, its sparse branches with their lush, jade-green leaves stretched out.

In this immortal land of ultimate bliss, Lin Ming’s focus was as steady as an ancient lake that had never been disturbed.

With all these conditions joining with each other, Lin Ming began to perceive the Laws of the shrine platform.

The runes marked atop the pillars of the shrine platforms began to flow into Lin Ming’s spiritual sea. Here, Lin Ming was like a little lonely boat, quietly drifting through a sea of Laws.

“The Laws of the shrine platform are similar in some ways to the Holy Scripture, but they are also completely different…”

Lin Ming’s eyesight was extraordinary. He was someone who had seen the Holy Scripture and Asura Sutra, and he could tell that the Laws of Fallen God Mountain Range’s shrine platforms were inherited from the Holy Scripture.

In fact, even the aura here seemed to echo with the golden page he had on him, their true meanings superimposing upon each other.

In order to prevent any accidents from occurring, Lin Ming had placed the golden page into his inner world. As he touched his divine sense upon the page, a strange cord of resonance seemed to form.

Like this, Lin Ming sat in meditation for a day. He discovered that even though cultivating wasn’t good at the Fallen God Mountain Range, it was actually highly beneficial for him if he were only trying to perceive the mysteries of the golden page.

Slowly, Lin Ming gained an increasingly profound understanding of the second wood page. Three days later, Lin Ming could sense something extra in his spiritual sea. Because of this, there was a change to his spiritual sea, and with a light cracking sound, one of the carved clouds on Lin Ming’s shrine platform lit up with a sparkling light.

This was the soul sea mark of the shrine platform.

Now, it had been lit up by Lin Ming.

“Mm… someone made progress. It’s so bright too, you rarely see that!”

At the Fallen God Mountain Range, countless people came to grasp the principles every year, so lighting up a soul sea mark wasn’t much at all. But for a soul sea mark to emit such a blinding light after lighting up, that was actually extremely rare.

The brighter the light was, the more a martial artist had grasped the principles. This also meant their potential was greater.

At this time, even though Lin Ming had only lit up the first soul sea mark, it was still more radiant than those people who had lit up three or four soul sea marks already.

“Who is so fierce…?”

Many people looked at Lin Ming’s shrine platform. As they realized who he was, a strange complexion came over their faces.

“It’s actually him…”

Jade Lifestone from the Soul Rapture Holy Lands had been attempting enlightenment on a shrine platform too. As he saw Lin Ming and his performance, his face twisted as if he had eaten a fly.

If it were anyone else he wouldn’t find it strange, but… why was it him?

This person clearly didn’t seem extraordinary at all, nor was he young, so how could this person have such a high degree of perception? This was just a joke!

Jade Lifestone looked at Lin Ming’s shrine platform which was nearly completely covered by Lin Ming’s large butt. He looked at the strongly shining soul sea mark and contrasted it to his own three dimly shimmering soul sea marks. At that time, Jade Lifestone felt as if 10,000 crows were flying above his head.

“How is this possible? This fellow looks like he should be selling pork on the side of the street so how is he better than me? Before this, he even asked me what it meant to light up three soul sea marks and it seemed as if it were his first time coming to the Fallen God Mountain Range. Was that all an act?”

Jade Lifestone felt sick to his stomach. He didn’t believe this was Lin Ming’s first time at the Fallen God Mountain Range.

He quickly stabilized his mind and returned to trying to grasp the principles. After being surpassed by this uncle-like Lin Ming, he was in a bad mood.

“Miss…”

“I see it…”

The purple-clothed girl with two little horns jutting out from her forehead was watching Lin Ming, her mouth slightly fallen open, a bit unwilling to admit defeat. The shrine platform that Lin Ming was sitting on had been hers, and when Lin Ming sat on it, it suddenly dazzled with a blinding light. But when she had tried, there had only been a dim glow.

“Could it be that perception is inversely related to one’s good looks? He is so old and hideous yet his comprehensions are so deep, and I am so cute yet… ugh…” The purple-clothed girl turned red with shame and no longer thought about it. After resting for three days her soul force had recovered and she could attempt the shrine platform again.

When Lin Ming lit up the first soul sea mark he created a small commotion, but the disturbance quickly died down. Although Lin Ming’s comprehension ability was rare, it wasn’t too uncommon. Through the many years there were lots of people with achievements similar to Lin Ming’s, but in the end they had all fallen short.

The shrine platforms of the Fallen God Mountain Range weren’t simple at all.

Many people recognized it as a matter of fact that Lin Ming had come to the Fallen God Mountain Range before. Otherwise, to light up the first soul sea mark in three days and also to such a degree – that was just unbelievable.

But soon, they were even more shocked.

Another 40 days passed. Lin Ming had been at the Fallen God Mountain Range for a month and a half now. On this day, another soul sea mark lit up on Lin Ming’s shrine platform, dazzling with a blinding light.

This was the second soul sea mark. Lin Ming felt as if another layer had formed in his spiritual sea and his soul force became increasingly deep. He had obtained considerable benefits from attempting enlightenment here.

Of course, these advantages were because Lin Ming’s enlightenment results were almost perfect, far above what the average person could compare with.

Chapter 1839 – Identity Revealed

In the hazy pall of spiritual light, Lin Ming was bathed in the brilliant luster of the shrine platform. In this halo he was a solemn monk, meditating in a deep trance like an ancient Buddha.

His dazzling aura sharply contrasted with his appearance.

On the cliff, many people were left speechless.

This old uncle with a full beard was unexpectedly fierce.

“This fellow, he was just pretending to be a sheep. This definitely isn’t the first time he’s been here and he must have already comprehended a lot before.”

Someone said with utter certainty in their voice.

But even if one came here many times and tried to grasp enlightenment repeatedly, to obtain such a deep understanding was still something worthy of praise.

This was because for many people, even if they tried meditating here for dozens of years, they might only light up their fourth or fifth soul sea marks. And as for the brightness of those soul sea marks, they were completely different from Lin Ming’s.

Compared to Lin Ming’s soul sea marks, theirs were like a little candle in front of the bright night moon.

In the world of martial artists, strength reigned supreme. Many people immediately discarded their earlier thoughts of belittling Lin Ming.

Among these people, Jade Lifestone had haunted eyes. He didn’t want to admit that he had been wrong from the start. An inexplicable surge of anger filled his heart, “Yes, enlighten yourself, keep on enlightening yourself, I don’t believe that once you go further you can continue singing so loudly all this time.

“When Soul Empress Sheng Mei attempted enlightenment in the past, she was far better than this. Even so, she stopped at three soul sea marks.”

Jade Lifestone unhappily said. No matter how many times Lin Ming had come in the past, this didn’t change the fact that he was now inferior to Lin Ming.

It was because these were inalterable facts that Jade Lifestone found them hard to bear.

And indeed, Jade Lifestone wasn’t wrong.

On the 90th day of grasping the principles, Lin Ming began to feel the difficulty rise.

The lines on the shrine platform weren’t as simple as they seemed.

Gradually, the lines on the shrine platform began to turn hazy and emit a mysterious rhythm.

Each line had an inexplicable attraction emanating from it, making Lin Ming’s divine soul be lost within them.

He felt as if he were standing in an endless labyrinth and had lost all sense of direction.

Moreover, the paths of this labyrinth winded about, with walls as high as mountains. It was impossible to see where they led. Everyone was covered in a thick pitch black fog, a black cage with a terrifying aura that made his heart quicken.

Facing this vast sea of Laws, a sense of powerlessness grew in his heart.

But all this knowledge, the texts of the golden page that were fused into his body and divine soul, all of those comprehensions he had obtained, began to emit a brilliant light that resonated with the mysterious strength in the darkness.

In that originally meandering labyrinth, beams of golden light would periodically appear.

This golden light appeared throughout the entire labyrinth in a profound sequence.

Lin Ming accepted this stroke of good luck and followed the golden lights…

In the outside world, his body began to shake. His body that was covered in a soft light seemed to gently sway.

100 days.

Lin Ming found it difficult to continue forwards.

Then, another 10 days passed. With this, he surpassed the 108 days that Sheng Mei had spent here.

111 days. 112 days.

At 115 days, Lin Ming’s shrine platform began to shine with a brilliant radiance that illuminated his surroundings.

“Three soul sea marks!”

Lin Ming exhaled a long breath of air. At the same time, he deeply frowned.

His speed was slower than Sheng Mei’s.

But, this was also reasonable.

Shen Mei had read the Spiritas Holy Scripture before and her understandings of the golden pages naturally surpassed Lin Ming’s. Even if Lin Ming had the support of the Asura Sutra, it was still impossible for him to surpass Sheng Mei in comprehending principles of the soul forging system.

Thinking this, Lin Ming felt there were countless hurdles blocking his way from becoming thoroughly aware of the principles here and obtaining the golden page.

“No wonder they said it was the same as impossible to come to the Fallen God Mountain Range and obtain the golden page here… even when a True Divinity was in their youth and came here, they still failed…”

Lin Ming sighed in his heart. He was completely unsatisfied with his current results.

However, if those people watching Lin Ming were to know his thoughts, they would probably have killed themselves in disgust.

“Three soul sea marks, and he can make them shine with such a powerful divine light!”

It wasn’t a surprise to anyone that Lin Ming had lit up three soul sea marks. This was because they had already recognized that Lin Ming had come to the Fallen God Mountain Range before, so it wasn’t strange if he could light up the fourth or fifth soul sea marks.

But, what amazed them was that the three soul sea marks that did light up blazed like suns. None of those present were able to compare.

They looked at Lin Ming with disbelieving expressions. No matter how they looked at Lin Ming he didn’t seem like a top genius from some large influence.

Some people nearly stamped their feet on the ground. This fellow was actually so much stronger than they were. This feeling was as if some spirit medicine had been eaten up by a pig.

“This person probably disguised themselves. Maybe he’s a peak genius from some sect… if he could do what he did, he’s definitely not some nobody.”

Jade Lifestone muttered to himself as he stared at Lin Ming.

“He’s likely hiding his identity.” Some other proud sons of heavens from other ancient influences commented, finding this entire situation suspicious.

In order to gain enlightenment on the Phantom God Spirit Cliff, one needed an extraordinary background as well a certain comprehension into the highest Laws of the spiritas. These highest Laws were all parts of top secret inheritances, so where would ordinary martial artists ever be able to study them?

“I wonder where he is from? Are there any large influences with such an ugly elite…?”

The purple-clothed girl with two horns thought to herself, finding it hard to accept Lin Ming’s appearance.

But Lin Ming completely ignored all the whispers around him.

In his ears, all he heard were the divine sounds of the world. The texts of the golden page that had fused into his body and divine soul, as well as his comprehensions of them, floated within him like giant stars, exuding endless true meanings. Their shining light granted him a great deal of inspiration.

He could feel his soul force billowing like a vast tide. He had gained great benefits here once more.

Although there were many advantages, Lin Ming was still worried about how he would obtain the golden page here.

Then, a timid voice echoed in Lin Ming’s mind.

“H-h-h-hey… just now… there are some things that you seemed to have… mistaken…”

This voice startled Lin Ming. It was the red-dressed little girl he had met in the Akashic Dream Battlefield!

She had turned into a pure energy form that lingered around Lin Ming. No one was able to discover her presence.

The reason she suddenly spoke up now was because she realized there were errors in Lin Ming’s enlightenment.

This shocked Lin Ming. His three soul sea marks had shined so brilliantly, but he was actually wrong in his approach?

“Where was my mistake?”

Lin Ming quickly asked with a sound transmission. He knew that the red-dressed little girl wasn’t ordinary, but he didn’t think she would be able to see through the profound and complex principles of the shrine platform’s Laws.

But before the red-dressed little girl could reply, the skies suddenly changed color. A dreadful fluctuation of energy began to rise up from all around.

Lin Ming was startled. He looked up into the skies.

What just happened?

Rumble rumble rumble!

The air trembled, as if there was thunder brewing.

Dark clouds formed, blotting out the skies.

This sudden change left everyone panic-stricken. They all looked upwards, not sure what was happening.

And at this time, with a loud tearing sound, a divine sword seemed to cut through the skies. The gray clouds above the Phantom God Spirit Cliff were violently torn apart.

A misty light converged into a shining sea of light, one that appeared without any indication.

This light drowned out the skies. It was omnipresent, covering every person there.

Each ray of light seemed to originate from the nothingness of ancient times, seeming to illuminate all their hearts.

A vast aura spread outwards, making everyone’s hearts shake.

Beneath this shining light, all of the martial artists at the Phantom God Spirit Cliff were frightened. Beneath this light they felt completely powerless, nearly overcome with a desire to prostrate themselves on the ground in worship.

“Endless light, endless life, illuminate the 33 Heavens…”

From the heavens, after the sea of light appeared, a deep and boundless ancient voice followed right after.

As this voice appeared, countless motes of light formed in the air, constantly wandering around those present.

“Great Brahmic God King!”

“It’s the old ancestor! The old ancestor’s divine sense! Why would it be here!?”

Some of the chosen prides of heaven here had accompanied their honorable masters to the divine mountain before, or even came from the influence there. Now, these people all felt fear in their hearts. They fell to their knees.

“What? This sense comes from the Great Brahmic God King?”

“Great Brahmic God King… this is the sense of a God King!”

On the cliff, there were still some people on the shrine platforms who didn’t know where the origin of this mystical light was. After finding out, they fell to their knees, sincerely bowing.

The Great Brahmic God King was one of the top powerhouses of the Soul World. He was worthy of their worship.

“God King!?”

Lin Ming was bewildered. What was a God King? A True Divinity?

Lin Ming didn’t want to believe this, but even if this existence wasn’t a True Divinity, the title of God King wouldn’t be given to anyone below an Empyrean.

And from the responses of the elites present, this person was likely a True Divinity!

Even an Empyrean couldn’t bring out such a reaction. At the Akashic Dream Battlefield, after Empyrean Myriad Ghost and Chaos Demon God had appeared, although the young elites present had been afraid of them, they didn’t all fall to their knees.

A True Divinity was able to permeate their divine sense into the Fallen God Mountain Range; how was this possible?

“A True Divinity is powerful to this degree? Even though their main body cannot enter the Fallen God Mountain Range, they can still cover this area with their sense? Even affecting this area?”

A foreboding premonition rose in Lin Ming’s heart. If a True Divinity’s sense had come here, then there had to be a reason…

A cold sweat seeped down Lin Ming’s back. Then, it should be to track him!

Just as this thought flashed through Lin Ming’s mind, a beam of divine light fell down from the skies and covered him.

As Lin Ming was covered in this mystical light, it was like he had been struck by a bolt of lightning, like countless meteorites were smashing into his spiritual sea.

Luckily, Lin Ming’s divine soul was extremely formidable. Otherwise, his spiritual sea might have already collapsed upon being covered by this divine sense.

“A True Divinity’s strength!”

Although he already had a guess, the impact on his spiritual sea by this light confirmed to Lin Ming that this person who sent the divine sense here was a True Divinity. And worst of all, this True Divinity had come for him!

In an instant, Lin Ming’s limbs went cold, as if he had fallen into an icy lake!

A True Divinity had locked onto him!

“Damn.”

Lin Ming grimly thought. As he was covered in this light, he felt his divine soul be attacked by some strange marks.

Beneath the influence of these marks, his Bodily Rebirth Technique melted away like snow beneath the scorching sun. His beard disappeared… his muscles deflated… his face became thinner…

Lin Ming’s true appearance had been revealed.

Chapter 1840 – Surrounded

Lin Ming’s change was far too conspicuous. This was because as the divine light was gathered onto him, everyone’s eyes were focused towards him.

“Isn’t that the bearded uncle…?”

“That’s him, the shrine platform he’s sitting on still has three soul sea marks lit up. Moreover, their light is also stronger than the others’.”

Many people remembered where Lin Ming had been sitting. As they saw his rapidly changing appearance, they were left dumbfounded.

What was going on?

“He wasn’t old at all, he’s a youth!”

“He was hiding his appearance…”

The purple-clothed girl with horns had her mouth fall open as she watched Lin Ming turn from that scary-looking uncle to a dashing young man; the difference was too great.

Why did he conceal his appearance? Did he have some enemy?

But just as this thought passed over everyone’s hearts, they also realized something.

“This person looks familiar.”

“I saw a bounty on him at Oceanguard City!”

“He’s Lin Muk!”

Someone cried out in alarm. Most of the martial artists at Fallen God Mountain Range had been here for some time already as they tried to gain enlightenment, thus they didn’t recognize Lin Ming’s name.

“Who’s Lin Muk? What’s going on? Why would a True Divinity be looking for him?”

Fallen God Mountain Range had a skeletal age restriction, so no matter how powerful a True Divinity was, they could only send their sense here. And they likely had to pay some price to do so. But, why would they cause such a grand scene to look for a mere junior?

“This Lin Muk is the one who killed Empyrean Myriad Ghost at the Akashic Dream Battlefield! Moreover, he cut down countless World Kings and Great World Kings to finally collect a billion merit points and exchanged them for a golden page, and also left behind his name on the Emperor God Wall.”

“Not only does he have the golden page but he also has a spirit medicine beyond the transcendent divine level; I’ve heard it has already manifested into a kirin form.”

“There are several influences that have posted a sky high bounty for him. If we can kill him then that will be a great lucky chance for us!”

Soon, many people began speaking of Lin Ming. As Lin Ming’s accomplishments were spoken out loud, the martial artists that had been meditating at the Fallen God Mountain Range for a long time let out exclamations of surprise. This Lin Ming was so fierce?

He was being hunted down by so many people; no wonder he was hiding his appearance.

As for before, this could also explain how he had been able to light up three soul sea marks so brilliantly.

Jade Lifestone looked at Lin Ming, his complexion alternating between red and white. He really found it hard to believe that this was Lin Ming’s first time at the Akashic Dream Universe and that he had even slain an Empyrean at the same level. This was simply a monstrous genius that others couldn’t compare with at all.

For a time, many people began to surround Lin Ming.

They knew that many influences had posted an incredible bounty for him in Oceanguard City.

Standing upon the shrine platform, Lin Ming’s complexion had turned black. After being covered with the sense of a True Divinity, he no longer bothered with maintaining any semblance of a disguise. Instead, he drew out the Phoenix Blood Spear.

This Great Brahmic God King was actually able to bypass the rules of the Akashic Dream Universe to a certain extent. Were True Divinities powerful to such a degree?

Thinking about it, a True Divinity truly could disobey the rules of the world.

For instance, in piercing through the God Lamenting Wall that divided the 33 Heavens, or displaying such tremendous supernatural abilities in the Akashic Dream Universe.

After all, a True Divinity was only a boundary lower than the Asura Road Master and the author of the Holy Scripture.

“So you were Lin Muk!”

A gloomy voice shouted out. With innumerable ringing sounds, people drew their weapons.

As these people did so, they all blocked Lin Ming’s paths of escape.

Like this, Lin Ming became the public target.

Many people looked on with gloating expressions. Who cared how powerful Lin Ming was? In this kind of environment it was impossible for him to escape.

He wouldn’t be able to keep that golden page.

“Your name is Lin Muk? We have no previous enmity or injustice with you, but you have offended far too many people and the treasures you possess are far too valuable. You should also understand what it means for a man’s own wealth to ruin him by arousing the greed of others. So, don’t blame us for this. If you want to blame someone, only blame those who posted a bounty for you.”

At this time, three people stood up and took positions in three different directions around Lin Ming.

They all held swords in their hands.

“The Three Feather Prodigies.”

Someone said, startled. The Three Feather Prodigies were extremely famous. They were known as the most outstanding disciples to appear in the Phoenix Feather Holy Lands for the last billion years. Even here at the Fallen God Mountain Range they had considerable accomplishments in grasping the principles and had lit up their fifth soul sea marks.

In particular, if these three people joined forces, their overall combat strength would double!

“Originally we only needed to provide clues about your whereabouts to get the bounty rewards, but since the Great Brahmic God King has found you there is no point in doing that anymore. We can only subdue you and bring you in. Don’t blame us for kicking a man when he’s down!”

The boss of the Three Feather Prodigies sneered and slashed his sword at Lin Ming!

“You think you have the qualifications to kick me when I’m down? I want you to get the hell out of my way!”

Lin Ming suddenly roared out loud. His joints crackled and his aura changed, immediately becoming like a raging and endless sea.

Bang!

With a loud explosive sound, Lin Ming’s spear seemed to pierce through the skies. The gorgeous spear light crossed through the air and smashed into the boss of the Three Feather Prodigies.

“Big Brother!”

The Three Feather Prodigies had fast responses. They moved together to resist Lin Ming’s attack. However, with a cracking sound, the spear light erupted and billions of jins of strength gushed out. The world shook and space disintegrated.

The Three Feather Prodigies’ fused sword light immediately shattered like glass. The soul force spirit essence they poured into their sword light was also completely wiped out.

The three of them cried out in shock as they were sent tumbling away. As for the boss, he was sent soaring back hundreds of feet as blood spewed out from his body.

“What!?”

Everyone was shocked. The Three Feather Prodigies were defeated just like that?

“Mm? They didn’t die?”

A cold light sparkled in Lin Ming’s eyes. He moved forwards and chased after the Three Feather Prodigies. His spear swept out, cutting through the skies. One of the Three Feather Prodigies was sliced in half by the Phoenix Blood Spear, his blood dyeing the heavens.

“Third Brother!”

The remaining two of the Three Feather Prodigies felt their eyes turn red with rage. However, they weren’t Lin Ming’s match.

Lin Ming’s feet flickered as space seemed to lose meaning beneath him. He nearly teleported next to the remaining two, his spear falling down once more.

Puff! Puff!

With two light sounds, these two people had their hearts pierced by Lin Ming’s spear.

With this, the Three Feather Prodigies were slain by Lin Ming. Their deaths had been so sudden and brutal that even their true bodies had been wounded and it would take them some time to heal themselves.

After killing these three people, Lin Ming turned around without missing a beat. The Phoenix Blood Spear and his hand were already dyed crimson with blood!

“Death God Lin Muk!”

Seeing Lin Ming like this, some people couldn’t help but cry out the title he was given.

He was just far too strong. Even outstanding elites like the Three Feather Prodigies had been slain like farm chickens.

“Horrifying!”

Many people said, frightened. For a time, none of them dared to move forwards.

Although they were well aware that Lin Ming would die sooner or later since he was surrounded by so many people, no one wanted to be one of the first to attack him.

Those that did were destined to be killed by Lin Ming, and would have no chance of receiving the bounty reward.

For a time, all of those martial artists that thought of killing Lin Ming stopped in their steps, deciding to observe instead.

At this time, a heaven-shaking roar transmitted from the skies above.

“Lin Muk, I’ve finally found you!”

“Lin Muk, you killed countless people of my spirit race at the Akashic Dream Battlefield, even harming their spiritual seas! I will make you pay for this blood debt!”

“Lin Muk, in the Akashic Dream Battlefield my boundary was suppressed so I was killed by you, but now this is a fair battle in the Akashic Dream Universe! I will slay you and take revenge!”

Howls and roars overflowed from the skies.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming was startled. He sensed several strong auras that were rapidly arriving.

Looking up, he saw several shadows in the midst of the sea of brilliant light.

These people were sent from the influences he was enemies with. They weren’t too far from the Fallen God Mountain Range to begin with, and after obtaining the news they quickly hurried here using a transmission array.

Amongst these people, Lin Ming even saw the Purple Chestnut King. At the Akashic Dream Battlefield when Lin Ming had struck down the Purple Chestnut King, it hadn’t taken him any effort at all. But at that time, the Purple Chestnut King’s cultivation had also been suppressed. Now, he re-entered the Akashic Dream Universe so that he could kill Lin Ming in a situation where his cultivation boundary wasn’t suppressed and wipe out his previous disgrace.

“You all… even managed to make a True Divinity move…” Lin Ming’s eyes burst out with a murderous light. He never imagined he would be caught in such a situation where his whereabouts would be found by others. It seemed that he had really underestimated the heroes of the Soul World, and completely misunderstood the powers of a True Divinity.

Chapter 1841 – Clash

More and more people arrived. Dozens of squads had come with women and men, each one of them shining with radiant light. It was clear they were all uncommonly strong.

However, none of these people surpassed the ordinary World King realm. In fact, only a very small minority were ordinary World Kings.

To become a World King by 3000 years of age, anyone who could accomplish this was a genius amongst geniuses.

As for becoming a Great World King by 3000 years of age, that was a true monstrous genius. This sort of person could easily become an Empyrean before they were 10,000 years old, and in the future they would likely become an extreme Empyrean with even a small chance of attacking the True Divinity realm.

This type of person was exceedingly rare even in the entire Soul World. And even if there was one, they wouldn’t be spending much of their time here. Thus, even though Lin Ming was surrounded by all these large influences, it would be incredibly difficult for them to come up with a Great World King that was less than 3000 years old any time soon.

“Lin Muk, I’ll kill you in the Akashic Dream Universe first, and then I’ll bury you in the real world!”

A vicious light shined in the Purple Chestnut King’s eyes.

He had led a group of his spirit race people here to encircle Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s eyes darkened. Since he dared to come here to gain enlightenment, he was already prepared for this sort of situation. He had chosen this spot because of the restriction of the Laws, so even if there were masses of people trying to kill him, he didn’t fear them at all.

However, he had been secretly marked by a True Divinity. This was something that Lin Ming feared.

“If you want to kill me, then I’ll just kill you all first!” With his identity already exposed, Lin Ming no longer hid his strength. A terrifying aura erupted from his body, impacting into the heavens.

He moved without stirring the wind. The Phoenix Blood Spear cried out as if it were an eternally bloodthirsty beast that was awakening. A large tract of the cliff was illuminated in a blinding red light and a dreadful smell of blood filled the air.

This roiling killing intent locked onto all the people standing in the distance.

The people who arrived were mostly from the influences he had slaughtered in the Akashic Dream Battlefield. There were influences like the spirit race and Yellow Springs Palace, but there were also many other martial artists who came here for the golden page or for the bounty.

Facing so many outstanding individuals, Lin Ming was even marked by a True Divinity. No matter where he went he would be a torch in the dark, unable to hide.

Then he might as well make his stand here and massacre everyone!

At this time, a white-clothed woman stepped out from the crowd. Her cultivation was at the ordinary World King realm.

A normal World King that appeared in front of Lin Ming would have been instantly cut down. But, this World King was different. She was only 1300 years old and if she encountered another great lucky chance, she might even become an Empyrean when she was 10,000 or so years old. If so, she would even have a small chance of becoming a True Divinity.

In other words, Lin Ming was facing a martial artist who was only slightly inferior to a young Emperor Shakya!

“I am from Great Brahmic God Mountain and am one of the Great Brahmic God King’s disciples. Today I have come here by the bidding of my honorable master to take your life!”

The woman’s voice was cold, with no hint of emotion in her eyes.

The surrounding martial artists on the shrine platforms sucked in a deep breath. Great Brahmic God Mountain! A True Divinity disciple!

Even in the main universe of the Soul World, a True Divinity was a legendary existence. Wherever a True Divinity disciple went, they would rouse feelings of absolute inferiority!

They didn’t know who this white-clothed woman was, but they didn’t doubt that she was a terrifying opponent!

“Senior-apprentice Sister Icydew, be careful around that brat! He has a stronger spear and also two avatars! Those two avatars have an unbelievable defensive power.”

Beside the white-clothed woman, the Purple Chestnut King warned her as he glared at Lin Ming, listing all of Lin Ming’s cards one at a time.

“There’s no need for words!”

The white-clothed woman’s voice was cold. She stretched out her hands and her fingers rapidly moved. Shards of ice began to fall down around her as the surrounding temperature rapidly dipped!

Weng!

A dreadful cold energy burst outwards. Even the rocks were suddenly covered with a layer of frost and the air became bone-bitingly cold.

For dozens of miles around, parts of the mountain froze over and began to fall down.

This was a horrifying level of power.

The geniuses standing on the shrine platforms near Lin Ming suddenly widened their eyes, their complexions changing. They knew that this was the attack of an ultra-powerhouse. They flew up from the shrine platforms, all of them hurriedly fleeing the waves of ice cold energy.

Lin Ming no longer had anywhere to hide. His killing spirit rose and his spear radiated a blinding light. In the void, the spear was wrapped in a massive sun-bright inferno. Lava seemed to tumble around in the air, carrying with it the inexhaustible power of heavenly tribulation power as it smashed into the freezing waves of cold energy.

Heavenly fire raged, bringing with it the true meaning of fire as it sank into the waves of ice and snow.

Two forces of extreme hot and extreme cold crashed into each other. Airwaves crazily swept out, wreaking havoc in all directions.

On the mountain peak, there were some servants of the young elites present. Some of these people weren’t able to move in time and were caught up in the energy waves. With miserable cries they were directly ground into paste.

In this strike, the two forces were evenly matched!

The white-clothed woman frowned. In that collision just now, she had felt Lin Ming’s enormous strength; he was a formidable opponent.

“Humph! This isn’t the Akashic Dream Battlefield where our cultivation boundaries are suppressed! Pathetic, give up any thoughts of escape!”

In the void, another World King level powerhouse began to move. With his entire body shrouded in dense demonic energy, he secretly attacked Lin Ming.

This martial artist came from Yellow Springs Palace. Although he was also a World King, he was nearly 3000 years old and had just barely managed a breakthrough. Although he was still an early World King, he was still far inferior to Icydew, whether it was in terms of talent or strength.

Hidden in the crowds of people, he took out a blood red jar that was filled with splashing black blood.

This black blood gushed out and transformed into a massive blood river. The blood river crashed about, emanating a cold yin chill.

In the midst of this blood river, devils bobbed up and down. With the pressure of a falling mountain, a terrifyingly monstrous demonic energy was emitted. Even the air melted away beneath this demonic energy, creating large swathes of nothingness. It was a fearful power.

This was an extremely cruel and violent magic tool. Everyone drew as far away as they could lest they be touched by this blood red light.

The proud children of heaven that were on the shrine platforms all flew away, afraid that the blood river would touch them and make it impossible for them to be saved.

Lin Ming glanced at the black blood. He could feel that the blood red jar was strange, but in terms of strength, this was much weaker than Icydew. His eyes flashed with a cold light and a black spear leapt into his hands, one that emitted a boundless ancient power. This was the Black Dragon Spear!

Many people who understood Lin Ming thought that he would choose to fight with the Phoenix Blood Spear in order to save his strength. But at this time, Lin Ming actually drew out the Black Dragon Spear; this was completely unexpected.

Woosh!

Spear light soared up. The Heretical God Tree appeared with countless tiny thunder dragons wrapped around it, each one carrying the endless true meaning of thunder. Then, these thunder dragons began to transform into tiny sand-like motes of thunder power.

These motes of thunder bloomed with infinite arcs of lightning and smashed into the blood river and the devils within like countless stars.

The heavens and earth became a vast expanse of blinding white for a moment. Then, lightning rumbled and the world shook.

The martial artist that was carrying the blood red jar was the first to bear the brunt of this attack. He was instantly submerged into the waves of lightning.

“Ahh!”

A frightening detonation rang out. Within the resounding claps of lightning, a youth in blood red robes soared upwards, avoiding the sheets of lightning.

The blood river and devils he released had been swallowed up by the power of thunder and had been completely destroyed. Even the blood red jar in his hands had a pitch black crack in it.

This crack still shined with the mystic power of lightning that tore apart the black runes swirling around it and prevented the blood red jar from restoring itself. Between the youth’s eyebrows, star-like motes of thunder shined, emitting endless thunderclaps that caused the blood red-robed youth to vomit blood again and again. It was clear that this blood red-robed youth had been severely wounded.

Everyone standing far away in the air was left amazed. This blood red-robed youth was clearly a World King genius, but he had been grievously wounded after a single strike from Lin Ming.

Lin Ming was about to rush forwards and finish off this person with his spear, but suddenly a wall of ice blocked his path; the one who was stopping him was that Icydew once more.

Shua!

Lin Ming faced Icydew. The long spear in his hands had changed, replaced by the Phoenix Blood Spear once more!

Kacha!

The Phoenix Blood Spear turned into a beam of light that thrust through the ice wall. Spear light shot out, blasting open chunks of the ice wall that rained down in all directions!

This left everyone surprised. Lin Ming was constantly switching his spears?

But they immediately understood what happened.

Lin Ming didn’t have confidence he could severely wound Icydew with the Black Dragon Spear in a single move. Thus, he had chosen to fight her with the Phoenix Blood Spear to conserve his strength.

But to deal with those who were relatively strong but couldn’t compare with Icydew, he would use the Black Dragon Spear so he could defeat them in a single move and save his strength.

“Rather than wounding ten fingers he would rather break off one. This Lin Muk is decisive!”

“Facing so many opponents he’s still saving as much strength as he can. What a terrifying enemy.”

The surrounding martial artists immediately understood Lin Ming’s plan.

And at this time, more and more people attacked Lin Ming.

They had no intention of fighting one on one – they chose to swarm him together!

Seeing energy of divine light cover the skies, Lin Ming’s eyes flashed with bolts of thunder. He rapidly drew back!

“There are too many enemies and there will be more and more of them catching up! If I can’t break my way out of here then I’ll die sooner or later and the golden page will be taken away!”

Lin Ming frowned as he looked at the people who were wrapped in divine light.

He had to hurry!

Ping!

Lin Ming kicked out at the nearest man. The blood of an Azure Dragon roared within him, carrying with it the endless draconic power. Like a True Dragon diving into the sea, the kick was like a shadow as it smashed outwards.

This kick contained billions of jins of strength, enough to shatter air itself.

The man was startled; he didn’t think Lin Ming would take the initiative to attack him. Soul force condensed into a wall to resist this attack.

But as a result, the soul wall was crushed by this kick and the man’s chest was caved in by the kick. With several cracking sounds, the man’s bones broke all over and he was sent tumbling away as he vomited blood.

These people were all proud children of heaven with the strength of a peak Holy Lord. But in front of Lin Ming, they didn’t even have the strength to resist.

“This human’s mortal body is far too terrifying!”

“Part of us focus on attack and part of us focus on defense. Join together and use as many divine soul attacks as you can. There’s no need to show mercy or honor here!” The Purple Chestnut King shouted out. Clearly fearing Lin Ming, he didn’t step forwards at all.

At this time, killing Lin Ming was all that mattered. Anything like a martial arts spirit was a secondary matter.

Even the arrogant Icydew didn’t refuse joining forces with the others. This was because she knew that she wouldn’t be able to defeat Lin Ming one on one.

With direct orders that came from the Great Brahmic God King himself, she had to complete her master’s commands no matter the cost.

Chapter 1842 – Killing, Killing, Killing

….

…

….

Dozens of figures threw themselves towards Lin Ming.

In the skies, endless radiance sparkled and hails of thunder and fire billowed. Divine pagodas came falling down with a mountain-like suppression and massive palms split open the void… all sorts of soul techniques came raining down.

Moreover, these soul techniques contained strange soul attacks within them.

Lin Ming’s complexion was dignified. Even if his fighting strength was amazing and his mortal body was incomparably powerful, he was still pressured when facing crowds of elite martial artists.

The peak Holy Lords among these people could fight an ordinary World King.

The ordinary World Kings could struggle with a Great World King.

Arcs of lightning wove themselves around Lin Ming. The grandmist space appeared to deal with all of these attacks, but it was still constantly weakened.

Lin Ming gripped his fists. At this moment he was being sieged from all sides. If he waited here then there would inevitably be more and more people arriving.

He reached out into the void and stirred up a massive black vortex. The Black Dragon Spear appeared in his grasp once more, exuding waves of surging slaughter energy.

Lin Ming poured his true essence into the Black Dragon Spear. The spear began to emit a space-piercing black light, as if it were a vicious dragon being rudely awoken.

Bang –

A deep and dull explosion rang out from within Lin Ming’s flesh and blood.

Following this deep sound were endlessly rolling thunderclaps that continued non-stop.

In his pitch black pupils, sand-like runes began to wink in and out of existence. Crimson energy started circling him like a blood dragon.

Scales jutted out from his skin, forming a black suit of armor that wrapped around him. His killing aura soared to the heavens.

Lin Ming had awoken the Asura blood.

In a brief moment, his bodily strength multiplied by several times and his defensive capabilities rapidly stormed upwards.

Dang! Dang! Dang!

His feet stepped on the void. Every step he took caused space to split open as if it were the ground.

He shot into the skies like a rising comet. The Black Dragon Spear emitted endless black light as the soul techniques crashing towards him began disintegrating one at a time.

With the Phoenix Blood Spear in his left hand and Black Dragon Spear in his right, he fired towards the severely wounded blood red-robed youth.

He’d kill him while he was down!

The blood red-robed youth sat cross-legged in the air, black soul force surging around his forehead, trying desperately to eliminate the star-like motes of light that flickered between his eyes. As he saw Lin Ming appear in front of him, his complexion turned white.

Several half-step World Kings nearby noticed Lin Ming’s plan.

They all reached out, trying to capture Lin Ming.

Lin Ming didn’t pause. The Phoenix Blood Spear emitted a blinding light, piercing through all the phantasmal great palms that reached towards him.

Lin Ming’s spear broke apart a flood dragon created by soul force. Then, the Black Dragon Spear drew a beautiful arc in the air and severed the heads of these half-step World Kings. Their blood began to gush out like fountains!

And at this time, Icydew’s eyes flashed with a sharp light. She appeared beside Lin Ming like ghosts and gods. Her right hand reached out with pinched fingers as she tried to strike Lin Ming’s ribs.

Wherever her fingers went, space froze over, as if a massive river of ice was galloping towards Lin Ming.

“Die!”

Lin Ming had erupted with the strength of the Asura blood and now he was a dragon in human form. His strength had more than doubled and it was no longer possible for Icydew to stop him.

Peng!

A terrifying explosion rang out and the endless cold ice was shattered by Lin Ming. Even the frozen combat armor worn by Icydew completely broke apart.

Icydew cried out in alarm and rapidly drew back, her chest dripping with blood.

“What!?”

Icydew was shocked. Lin Ming was actually this powerful!? She thought Lin Ming was originally just a tad stronger than she was, but after undergoing this body metamorphosis, his strength had multiplied.

At this time, Icydew could only stare helplessly on as Lin Ming pierced towards the blood red-robed youth at an inconceivable angle.

The blood red-robed youth panicked. He had been a renowned martial artist for a long time already, but when facing this Black Dragon Spear, he felt his divine soul tremble. His hairs stood on end and he tried to flee backwards. The crimson jar in his hands rose up, rumbling towards the Black Dragon Spear.

This was an extremely evil magic tool that had been refined by his honorable master using 100,000 years. It contained the resentments of a trillion anguished spirits and was extremely durable.

But this magic tool was instantly pierced through by the Black Dragon Spear. The trillion spirits within were then sucked up by the black energy circulating around the Black Dragon Spear.

Woosh!

The blood red-robed youth from the Yellow Springs Palace had just managed to retreat a thousand feet, but almost instantly he was run through by the Black Dragon Spear. In his horrified eyes, his blood essence was completely sucked up by the Black Dragon Spear as his body turned into a leather bag of bones that slowly fell to the ground.

Lin Ming killed the blood red-robed youth with a single spear strike. The death of a World King genius had occurred in an instant.

However, during this brief moment, Lin Ming also came under attack from others.

He was being bombarded from all sides!

Although the grandmist space blocked the majority of these attacks, many soul techniques still struck his body. Yet, after stimulating the Asura blood, his incredible defense allowed him to resist it all!

And as this sight fell into the eyes of those present, they felt nothing but abject horror.

“My attack would have severely wounded an ordinary World King, but he wasn’t injured at all?”

“My strike just now could pierce through a small planet, but he didn’t even spit blood… he even killed that World King from the Yellow Springs Palace…”

A cold chill swept through the hearts of those present. All of them looked at each other, able to feel that this human youth was incomprehensibly fierce. Someday in the future, although he might not be able to harm the spiritas as a whole, he might be a scourge upon their various influences!

“To all the heroes at the Phantom God Spirit Cliff, this human called Lin Muk snuck into our Akashic Dream Battlefield and used despicable means to kill my people, even angering the Great Brahmic God King to the point where he took personal action to seek this human… to all fellow martial cultivators, let us kill this human together! If anyone has accomplishments during this battle then my people will give you a large reward, we can even double the posted bounty!”

The Purple Chestnut King shouted out from a safe position far away from the battlefield. His voice spread out for hundreds of miles.

On the Phantom God Spirit Cliff, there were innumerable proud children of heaven from different influences trying to grasp the principles here.

Although the average level of these people couldn’t match with the martial artists that had rushed here to kill Lin Ming, there were still some peerless young elites hidden in the crowd where they remained unknown.

If these people could be used, they would be a considerable force.

After the Purple Chestnut King spoke, some people didn’t wish to be used as a weapon by these influences and quietly withdrew.

But there were some people who had harbored a burning envy towards Lin Ming for lighting three soul sea marks in such a short period of time. Moreover, with Lin Ming’s status as a human added on and the total amount of bounties offered for him, they were tempted.

“If you take the lead we will naturally help.”

A martial artist on a shrine platform said. They already considered Lin Ming as a fish on a chopping block, but this struggling fish just had a few more bones than usual.

“Kill him! Strike together!” Someone from the Yellow Springs Palace cried out loud.

“As long as we kill him in the Akashic Dream Universe then his true body will be ejected from the  separate space and the Great Brahmic God King can use his transcendent methods once more to find him! At that time, we can kill him however we want!”

Outside the battlefield, the Purple Chestnut King yelled out.

“Hahaha! Lin Muk, I want to see just how you’ll die then!”

The Purple Chestnut King’s eyes were fierce. Lin Ming’s thoughts turned cold. He had already experienced the Great Brahmic God King’s methods once and he didn’t doubt that he could be found again!

If he died here, then losing the golden page wouldn’t be the only consequence!

In the end, the reason Lin Ming was in such a crisis was because he didn’t completely understand the methods of a True Divinity.

At this time, the people from the Yellow Springs Palace took the initiative to attack. Endless ghosts blocked out the skies!

Behind them, several whistling sounds rang through the air as the people atop the shrine platforms flew towards Lin Ming. Arcs of blazing light radiated from their bodies as the world seemed to surge around them.

“You want to kill me?”

Lin Ming’s eyes turned blood red. Black light shot out from his body. The Black Dragon Spear thrust into the void, causing a pitch black light to appear.

Soon, the pitch black light expanded again and again, carrying with it a billowing power of chaos. Like a black hole, it emitted an inexhaustible power to swallow everything.

The dozen plus martial artists that flew towards Lin Ming weren’t able to stop. The black hole swallowed them all and specks of their flesh and blood rained down from the skies.

The thick stench of blood filled the air.

These people had been killed in such a violent manner that even in the real world their divine souls had been injured. Moreover, these injuries weren’t minor at all!

But at the same time, as Lin Ming attacked, his back was also ambushed by several people.

There were far too many people here! They came in swarms larger than the time Lin Ming had been surrounded in the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

And, these people didn’t have their cultivations suppressed. Many of them had a cultivation base higher than Lin Ming.

Rumble rumble rumble.

These people were all elites of their era and their striking power was astonishing. Beneath the barrage of star-bright beams of light, Lin Ming avoided the majority of them but was still struck by a good number of attacks. No matter how strong his defensive capabilities were, after being bombarded by so many people his blood vitality still swelled up and his inner energy turned chaotic.

Blood began flowing down the scales on Lin Ming’s back.

“I have to move! I can’t just stand here in the middle and let them attack me, otherwise I’ll just exhaust myself and die!”

Lin Ming immediately thought. He turned his head and an infinite mystical strength erupted once more. His icy cold gaze swept through the spiritas martial artists that had attacked him from behind.

“I’ll start with you!”

Lin Ming shouted out. He stepped on the void and his velocity reached the limit.

He revolved the Space Laws, instantly appearing in front of those who had ambushed him, causing everyone else to lose their target.

“Be careful!”

Someone cried out in alarm. But, it was too late!

The Black Dragon Spear swept out and a terrifying killing intent erupted. The heads of three ambushers exploded into bits, their brains and blood spraying outwards!

This brutal way of dying frightened the other martial artists. If they died in such a manner, and especially with their heads blown apart, this would inevitably cause major damage to their spiritual seas. Even their true bodies would suffer debilitating losses and would require at least a year to recover from. Moreover, they wouldn’t be able to fully recover without the use of miracle medicines.

“Kill him!”

In the skies, someone from the Yellow Springs Palace attacked!

Just as he attacked Lin Ming, Lin Ming instantly vanished, appearing not too far away from him. As for those other martial artists that had been standing near Lin Ming, they were caught in the radius of the missed attack. The ghosts sent by the Yellow Spring Palace martial artist swallowed them whole, leaving their ear-piercing screams to fill the air.

The feeling of being swallowed up by these ghostly spirits was no better than having one’s head blown apart, and it also caused major damage to one’s divine soul.

“Damn it!”

The one who attacked was stunned. He had actually accidently killed those on his side.

But in that brief moment of surprise, Lin Ming had appeared in front of him. With arctic eyes, the Black Dragon Spear in his hands slashed out like the scythe of a death god!

Blood bloomed like a red lotus…

Chapter 1843 – Tragic

Puff! Puff! Puff!

Lin Ming was like a god of death, endlessly harvesting life. As for those martial artists who were killed by Lin Ming, their hearts were blown up and their spiritual seas shattered into pieces.

This was a ruthless and brutal killing method that horrified all of the martial artists present.

Even in the Akashic Dream Battlefield, if they were killed like this by Lin Ming then they would still have to pay an enormous price.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

Starlight from the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace poured into Lin Ming’s body. His body emitted crackling sounds as he swept away all obstacles in his path!

And with Lin Ming’s speed, nearly no one was able to lock onto him. Their attacks missed, even striking nearby people.

“Lock him down!”

The Purple Chestnut King roared to the crowd.

At this time, a yellow-haired youth from Chaos Divine Palace flew out, a turtle shell in his hand.

This turtle shell was strange. As soon as it appeared, it emitted an endless chaotic light, immediately transforming into a bizarre soul beast as large as a mountain that roared like thunder.

This soul beast looked like a giant taotie from afar. The hairs down its mouth were as thick as buckets and the light of chaos shimmered around it. Simple runes exuding soul force shined on its forehead, spreading through the heavens and earth and exuding an overwhelming atmosphere. It opened its maw and swallowed, drawing in all of the nearby soul force.

“Mm? Heaven swallowing beast!”

The spiritas martial artists immediately recognized this soul beast. In the legends, once this beast grew into an adult it could even swallow up the life force of a planet, turning it into a dead rock.

This heaven swallowing beast in front of them had been killed by Chaos Demon God before it was an adult and then had its soul sealed into this ancient turtle shell and refined into a magic tool.

As this turtle shell was taken out, the spirit essence of the heaven swallowing beast could be released to swallow everything nearby, including even nearby allies.

In ordinary times, a direct disciple that held this turtle shell wouldn’t think of using it. This was because every time this heaven swallowing beast’s spirit essence was used it would be weakened until it was finally ruined.

But now, facing Lin Ming, he could only take it out.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Icydew, if you and I join together we can seal up the surrounding space and cage in this Lin Muk to kill him!” The yellow-haired youth said to Icydew.

Icydew frowned. As a proud disciple of the Great Brahmic God King, to join forces with so many others to strike down a human left her feeling frustrated. But now she had no other choice; she could only coordinate attacks with these people.

She took out a soul tool that looked like a fish scale.

This scale came from a Deep Sea Leviathan God Beast, and inherently carried the true meaning of the Ice Laws. It had been personally refined by her master and was considered her best soul tool.

As this soul tool appeared, a chilling wind spread out, even freezing the nearby space.

Soul force surged within her body. The strange fish scale rose up against the wind.

Countless ice runes rapidly froze the space around Lin Ming and the heaven swallowing beast, creating a ten thousand foot cage of ice and snow around him.

This cage of ice and snow trapped Lin Ming with everyone else.

As Icydew activated the fish scale, more and more ice runes grew around the cage of ice and snow, making it increasingly thick.

“Mm?”

Lin Ming frowned as he saw the surrounding space freeze around him. He could no longer increase his speed. Then, the heaven swallowing beast opposite of him locked its blood red pupils onto him as they bloomed with a boundless light.

A terrifying swallowing strength covered him, causing his speed to fall.

Rumble rumble rumble!

Inside the freezing enchantment, strands of energy exploded, shaking the world.

“The heaven swallowing beast’s swallowing power can lock down the void. Lin Muk will be unable to use his previous speed. He will die beneath a barrage of our attacks.”

The yellow-haired youth from Chaos Divine Palace shouted out, “Attack together!”

Icydew’s freezing enchantment didn’t block the attacks of anyone else. For a time, everyone struck out together; the air lit up with countless beams of divine light!

To Lin Ming, the individual strength of these people wasn’t anything at all. But when they were all combined together, it was enough to shatter a planet!

“He’s dead for sure!”

The Purple Chestnut King stood outside the freezing enchantment, his lips curved up in a fierce smile. No matter how great Lin Ming’s defensive powers were, it would be impossible to live through such a terrifying barrage of attacks.

The moment that Lin Ming was covered in this divine light, an inexplicably vast aura violently surged out from the freezing enchantment.

This aura was sly and treacherous, like a deep crimson sea.

As the various elites of the Soul World surrounding the freezing enchantment felt this aura, all of them shivered in the depths of their divine soul.

This Lin Muk – he could still resist?

A shocked light flashed in Icydew’s eyes. The fish scale soul tool in her hand violently shook and the light within it weakened. Even the numerous floating Ice Law runes began shattering in droves as they were constantly annihilated. This was proof that her freezing enchantment had just suffered a horrifying impact.

Ka ka ka!

A crack appeared in the freezing enchantment; it was being slowly torn apart.

Rumble rumble rumble!

All of the divine light exploded together. At the center of the freezing enchantment where Lin Ming was standing, the dim phantom of a black-armored warrior stood high, pushing a massive wheel.

In every revolution of the wheel, endless Asura fighting spirit shined within. Countless runes glittered like stars inside it, making it feel as if even gods and buddhas would be extinguished within this black wheel.

Beneath this giant wheel, the previously inordinately arrogant heaven swallowing beast was being slowly crushed. With loud cracking sounds, every impact caused countless soul force runes to break apart and the heaven swallowing beast to weaken.

This black wheel was the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and Myriad Essence Reincarnation Wheel overlapping on each other.

In the separate space within the stone forest, in that ancient galactic battlefield, Lin Ming had obtained endless harvests when he witnessed and comprehended the final battle between the Asura Road Master and the ancient spiritas king.

His comprehension of the Asura Sutra became far more profound and with that, the associated Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel became even stronger.

The Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel had an inherent ability to crush apart all source force and evil spirits. Besides the Magic Cube, it could be called one of Lin Ming’s strongest methods to deal with the spiritas.

Rumble rumble rumble!

All of the divine lights of these attacks fell atop the wheel and were completely swallowed up by it.

However, the wheel also withstood a tremendous impact!

Lin Ming’s blood vessels rose up, his meridians appearing!

“He cannot keep withstanding this! He has consumed too much energy and his aura is weakening!”

“That black spear is fierce, but it also sucks out a massive amount of his true essence!”

In the crowd, many people shouted out loud. But at the same time, all of them were dumbstruck to the extreme. Lin Ming was far too horrifying an enemy. Even under such an onslaught of attacks he was still able to persist.

Woosh! Woosh! Woosh!

More people attacked. Some martial artists that were observing the battle from the shrine platforms also joined in on the melee. They saw Lin Ming decisively killing all those nearby and hadn’t attacked because they feared they would be drawn into the mess and destroyed. But now as they saw Lin Ming besieged by innumerable people, like an elephant being slowly whittled down, they also took this chance to join in. They wanted to be the last straw that crushed his back.

More and more people joined in. Lin Ming was the target of all.

In this world, there would never be a lack of people who were willing to take advantage of someone when they were down. Moreover, Lin Ming was from a different race, and the spiritas geniuses were jealous of his achievements and talent.

These people never wanted to see others do well. Thus, seeing Lin Ming in distress and also with bounty rewards to take, they didn’t mind giving Lin Ming an extra kick.

Bang!

An even more horrifying explosion lit up the skies. A crack appeared in the Asura phantom’s giant wheel. Blood began to flow down the corners of Lin Ming’s lips.

His eyes were blood red with rage and his body erupted to the peak with killing intent.

This was the sorrow of being from another race. The more he dazzled with glory, the easier he would be classified as a foe!

“Hehe, die!”

The Purple Chestnut King also attacked. Before this he had been hiding safely on the sidelines of the battlefield, but now as he saw that Lin Ming was nearly exhausted, he finally chose to move forwards and attack with everything he had. He tossed out all sorts of inscription symbols, wanting to tear Lin Ming to pieces.

Lin Ming’s eyes blazed with a fierce murderous intent.

Woosh! Woosh!

From Lin Ming’s inner world, two figures rushed out.

The speed of these two figures approached extreme velocities. One figure rushed towards the shrine platforms to finish off the weaker martial artists and another one hurtled towards the Purple Chestnut King!

“Be careful!”

Someone cried out. But, it was too late.

The figure flying towards the shrine platforms was the purple-clothed Lin Ming, the Soul Springs Divine Embryo. His movements were like ghosts and gods; in an instant, several geniuses on the shrine platforms had their spiritual seas pierced through.

At the same time, the black-clothed Lin Ming, the Essence Spirit Embryo Stone, also reached the Purple Chestnut King.

“Damn it!” The Purple Chestnut King roared, “Do you think a mere avatar can harm me!?”

The Purple Chestnut King extracted a heavy sword from his spatial ring and cut down towards the black-clothed avatar. A divine soul attack was contained within his sword light!

Bang!

A terrifying collision occurred. The black-clothed Lin Ming’s mortal body had been refined endlessly through billions of years and had long become indestructible. In terms of bodily strength, this avatar was stronger than Lin Ming. As for the Purple Chestnut King’s divine soul attack, it was unable to do anything to the black-clothed Lin Ming, because within the avatar’s spiritual sea, what was condensed there was the murderous thoughts of the Asura Road Master.

Puff!

The Purple Chestnut King spat out a mouthful of blood as he tumbled away. He had been defeated in a single strike!

The Purple Chestnut King hadn’t even been able to contend with an avatar. The disparity was far too great!

The black-clothed Lin Ming continued his onslaught. It joined forces with the purple-clothed Lin Ming and began slaughtering the surrounding martial artists. With these two avatars fighting together, their combat strength reached incomprehensible levels. They cut down swathes of martial artists and were no less ruthless in their methods. The martial artists that died had their heads burst open!

Blood rained down from the skies.

But at this time, Lin Ming had also consumed his strength to the limit. The black wheel in the Asura phantom’s hands had thoroughly disintegrated!

Lin Ming had been severely wounded and was bleeding all over.

His chest and stomach were stained with blood and a great number of his ribs were broken. His organs were torn in multiple places and his meridians were ripped. This was an extremely tragic battle.

No matter how strong he was, he couldn’t withstand the bombardment of so many people.

“He’s almost done for.”

Someone said. But as their voice fell, they heard a pitiful cry echo through the air. The Purple Chestnut King had his heart pierced through by the combined attack of the two avatars.

The Purple Chestnut King howled in fear, panic coloring his face. He had just been killed by Lin Ming in the Akashic Dream Battlefield not too long ago, and his divine soul had yet to fully heal from that. Now, he was suffering a similar fate.

“No!”

The Purple Chestnut King screeched. After being continuously killed twice, this would create heavy damage to his divine soul, to the point where it would affect his future achievements.

Peng!

The black-clothed Lin Ming’s expression was indifferent. His fist came punching out, directly exploding the Purple Chestnut King’s head!

Chapter 1844 – Change

As red blood and white brains rained down, the martial artists present were left terrified. The Purple Chestnut King had been killed by Lin Ming once more!

To die twice in the Akashic Dream Universe within two or three years, and in such a brutal manner, it was highly likely that the Purple Chestnut King would suffer severe wounds to his soul that would be hard to recover from.

And at this moment, Lin Ming attacked once more. The full weight of the Black Dragon Spear came smashing down on the turtle shell floating in space.

Kacha!

The turtle shell cracked and the yellow-haired elite was panic-stricken, his heart trembling. This was a treasure granted to him by Chaos Demon God; he absolutely could not lose it!

As his heart raced with fear, the yellow-haired youth thrust forth his hand and cast out a soul technique. A flood dragon of soul force flew into the void, wanting to snatch back that turtle shell.

Lin Ming ignored the wounds covering his body. The broken Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel began to forcefully revolve once more, wiping away that soul technique. Then, he thrust out a hand and grabbed the simple-looking turtle shell.

The turtle shell was covered with all sorts of ancient and solemn runes. It was a mass of soul force condensed by an Empyrean, but after being rubbed by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel, the light of these runes immediately dimmed down.

Lin Ming reached out and wrapped the turtle shell with layers of seals before placing it in his spatial ring.

As the yellow-haired youth felt his mental connection with the turtle shell severed, he was so angry he nearly vomited blood.

“Continue the barrage! Turn him to ashes!”

The yellow-haired youth roared out in rage. He could sense that Lin Ming was already a spent force, but he didn’t think he would still be so strong.

“Lock in the space, don’t let him escape!” A disciple from Great Brahmic God Mountain stood up. He led the main force here to kill Lin Ming.

“Junior-apprentice Sister Icydew, use the freezing domain once more!”

The disciple turned and said to Icydew. He was an extremely calm and collected yellow-clothed youth.

Icydew took a deep breath. Because she was a proud character, she felt that her actions were dishonorable. But, she wouldn’t defy her master’s orders nor would she hold back.

Ca!

An ice flower bloomed. The void froze over once more, slowing down Lin Ming’s speed.

She was amongst the strongest martial artists here. Although she had an ordinary World King cultivation, she could kill a Great World King.

With other people protecting her, there was nothing Lin Ming could do to her.

“To all those at the Fallen God Mountain Range, I’ve come here as the representative from Great Brahmic God Mountain to say this. Today, as long as you fight and do your best to bring down Lin Muk, you will obtain 10 top grade soul crystals as a reward, provided by Great Brahmic God Mountain. If you are unfortunately killed by Lin Ming in battle, then the reward will be doubled. Moreover, Great Brahmic God Mountain will provide spirit medicines to heal you and remove the soul wounds you receive from dying in the Akashic Dream Universe.”

Standing besides Icydew, the yellow-clothed youth spoke to those present.

His cultivation was also at the World King realm.

In the Soul World, it was incredibly rare to find a Great World King below 3000 years of age. But, to find ordinary World Kings below 3000 years of age was much easier.

This youth was also a core disciple from Great Brahmic God Mountain. Although he was less talented than Icydew, he managed the daily affairs of Great Brahmic God Mountain and his words held great weight.

By killing Lin Ming, the golden page on him would belong to the Great Brahmic God King. Compared to such a priceless treasure, some soul crystals and spirit medicines weren’t anything at all.

And indeed, as the martial artists on the shrine platforms heard this yellow-clothed youth’s words they were all stirred up. To them, 10 top grade soul crystals was an unbelievable amount of wealth.

“Attack together!”

“Dying doesn’t matter. Great Brahmic God Mountain has come here and offered their own resources in front of everyone. They won’t go back on their spoken words.”

More and more people joined the battle. This Fallen God Mountain Range was originally a gathering place for geniuses, and now these waves of people surrounded Lin Ming, making it impossible for him to escape!

Without a doubt, this was because Lin Ming had great treasures on his body. But, it was also because he was of a different race. In the Soul World, humans were simply servants to be pushed around.

In the eyes of these people, Lin Ming was nothing but a walking bag of soul crystals and rewards.

As for the value of his life and survival, no one cared at all.

The battlefield in space was horrendous. Countless runes shattered and soul force broke apart.

Vast waves of potent strength swelled up, twisting apart the void and causing space to boil.

Lin Ming was completely drenched in blood. Although the fused Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel and Myriad Essence Reincarnation Wheel had split open, it wasn’t fully destroyed just yet!

This was because after Lin Ming killed these numerous elites, he was able to draw out spiritual energy and blood essence from their broken bodies to restore himself.

However, his restorative abilities weren’t as fast as the rate at which he used up energy.

The light of the two wheels faded as more and more cracks appeared over their surface.

The massive Asura phantom also began to weaken. Only its two pupils continued to emit the same bloodthirsty red light as it killed more people. It still projected a terrifying killing intent that made one’s heart race.

More and more wounds crisscrossed Lin Ming’s body.  His blood-drenched body stood proud in space, completely covered with dense curse seals.

His scales had been broken in numerous places and there was not a single unharmed inch on his body. Blood wet his clothes, broken bones pierced through his skin, and his long hair was in a wild mess; he looked like a fierce devil that had climbed out from a mountain of corpses!

And at the same time, the number of geniuses that Lin Ming slayed was also innumerable.

Their bodies fell in mountains, piling up between the shrine platforms and forming rivers of blood!

This battle had reached unprecedented levels of savagery!

Enemies lay in all directions. The proud children of heaven were without end!

Lin Ming’s slaughter energy soared to the heavens. He killed and killed, killing until those geniuses on the shrine platforms lost all courage. A portion of them only surrounded Lin Ming, not daring to move forwards. They had lost all their previous haughty demeanor.

However, Lin Ming’s condition was becoming increasingly worse. Luckily, he had his two avatars supporting him. When he joined forces with them, they cut down all the incoming elites, and those that died would have their heads blown apart, their spiritual seas sundered!

Lin Ming’s message was clear. Whoever wanted to kill him would have to pay the price. Even with the spirit medicines from Great Brahmic God Mountain, the destruction of their spiritual sea would likely leave behind invisible wounds.

“He’s too terrifying!”

The more everyone fought, the more horrified they became. They knew that Lin Ming couldn’t last forever, but even though he seemed completely exhausted he was still recklessly harvesting lives.

“Monster!”

The descendants from Chaos Divine Palace were left in a cold sweat. As for Yellow Springs Palace, they were in an even more miserable state. Of the original group of people they had brought here, only two were left.

This caused their originally pale faces to turn utterly white without a hint of blood. Their main form of combat was to release ghosts, but these ghosts were negated by the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. Not only were they negated, but they could even act as energy supplements to the Myriad Demon Karmic Wheel. It was because of this that Lin Ming had focused on them, causing them to die even quicker.

“Where did this human come from? The humans in the Soul World have never produced such a hero before.”

“We must eliminate this human as soon as possible, otherwise he will become a disaster upon our heads in the future!”

Many large influences had suffered major losses. But because they had an overwhelming advantage in numbers, none of them wanted to leave. Fallen God Mountain Range was originally a gathering spot for elites, and the ones Lin Ming killed so far were only the tip of the iceberg.

It was impossible for Lin Ming to kill them all.

As soon as he showed weakness he would be immediately eaten up by the tides of people!

The spiritas martial artists around Lin Ming were like giant wolves surrounding their prey. They wouldn’t attack together, but would instead constantly use up their prey’s strength until their prey fell over. Then, they would strike.

Peng!

Another peak Holy Lord martial artist from Great Brahmic God Mountain had their head pierced through by Lin Ming’s spear. The spear penetrated to the other side, the brain still attached to it. This martial artist was as dead as he could possibly be.

Following that, the spear point turned back and burst open the head.

But at the same time, another wound appeared on Lin Ming’s chest. Because the Asura scales had been ripped open, their protective effect was extremely limited, and even Lin Ming’s protective true essence had become extremely frail.

But in that moment, silence fell over the battlefield, as if time itself had frozen over.

Bursts of auspicious light gently fell down, illuminating the Fallen God Mountain Range.

Everyone was startled – what was happening?

They looked up to see a faint blue shadow appear in the distant highest heavens. This was a mind-boggling distance away from the Fallen God Mountain Range. In fact, one could say that this blue shadow was still in the starry space, but because it was too large, everyone was able to see it.

It was like a miniature planet.

The blue shadow approached at an incredible speed. As it flew forwards, everyone could hear the echoing screech of a phoenix.

This was clearly a phoenix God Beast!

“Deep Blue Ice Phoenix!”

Someone cried out in alarm. This was the phoenix with a royal sovereign’s bloodline flowing through it. It was far more powerful than an ordinary phoenix.

Everyone watched as the blue phoenix let loose a deep cry. The blue phoenix unfurled its two wings and stretched them out for over a thousand miles, blocking out the skies. Endless blue flames appeared everywhere. These flames carried with them an endless cold, the purest of the Ice Laws. Massive tracts of surrounding space began to freeze over.

In contrast to this terrifying cold energy, the freezing domain that Icydew used before was nothing but child’s play.

At this time, a dim blue figure could be seen standing above the ice phoenix’s back, tall and lofty as if she stood in the profound darkness of a star.

Beneath her feet, endless blue flames flowed out. Mystical Laws scattered out around her, and dao patterns circulated by her side, forming motes of ice that shimmered like stars.

She was like a fairy that descended from the highest heavens, elegant beyond mortal means and without equal.

As she flew forwards, mountains and rivers shined below her. Everything was covered in a sacred and halcyon halo of light.

Just this endless halo of light alone contained an incredible momentum that caused everyone’s heart to shiver.

“Soul… Soul Empress Sheng Mei!”

“It’s the Soul Empress!”

Someone cried out in bewilderment. For a time, all the elites that surrounded Lin Ming were left in a stunned daze.

Although this person’s appearance remained as hazy and unclear as before, the appearance of the Deep Blue Ice Phoenix and this unfathomable aura already revealed this person’s identity – that of Soul Empress Sheng Mei!

Some proud children of heaven had excited expressions cross their faces. Soul Empress Sheng Mei was a legend amongst the younger generation of the spiritas. She was the most beautiful existence below the heavens, heroic and invincible.

She had become an Empyrean long ago, and her cultivation far surpassed those of the same generation.

Many proud children of heaven regarded her as their lifetime’s goal and diligently cultivated to chase after her shadow. If they could only see one side of her face, that was enough to leave them incomparably excited.

“She is Soul Empress Sheng Mei? Is she here to attempt enlightenment? Or to kill Lin Muk?”

Some geniuses asked out loud, their voices shaking with elation.

“No matter what the reason, Lin Muk will die.”

“Yes, if the Soul Empress is here to grasp the principles, she might just conveniently kill Lin Muk. No one among the same generation can match the Soul Empress. However, this lowly human is lucky to be able to die under Soul Empress Sheng Mei’s hands.”

Chapter 1845 – Sheng Mei Arrives

Sheng Mei’s appearance left the many proud children of heaven dazed but also excited.

In particular, the most excited one of all was the Soul Rapture Holy Lands’ Jade Lifestone.

The Soul Rapture Holy Lands was far too large, and Jade Lifestone was a disciple not worthy of any special mention. The time that he had managed to luckily catch a glimpse of Sheng Mei was at a grand ceremony, and that had been from several hundred miles away.

Now that he saw Sheng Mei arrive with his own eyes and also at such a close distance, his cheeks turned red and he waved his hands.

“Soul Empress!”

With the Soul Empress here to help, Lin Ming would die without a doubt. As for the golden page, that would also end up in her hands.

Realizing this, the disciples from Great Brahmic God Mountain had ugly complexions. They didn’t believe that anyone on their side could hope to negotiate with Sheng Mei, but neither were they willing to give up on the golden page so easily.

The freezing enchantment that Icydew laid down existed only in name to Sheng Mei. From the far off distance in the starry skies, she simply took a step forwards and vanished, instantly reappearing within the center of the freezing enchantment, right in front of Lin Ming.

She wore a blue dress and a halo of light shrouded her body, making her seem mysterious and sacrosanct.

Because of the halo of light and the hazy mist that drifted around her, it was hard for the surrounding martial artists to see her face. They could only feel her sacred and potent aura, one that made them all wish to fall down in worship.

Everyone thought that Lin Ming would be immediately killed by Sheng Mei. After all, in front of Sheng Mei, Lin Ming was nothing but a little baby without any strength to resist.

“This brat is too lucky, to think he can die beneath the Soul Empress’ hands.”

“What kind of character is the Soul Empress? If she only came for the golden page then the Empress wouldn’t need to do anything at all. The lot of us are more than enough to kill Lin Ming!”

Jade Lifestone said. Many people nodded in agreement. How could they allow the Soul Empress to dirty her hands by killing such inferior human trash?

Although they would have to pay a considerable cost to kill Lin Ming, they were willing to do this for Sheng Mei.

For a time, more and more martial artists came to the Fallen God Mountain Range, eagerly approaching him, wanting to kill him. The presence of Sheng Mei was even better than the rewards announced by the youth from the Great Brahmic God Mountain.

Facing all of this, Lin Ming remained silent, only looking at Sheng Mei.

As for Sheng Mei, she also looked at Lin Ming. Her pupils were deep and a ghostly light bloomed within them, as if she were able to pierce through all the complexities of the human psyche.

Currently, Lin Ming was bathed in blood and innumerable scales were shattered. There was not a place left unscathed on his body and mountains of corpses and rivers of blood lay beneath him.

He was a death god of the battlefield!

And standing opposite Lin Ming was a graceful and elegant goddess, one that stood above the sins of the mortal world.

The smell of blood and death formed an incomparably stark contrast with the radiant beauty.

It was like Lin Ming and Sheng Mei represented two polar extremes of the martial arts world!

Time seemed to slow to a crawl. Two peerless geniuses in Lin Ming and Sheng Mei stared at each other. And all around, countless masters of the Soul World surrounded them. The shrine platforms were silent as the martial artists stood up in attention, mystical Law runes shimmering around.

Before this, Lin Ming never imagined he would meet Sheng Mei in such a situation.

“So it really was you.”

Sheng Mei said, her voice simple and charming. She didn’t pour any spirit essence into her words, but they were heard by all the martial artists at the quiet Fallen God Mountain Range.

“You finally came.” Lin Ming replied.

The two voices were clear. For a time, everyone was stunned.

Sheng Mei knew Lin Muk?

This Lin Muk was a bizarre character that had come from out of nowhere, but Sheng Mei knew who he was?

Thinking more carefully about it, everyone couldn’t help but acknowledge that Lin Muk’s talent had already reached incomprehensible levels.

He might even be no worse than Sheng Mei!

And these two peerless geniuses were old acquaintances?

Realizing this, many people were left speechless. Because Lin Ming was a human they had subconsciously considered him as coming from a lowly background, a weak and inferior sect. After all, he was nothing but a mere human.

As for these Soul World martial artists, including Jade Lifestone, when they faced Lin Ming they still felt an inborn sense of superiority even though their strength and talent were far worse.

This was because they were spiritas, because they came from large influences and were the proud elites of these influences.

As for Lin Ming, no one knew where he came from. They assumed he was a human boy who had managed to stumble into a mind-boggling lucky chance.

Thus, when facing Lin Ming, they looked at him like a rich noble living in a capital city would view a bumbling newly wealthy merchant from the countryside.

Even if these nobles weren’t as rich as these newly wealthy merchants, they would still despise the merchants for being lower class.

But now, Sheng Mei’s words left everyone dumbfounded.

This Lin Muk, just what was his deal? How could he know Sheng Mei? Could he have come from some top influence?

In the Soul World there clearly weren’t any great human influences. Could he have come from another universe?

Many people couldn’t figure out what the reason was.

And now, listening to Sheng Mei’s tone, although she didn’t place Lin Ming on the same status as her, he was at least worthy of her treating him earnestly. And Sheng Mei leaving seclusion and crossing countless miles to come all the way to the Fallen God Mountain Range was clearly in order to see Lin Ming.

On the other hand, everyone else, including the disciples from the Soul Rapture Holy Lands like Jade Lifestone, didn’t even enter Sheng Mei’s eyes. They didn’t even receive a greeting from her. This was also a reasonable matter. An emperor wouldn’t personally greet the poor, even if they were his own citizens.

Time slowly passed, Lin Ming’s wounds wriggled about as they slowly regenerated.

Because Lin Ming had used up too much energy, his wounds restored at a snail-slow speed. It was clear that his current condition was extremely poor.

Looking at Lin Ming’s wounds, Sheng Mei said in a quiet voice, “It seems you were waiting for me to see you all this time? However… your current situation isn’t good at all. If I was late by just a single step, I fear you would have died here. Losing the golden page is already a grave enough consequence, but even your true body would be targeted by the Great Brahmic God King. With the Great Brahmic God King’s strength, finding your true body wouldn’t be too hard at all. At that time, you wouldn’t be able to leave the Soul World alive.”

A faint victorious smile hung on Sheng Mei’s face.

Compared to Lin Ming, Sheng Mei was indeed a superior existence. This was because of the disparity in their backgrounds and the disparity in their strength, something that couldn’t be bridged so easily.

Moreover, Lin Ming needed Sheng Mei’s help.

“I might not have been able to keep the golden page, but I don’t think my true body would have had any problems.” Lin Ming calmly said. Even though he was in a disadvantageous position, he didn’t appear weak at all.

“Oh?” Sheng Mei remarked, surprised. “You still have the assurance to escape to the heavens, even when hunted down by a True Divinity?”

“I won’t sit and wait for death.”

Lin Ming also had an escape route, and that was to retreat into the Asura Road. He had the Asura Command and could return to the Asura Road with it. The only problem was that returning there wasn’t an easy task, and it required a long period of set-up time in which he couldn’t be disturbed during the process.

During this period of time, if Lin Ming was locked down by the sense of a True Divinity then the results could be imagined. Lin Ming didn’t doubt that a True Divinity possessed the ability to cross the void of a trillion quadrillion miles and affect his spiritual sea to remove his disguise.

“Your cultivation… seems to have fallen.”

Although Lin Ming could feel Sheng Mei’s terrifying aura, as he probed her soul sea more carefully, he discovered that her cultivation had fallen to the World King realm and she was no longer an early Empyrean. Even so, she still maintained the pressure of an Empyrean. The pressure she exuded also felt far more terrifying than any common Empyrean’s.

This was because she had completed the seventh revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art.

Through every revolution of the Grand Reincarnation Art, one’s cultivation would fall and their skeletal age would fall with it. The more thorough one’s reincarnation was, the larger the change would be.

“It will continue falling with time…” Sheng Mei confidently said. After completing the Grand Reincarnation Art’s seventh revolution, her cultivation would continue falling for the next year. The lower it fell, the better the effects would be.

And after that when Sheng Mei cultivated again, her cultivation speed would reach incredible degrees. It could even jump several boundaries in a few years.

“You came to the Soul World specifically to look for me?” Sheng Mei asked. Lin Ming had created such a large disturbance in the Akashic Dream Battlefield and had even written down the name Polar Ice Lin right next to hers. All of these signs indicated that he had come to the Soul World to look for her.

If Lin Ming couldn’t find Sheng Mei, then his only option was to have Sheng Mei find him instead.

“State your purpose. I know it’s impossible for you to come here to discuss old times, but… if you came here because of the war between humanity and the saints, and you think that humanity can ally with the spiritas, then I can only tell you that you have made this trip in vain. That is an impossible matter because doing so has no benefits for the spiritas.”

Sheng Mei’s words caused Lin Ming to frown. Although he already expected that negotiations wouldn’t progress smoothly, he didn’t think that Sheng Mei’s first words would nearly suffocate him to death and leave him with no room to argue.

Seeing Lin Ming’s expression, Sheng Mei confirmed her speculations. She sighed and said, “It seems I was right. Besides this, I can’t imagine any other reason you would come to the Soul World to seek me out. In order to come to the Soul World, you must have paid a deep price…”

The journey to cross the barriers of the 33 Heavens was extremely arduous unless there was a previous connection that was already established through the God Lamenting Wall. Otherwise, even Sheng Mei would find it almost impossible to pass through.

Lin Ming looked at Sheng Mei and Sheng Mei looked at Lin Ming. As their eyes met, they fell into an awkward silence.

Then, Lin Ming asked, “Are the spiritas not a match for the saints? The two races had a war erupt between them in the past, so why has that stopped now?”

Sheng Mei replied, “The spiritas and the saints truly do both wish to swallow the other, and there was a great war that erupted between them, but… this is a matter of the past. Now, because of some reasons, the war has momentarily been put on pause. The Good Fortune Saint Sovereign and the spiritas’ Soul Emperor have reached a temporary armistice. After the saints complete a certain matter they will begin their annihilation of humanity, and to them, exterminating humanity isn’t difficult at all. Depending on yourself… there is nothing you can do!”

Sheng Mei indifferently said. What she said was nothing but the facts. Compared to the saints, Lin Ming was far too weak.

“What is the reason for this armistice?” This was what concerned Lin Ming the most.

Sheng Mei refused to answer. “That involves the secrets of my race. I cannot tell you.”

Lin Ming’s complexion darkened. He took a deep breath and slowly said, “Then, what if I put out enough chips?”

“Mm?” Sheng Mei was surprised. She looked at Lin Ming, unable to imagine what chips he could put out.

Chapter 1848 – First Wood Page

Sheng Mei’s words caused Lin Ming’s thoughts to shake.

Exchanging golden pages was a condition that was more advantageous for Lin Ming. This was because Sheng Mei had already read through the replica of the golden pages, but Lin Ming hadn’t seen anything at all.

At this time, Sheng Mei gathered her hands together. Between her palms, golden rays of light began to shine out as a golden page seemingly spun from silk started to slowly appear.

As the people on the distant edges saw this, they all held their breath. For almost all of these people, this was their first time seeing a golden page.

“First wood, it is also the first of the golden pages.”

Sheng Mei faintly said.

Lin Ming’s golden page was the second wood page, and thus the second page, one directly connected to the first page.

If they could be linked together and studied from the start, the advantages would naturally be tremendous.

For Sheng Mei to take out the first wood page more than showed her sincerity.

Sheng Mei also said, “There are only 10 golden pages. But, the Spiritas Holy Scripture includes more than 10 golden pages. There are also many other things.”

As Sheng Mei spoke, the golden page had already fluttered into Lin Ming’s hands.

As for Lin Ming’s second wood golden page, he passed it to Sheng Mei.

The two people exchanged pages and started to meditate upon them.

Lin Ming sat on a shrine platform, his heart no longer thinking of anything else. His senses were focused and it was like the bells of nature were echoing in his ears, allowing him to meditate even more calmly.

The surrounding area seemed to have become a completely separate space, severed from the outside world.

In his hands, the golden page he had exchanged with Sheng Mei slowly fused into his inner world and spiritual sea, turning into countless motes of star-like light that surged within his divine soul.

His spiritual sea was filled with raging waves. In a deep trance, Lin Ming soon arrived in front of a pitch black mirage world.

The land he was in seemed to be made from nothingness, but if he touched anything, he could feel it was incomparably solid.

The chilling space was empty and filled with eerie mysteries.

In the far off void, countless people were covered in mystical halos, exuding endless light. They whispered in a low voice, their chants echoing through the air.

These verses were obscure; he couldn’t understand even a single word. But his flesh and his divine soul could feel a clear power emanating from them.

This was a mysterious feeling, one he could only sense but not explain.

This feeling allowed him to see many things, marvelous images passing through his eyes like grains of sand falling in a storm.

He saw a tree of heaven, its towering crown reaching high, piercing into the distance like a mountain and stabbing into the skies. This tree began to crackle and burn. Essence energy shot out and its life force was cut off. It crashed into the ground, reduced to ashes… after the wind and rain, the ashes of the great tree melted into the earth, vanishing without a trace.

He saw a boundless sea with fish dragons leaping and leviathans stretching out for 90,000 miles. The entire sea was lively and amazing. But in the blink of an eye, the skies filled with a sun-bright fire and the seawater evaporated. The sea became a mulberry field…

He saw vast planets with countless lives on them. Eagles screeched in the endless skies and tigers roared and wolves howled in the forests. There were bustling cities, adrift in the smoke and smells of a mortal world… but as the years passed, the sky began to break apart and the earth collapsed. Fire and water raged all around and the bustling world became one of terror and disasters, all life fading away in the chaos.

One after another, countless images wove together before him, manifesting and then being destroyed.

All the images exuded an icy cold death energy, endless bursts of destruction…

Lin Ming seemed to become a towering tree, a sea, a star. With incomparable clarity, he was able to sense how he was destroyed, how he died.

“Death… is just all things returning to their home…” Lin Ming sighed, his heart becoming even more desolate.

Endless scenes of death caused a certain feeling to percolate in Lin Ming’s mind.

With death, there was inevitably life. These were the two most important stages of life!

As this thought appeared, it became a cloud of smoke rising into the highest heavens, uncontainable.

Those figures chanting in the void were like suns. They began to emit a dazzlingly bright light that illuminated all directions.

Bang!

…From the towering tree of heaven that was burned down by the raging fires and reduced to ashes, those ashes began to nourish the earth. From where it collapsed, small seedlings appeared. Rain fell from the skies and strong winds helped it grow straight and tall. Blades of green grass grew, each one seeming lofty and filled with grandeur…

…From the dried sea, winds rose up. Thousands of rivers began to swell up from all directions, scouring the world left and right, slowly merging together into a boundless sea once more…

…From the center of the shattered planet, a nucleus began to form once more. For billions of years it gathered the spiritual power of the infinite universe, growing once more. The planet gradually expanded, and life began to appear on its surface…

Each scene was filled with inexhaustible bubbling vitality.

At this time, Lin Ming was a seed. He stretched out his limbs, absorbing nutrition from the ashes of the towering tree. He became a sapling and started to slowly grow.

He was a dry sea bed. From the deathly stillness, infinite water vapors began to gather, wetting the land once more.

He was a cold and lonely planet nucleus. Through billions of years of loneliness, he accumulated the thinly spread out spiritual essence of the universe, eventually giving birth to endless life forms…

From the infinite chanting, Lin Ming realized the experiences of life to death, from death to life. He became all things, repeating the cycle endlessly.

Again and again and again.

His heart went from desolate to vigorous, from vigorous to desolate, continually being tempered…

He suddenly understood. The texts that floated in his spiritual sea began to resonate with the endless chanting.

He became a blade of grass, as well as a towering tree.

He became a drop of water, as well as a vast sea.

He became a planet nucleus, as well as a giant planet.

He was everything, and everything was him.

“The universe is samsara, space and time are infinite…” Lin Ming silently read the simple texts, each word shining in his heart, floating in the void of his mind like stars.

Floating in his spiritual sea, the ancient texts of the golden page began to resonate with his words. The runes started to release a fervent cheer, becoming increasingly bright.

Although some texts still remained obscure and puzzling, the current Lin Ming had already comprehended the essential true meaning contained with the golden page that Sheng Mei had traded him.

The Asura Sutra that the Asura Road Master left behind could be said to speak about the ultimate Heavenly Dao that stood atop the 33 Heavens; it was the power of the universe.

Then, the golden pages left behind amongst the spiritas spoke about returning to one’s true origins.

I am the universe. I am the myriad of existence!

……….

On the shrine platforms nuzzled into the sheer cliffs, Soul Empress Sheng Mei was grasping enlightenment not too far away from Lin Ming.

The icy cold energy had frozen a thick ice wall a thousand feet around her. Strange runes flashed along them, making it impossible for others to see what was occurring inside.

As for the soul sea marks, from the moment Sheng Mei sat down on the shrine platform and started to perceive the second wood golden page, these soul sea marks also began to light up.

On the 100th day, the fourth soul sea mark had already started to emit a dim light.

On the cliff, some proud children of heaven from various races tittered in excitement upon seeing this.

“The Soul Empress is truly fierce. The last time she was here she lit up three soul sea marks in 108 days. Now, in just 100 days she is already able to have the fourth soul sea mark shine with a dim light. In time completely lighting it up will be no problem at all. Perhaps this time the Soul Empress really might be able to obtain the golden page from this Fallen God Mountain Range.”

“Of course. The last time the Soul Empress was here she had only completed her sixth revolution, but now she has completed her seventh. There is no comparing the her from back then to her now. Moreover, Lin Ming gave her the second wood golden page, making her even more powerful.”

Jade Lifestone smiled. As someone who was originally here at the Fallen God Mountain Range to attempt enlightenment, he naturally didn’t leave with those from Great Brahmic God Mountain. He stayed at the cliff to continue his enlightenment.

Soul Empress Sheng Mei came from the same Holy Land he did. If Sheng Mei was strong, that was also something he could be proud of.

However, as he glanced at Lin Ming, who was at a shrine platform not too far from her, a complex light filled his eyes.

This character Lin Ming was the same as an enigma. He made the heart race.

“This brat has a terrifying combat strength. I wonder how far he can go.”

Jade Lifestone didn’t dare to look down on Lin Ming’s background anymore.

Then, on Lin Ming’s lonely shrine platform, the light of the first soul sea mark began to shine.

Following that, the second and third soul sea marks lit up.

This meant that Lin Ming had finally finished perceiving the golden page and was beginning to grasp the Laws on the shrine platform.

The light was blinding, like a miniature sun rising. It was even brighter than Lin Ming’s previous attempt, and no worse than Sheng Mei’s.

The proud children of heaven found it hard to not pay attention to what was occurring.

Sheng Mei and Lin Ming, two peerless geniuses, had arrived at the Fallen God Mountain Range. Could they create a miracle here?

Chapter 1849 – Mysterious Woman

At this time, Lin Ming was like an ancient well on the shrine platform, calm and serene.

Although there were many things he was still unsure of, he had already become aware of the true meaning of the golden page Sheng Mei had traded him. Now, he only needed time to slowly verify the truths within the golden page and master it.

However, just comprehending the true meaning of the golden page alone gave Lin Ming many benefits.

Soul force surged like a tide within his body, washing through him without end and making him feel as if he were being reborn.

Without stop, he began to rapidly grasp the principles atop the shrine platform.

He knew that as long as he obtained more golden pages and verified them with each other, it would be much easier to master them.

Luckily, this fleeting feeling had appeared.

Within his divine soul, the texts of the two golden pages resonated with each other, emitting clarion sounds of nature that sobered Lin Ming’s mind.

After another day passed, the fourth soul sea mark smoothly lit up.

But after that, comprehending anything further became increasingly difficult.

The dark shrine platform was shrouded in a great power that emitted an endless mystical strength.

Not knowing when, Lin Ming discovered that he seemed to have stepped onto some narrow winding path. There was nothing but haze around him. He couldn’t make out his surroundings nor where he needed to go.

Within this misty haze, he was like a lonely boat in a pitch black sea, helpless and lost, floating quietly in the world.

Even the sparkling lights in front of him that had exuded mysterious sounds had disappeared. It was like he had been completely cut off from the outside world.

“This feeling is…”

Lin Ming’s thoughts tightened. If he couldn’t escape from this strange maze, then the following comprehensions would be increasingly difficult.

To grasp the principles of the shrine platforms of the Fallen God Mountain Range was an incredibly arduous task. Since ancient times, countless spiritas martial artists had attempted to gain enlightenment here, but all of them had been defeated one after another. This included even young True Divinities!

Thus, some people even suspected that the rules of the world had already been blocked here. No one should be able to obtain any results.

Although Lin Ming believed in himself, he didn’t think he was stronger than those spiritas True Divinities when they were young.

Nearing the bottleneck, Lin Ming became increasingly cautious.

At this time, within Lin Ming’s mind, he tried to recall some contents of the first and second wood golden pages.

The true meaning of the golden pages that he had comprehended began to shine like stars, emitting the sound of the Great Dao from within him like a great bell that thundered in his mind.

The surrounding thick mist dispersed and the black sea vanished.

In front of him, another road appeared. It was simple and plain, leading to some point in the endless horizon, as if it led to the past, as if it led to the infinite possible futures…

Lin Ming’s eyes brightened. Another bizarre roar sounded out in his head. After obtaining some comprehensions, the world suddenly fell black once more.

The endless mist covered him again, hindering him from taking even a single step forwards.

“How should I keep walking down the road?” Lin Ming pondered. He tried sensing the existence of the world around him. His comprehensions of the golden pages also became increasingly profound.

But, the fifth soul sea mark was like an endless moat that blocked his way, an obstacle that he would never be able to surmount.

As Lin Ming fell into a torpor, not too far away from him on another shrine platform, Soul Empress Sheng Mei was silently meditating.

Waves of sky-blue light from the Great Dao emanated from her. But, the fifth soul sea mark still didn’t light up.

To grasp the principles atop the shrine platform was an extremely long process. It wasn’t something that one could complete in 100-200 days. There were even people who stayed for 10 or more years at a time.

Even for the likes of Lin Ming and Sheng Mei, wanting to take away the golden page here was an extremely difficult task.

Time passed a day at a time.

Lin Ming and Sheng Mei were like statues, completely motionless. Their soul forces had reached unbelievably profound levels. For many people, sitting on the shrine platforms in meditation for a few dozen days would exhaust their soul force, but to Lin Ming and Sheng Mei this wasn’t any problem at all.

This was because they knew how to conform to the world Laws here and conserve their soul force. At the same time, their restorative abilities were incredible.

In this aspect, Sheng Mei was far more powerful than Lin Ming. Lin Ming might not compare with Sheng Mei, but because he possessed the Magic Cube his soul had similarities with the Eternal Soul and the stability of his soul was extraordinary.

“How terrifying. They have already sat there for 10 months without moving. From the looks of it, they can sit there for several years without any problem at all.”

“Lighting up the fifth soul sea is difficult beyond compare… even Soul Empress Sheng Mei won’t find it easy…”

“That Lin Muk is also stranded at the fifth soul sea mark. Nothing’s happened for quite some time…”

“Although this human brat is strong, his strength lies in the essence gathering system. In gaining enlightenment atop the shrine platform, it is impossible for him to compare with the Soul Empress. I think that… the Soul Empress will light the fifth soul sea mark soon…” Someone quietly spoke, afraid of disturbing Sheng Mei.

On the shrine platform, Lin Ming was still struggling with his thoughts.

In front of him was a vast wilderness flooded with endless fog.

He could not see where the road was.

He walked alone. Beneath him were blue stones, just like the blue stone road he once walked upon at the Asura Road’s final trial.

“Every golden page is connected to the others, but their true meanings are all greatly different… the reason my enlightenment here was so fast at the start was because of my previous experiences and also because I have comprehended the true meaning of two golden pages. After the start, the difficulty suddenly increased. My background was also used up in the first part of grasping the principles.”

Lin Ming mumbled to himself.

At this time, a voice echoed in his ears. “Eh? Someone’s here carving characters on the stone.”

Lin Ming was startled. This voice was clearly from the red-dressed little girl that had always been following him.

He turned his head and saw that in his sea of consciousness, the red-dressed little girl was sitting around. Her eyes were bright and wide and she struggled to see through the hazy fog before her. Her pupils shimmered with a strange light, as if she could see through the thick fog.

“What did you say? Someone’s carving characters?” Lin Ming’s heart quickened. He didn’t ask how this little girl appeared in the world of his consciousness. It seemed as long as something involved soul force or the mind, there was nothing that could block this red-dressed little girl.

What he cared the most about was that on this blue stone road, there was someone else here that he couldn’t see.

This was clearly because the road in front of him was covered by some strange strength. Lin Ming was completely unable to see through the source of this strength, but the red-dressed little girl was. Her origins were a puzzle, making one feel her very existence was inconceivable.

“Mm, it’s a pretty aunty. She’s using her finger to write on the blue stone…”

A woman?

Lin Ming was bewildered. Who could this person be?

“What is she writing?”

Lin Ming asked. The red-dressed little girl’s large eyes widened as she blinked again and again. Then she whispered, “They are v-very complex characters; I don’t understand them at all. But this aunty… I… f-feel she’s familiar…”

The red-dressed little girl said, lost in her thoughts.

Lin Ming’s heart skipped a beat. Familiar?

He simply had no idea what status this red-dressed little girl had. And who was this woman that was carving characters? Could they be mother and daughter?

And what were the characters that the woman was carving?

“That aunty is starting to draw pictures. There are water currents… people… planets… people on the planets… small blades of grass, soil, fire…”

The red-dressed little girl said without end. These images weren’t connected at all. As Lin Ming heard them, he was still left puzzled.

Thus, he decided to calm his mind and use his eyes to look as hard as he could at the blue stones on the side of the road.

However, as he stared unblinkingly at these blue stones, he felt his eyes hurt as if a biting wind was tearing into them.

The blue stones emitted a light that stabbed into his eyes like countless golden needles.

Lin Ming had a feeling that what the woman carved down were Laws.

Everything within the heavens and earth followed the Laws of the universe; life was no exception.

The red-dressed little girl stood beside Lin Ming, occasionally speaking. Lin Ming firmly remembered every word she said.

Lin Ming continued watching, always watching. Even though his eyes had become bloodshot, he never relaxed.

And then one day, he could see the blurry shadow of a person standing beside the blue stones.

Long hair. Blue clothes. This person emitted a terrifying aura.

This was indeed a woman, a woman that caused Lin Ming’s heart to race. Her long hair fell down her back like the river of time, making one lose themselves in a daze just by looking at her.

He was unable to distinguish what boundary this woman had reached. He only saw her quietly pace around the blue stones. Sometimes she would be deep in thought, and sometimes she would lower her head and carve some things into the blue stones.

As if she were finishing a piece of art.

Lin Ming stiffened, unable to move. He could confirm that this woman wasn’t just some illusion. An aura exuded from her, one that seemed like the endless flow of time. It was a familiar feeling, one he had felt back in the final trial and at Tragic Death Valley. This was a terrifying aura of the endless years, one that came from over 10 billion years ago. He couldn’t follow it nor could he sense the point from which it originated.

“This is a phantom left behind from 10 billion years ago?”

Lin Ming thought out loud. This aura had been preserved until now, even after such a mind-boggling period of time had passed. It left Lin Ming feeling fearful and apprehensive.

What sort of woman was this? Perhaps, the scene that the red-dressed little girl saw was that of the Akashic Dream Universe being formed, and the images that the woman carved down were the Laws that were recorded in this world. This was the best explanation he could find.

It was even possible that this woman was the one who had created the enlightenment shrine platforms of the Fallen God Mountain Range.

However… the one to create the shrine platforms, shouldn’t that person be the creator of the Holy Scripture?

In a dreamland, Lin Ming had seen the creator of the Holy Scripture twice already. He was also the person who had battled the Asura Road Master in the past. Although Lin Ming had only glanced at him, he could confirm that this person was a man.

What was going on here?

Lin Ming felt his thoughts turn chaotic. The characters from 10 billion years ago and their relations were a complete riddle to him. He couldn’t help but turn his head and look at the red-dressed little girl. This little girl might also be a character that existed 10 billion years ago, otherwise why would she feel that this woman was familiar?

If this were true, then what role did she play in the past? Why would she fall asleep for so long? Why would she still exist? Why would there not be such a strong aura of endless years emanating from her body?

Countless puzzles ran through his mind. But currently, he didn’t have time to think about these matters. He looked towards the woman’s hand, trying to see what she was carving. However, the writings shined with a mystical light, making Lin Ming unable to see them clearly.

Chapter 1850 – Eye

“Just what are these carvings?”

Lin Ming anxiously thought. His eyes stung with a torturous pain. Looking at this divine light was like being stabbed with needles.

This continued for some time. Lin Ming’s eyes had turned blood red; he was at his limit.

Looking straight at these runes carved by an ancient peerless character, this was an extreme test on Lin Ming’s soul force.

In the next moment, Lin Ming’s body shook and blood flowed from his eyes.

He fell to the ground, propping himself up on his knees as he continued watching the woman write.

“Brother Lin, d-d-don’t look, your eyes are bleeding… if y-y-you continue to watch your eyes will collapse…”

The red-dressed little girl panicked as she saw Lin Ming’s horrible appearance, and as she panicked she began to stutter again.

“I’m fine…”

Lin Ming waved his hand, not caring at all about the problems with his eyes.

“B-but…” The red-dressed little girl was concerned about Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s heart warmed. He remembered that the little girl said he had a nice familiar smell coming from him, and it was because of this that she was attached to him. Ever since coming out from the Akashic Dream Battlefield, she had continued to follow him.

Lin Ming looked at the little girl, a gentle light in his eyes. “I don’t know your name, and you probably don’t know it either. Would it be alright if I call you Ruby from now on?”

The little girl tilted her head, nodding, seeming to be a little excited. “S-sure.”

“Mm… well, Ruby, I’m fine…”

Lin Ming grit his teeth, continuing to look at the mysterious woman’s writing.

He focused all of his concentration on what she was writing, ignoring the blood dripping down from his eyes.

He didn’t have much time remaining. The war between the saints and humanity would erupt in just several dozen more years. He couldn’t just watch helplessly on the sidelines as everything and everyone he cared for was annihilated.

And now, in this brief period of time, even though he was cooperating with Sheng Mei he was afraid that he wouldn’t be able to fulfill her conditions. This was because one of them was to have him find the path to cultivating the Law of Eternal Life, and for Lin Ming this was impossible – unless he offered up the Magic Cube!

If so, then all Lin Ming could do was increase his strength as far as possible. He had a faint guess that if he could combine the Heavenly Sutra and Holy Scripture together, achieving perfection of within and without, simultaneously cultivating the universe of his body with the universe of the world to the limit, he would be able to reach an inconceivable boundary. Maybe with this he would be able to have his own strength rise drastically in a short period of time, enough so that he could help resist the great calamity.

Of course, he feared this so-called short period of time was likely far more than several dozen years…

Even so, Lin Ming had to try his best to obtain a golden page!

If Sheng Mei obtained the golden page of the Fallen God Mountain Range then there wouldn’t be anything for Lin Ming. But if he were to obtain it, he could use it to trade for another golden page with Sheng Mei. That was equal to obtaining two.

Then, Lin Ming would have four golden pages.

Although it was impossible for Lin Ming to perceive the entirety of the Holy Scripture through four golden pages alone, his hopes would be much greater than before.

He clenched his teeth, not blinking his eyes even as he overdrew on his soul force.

At this time, in the outside world, Lin Ming’s body was also undergoing a severe response.

“That Lin Muk, his eyes are bleeding...”

Several people noticed Lin Ming’s situation and were at a loss for words. Many martial artists would overuse their soul force when they tried to grasp the principles, and they would pale and be forced to withdraw.

But this Lin Ming persisted until he bled from the eyes; this was the first time they had heard of someone going this far.

“His soul force is unstable as if he’s consumed a great deal of energy. He is clearly overdrawing his soul force.”

“I’m speechless. If he doesn’t draw back now and continues to forcefully continue, is there any meaning to it…”

“Grasping the principles on the shrine platform is only something that everyone attempts; there is no hope to actually become thoroughly enlightened. At this Fallen God Mountain Range, it has been countless years since anyone has comprehended anything. Even the several True Divinities of the Soul World came here during their youth but returned without any benefits, yet this human boy is actually pushing himself this far. It seems he really is an idiot.”

Someone said with an amused, gloating expression. In truth, to many people, even someone like Soul Empress Sheng Mei would find it near impossible to obtain the golden page of the Fallen God Mountain Range.

For better or worse, Sheng Mei still had a thread of hope. At least, one of her die-hard fans like Jade Lifestone believed she would be able to succeed.

“He’s bleeding from the nose now…”

Some people glanced at each other in dismay and some people laughed. Many of them had smiles of schadenfreude.

Not only were they repulsed by Lin Ming, they were also jealous of him.

Their background was the number one race of the universe – the spiritas. Yet, they couldn’t compare with a human. This left them feeling uncomfortable in their hearts. But now as they saw Lin Ming end up like this, they felt much better as if they had vented a good deal of their frustrations.

How could a mere human think of obtaining the inheritances of their soul race?

“He has only lit up the fourth soul sea mark, but to completely grasp the principles of the shrine platform one has to light up seven soul sea marks. The disparity is incredible. Does he really think he can attain complete enlightenment in a single go?”

“I think this boy might have gone mad…”

Some people laughed.

They looked at Lin Ming and then looked at Sheng Mei.

Sheng Mei was still as calm as before. Her slender eyebrows were only slightly pushed together, but as for Lin Ming, he had ended up in such a state. The difference between them was far too great. Moreover, as time passed and Sheng Mei lit up more soul sea marks, the disparity would only increase.

Perhaps Lin Ming wouldn’t even be able to light up the fifth soul sea mark.

……………..

“The beautiful aunty is drawing a fish…”

Ruby suddenly said. Every time she saw the mysterious woman draw something she could speak out what she saw. Ruby saw all of this easily, as if she were watching someone draw lines in sand. As for Lin Ming, he couldn’t see anything no matter how much he struggled.

“Fish… rivers… the rhythm of the Dao…”

Lin Ming felt as if the mysterious woman’s hand had been thrust into the infinite river of time. It was impossible for him to clearly see it.

He persisted past his limits. His eyes were covered with blood and he nearly became blind.

The mysterious woman lightly stepped about like a celestial goddess. She sat down on a blue stone, every movement and every action she took filled with the aura and rhythm of the Laws.

She seemed to be deep in thought. Her endlessly long hair hung down like the curtain of night, concealing her appearance, making it impossible for anyone to see her.

After an unknown period of time she stood up and began drawing again.

“She’s drawing an eye!”

Ruby said. No matter what the mysterious woman did, nothing could hinder her from seeing.

“Eye…”

Lin Ming’s field of vision had already turned crimson. The figure of the mysterious woman blurred in his eyes.

Then, the mysterious woman turned around and glanced at Lin Ming.

Lin Ming’s body shook; he spat out a mouthful of blood!

He fell to his knees, feeling an incomparable burning heat between his eyes.

“Eyes…”

Lin Ming grit his teeth and bit his lips until they bled. Even his consciousness seemed to become blurry. But, he summoned the final dregs of his strength and watched the blue stone beneath the woman’s hands.

He could faintly feel that success wasn’t too far away. As long as he could persist just a little longer, there would be clarity!

However, what worried Lin Ming was that at this time he could no longer see anything at all.

Everything in his eyes was blood red!

He approached unconsciousness. But just as he was about to fall over, he didn’t know why but within his field of vision, he could faintly see an eye!

Rather, it should be said that this eye was an image that directly imprinted itself into his mind, thrust there without passing through his own two eyes.

Lin Ming could feel an agonizing ache between his eyebrows. Faintly, it was like a little bit of starlight gathered in this space, converging towards the point between Lin Ming’s eyebrows.

Hum - ! Hum - ! Hum - !

The world trembled. This world of consciousness seemed to tear apart and endless starlight fell down. In the skies, nine stars appeared high in the air, all of them burning like scorching hot suns.

Infinite starlight fell down like a river of stars.

Lin Ming experienced a splitting headache, as if his head would be forcefully cut off by this starlight!

“This is…”

Lin Ming clearly felt that between his eyebrows, there was a burning heat that felt like it would melt away his skull. But endless starlight gathered there, slowly forming a Dao Palace!

“Daevic Eye? Daevic Eye Dao Palace?”

Lin Ming’s heart shook. Of the Nine Stars of the Dao Palace, this was the Celestial Eye Dao Palace!

This Dao Palace didn’t have any specific striking power, but once opened, it would directly enhance a martial artist’s divine sense, so that they could spy upon the secrets of heaven and see through the infinite mysteries!

“I actually accidentally opened a Dao Palace…”

Lin Ming muttered, gasping for breath. His forehead was covered with blood, but within this thick blood, a mystical eye seemed to flash.

Previously, when Lin Ming opened the Purple Temple Dao Palace, Heavenly Retribution Dao Palace, and Extreme Polar Dao Palace, he had relied on gathering numerous spirit medicines to accomplish those feats, but this time in opening the Daevic Eye Dao Palace, Lin Ming simply relied upon his own strength and accumulations to forcefully open it.

Chapter 1851A – Moon and Star Struggle For Brilliance

Whether it was martial artists, mortals, or perhaps even animals, there was a natural hollow between their eyebrows where the third eye was hidden. This third eye had already degenerated into the brain, and was known by some as the upper dantian; this was also the daevic eye.

If one could open their daevic eye, they could gain the power to see through all mysteries and obtain an unparalleled perception.

But currently, Lin Ming’s daevic eye had just opened and was still bleeding. He hadn’t thoroughly opened it, but had just barely managed to. It was naturally impossible for him to see through all matters, but he could hazily make out the hand of the mysterious woman.

The moment that the woman’s fingers fell upon the blue stone, the surrounding Heavenly Dao Laws gathered unto her, combining with the power of life and turning into runes that carved themselves into the blue stones.

With her fingers as the pen, with the Laws as the ink, everything this woman drew seemed to be alive.

Flowers, plants, insects, birds, beasts, everything was lifelike. Even rocks and rubble, or even the simplest words were brimming over with life. The mysterious woman’s two hands seemed to grant all dead things a spirituality of their own, filling them with an impossible vitality.

Lin Ming even had a feeling that as long as the mysterious woman blew upon the designs she drew, they would jump to life. Like the mythical brush of god, everything she drew seemed as if it would become reality.

Lin Ming consumed a massive amount of soul force. Still, he continued to persist and read the Laws that the woman wrote down.

He felt that everything the mysterious woman carved down was something that always seemed to fall through his fingers.

The disparity in their boundaries was just far too great, so great that even just looking at the mysterious woman draw caused him to overdraw his soul force and find it difficult to continue.

“There’s no point in being too greedy.”

Lin Ming suddenly awoke to this point. This woman carved down far too many Laws. Every blue stone had marks she left behind, and these marks all contained inherent Laws. Although they all interpreted life itself, every interpretation held a different meaning.

If Lin Ming wanted to comprehend the meaning of all these Laws, a situation would appear where everything would fall beyond his reach.

After realizing this, Lin Ming calmed his mind. Then, he focused all his attention on the pattern that the mysterious woman just drew.

This pattern was in the shape of a raindrop, only the size of a mung bean. Compared to the previous carvings such as the flowers and beasts, this design was extremely simple. It consisted of only several strokes and the mysterious woman only took a few breaths of time to complete it.

Even so, this simple image revealed extraordinary meanings.

Lin Ming stared at this raindrop, completely immersing his every thought into it, going into a trance-like state.

In a dreamy haze, he saw the raindrop divide into two, two divide to four, four divide to eight, continuing on and on, becoming increasingly crowded until it was a pall of rain that stretched out without end. Within the cloud, faint arcs of lightning flashed, like silver snakes flying through the air. It was a mesmerizing scene.

Such a scene left Lin Ming utterly immersed within it.

Rain, was the convergence of water vapors from all longs. Its life was to grow in clouds high in the skies, and its death was to fall onto the earth, fall into the sea, and return to the world…

Its life was extremely short. A single drop of rainwater was also insignificant.

But the endless rainwater nourished all things. It nourished life. Flowers and birds, insects and beasts, all thrived because of rain!

A single drawing of a raindrop seemed simple, but it contained a Concept of Endlessness. As Lin Ming slowly felt the infinite mysterious within, he forgot the passage of time.

His soul force was constantly being used up, but the Concept of Endlessness subtly nourished his spiritual sea. Within his originally depleted spiritual sea, drops of rain seemed to appear, each drop made of incomparably pure source soul force. Through the revitalization of this rain, Lin Ming felt his own energy begin to fill back up.

Such a change manifested its effects on Lin Ming’s body.

His pale complexion slowly became ruddy. However, the blood that flowed from his eyes and ears still stained his face, making him seem fierce.

“This brat, he seems to have managed to live through it?”

Many people were surprised. Under ordinary circumstances there would occasionally be martial artists who appeared on the shrine platforms that overreached past their limits, causing their situation to become increasingly worse until they fell over.

Lin Ming clearly wasn’t able to last much longer, but color had suddenly returned to his face. Something strange was happening.

“This is just the final radiance of a setting sun. Watch, he’ll collapse soon enough. Originally, all of us came here for the experience without any hopes of gaining harvests, but this boy is truly a rare creature. He isn’t a fellow spiritas and he also excels in the essence gathering system, yet he came waddling over here with thoughts of the inheritance that our spiritas ancestors left behind. In this great world all strange sights are possible.”

“Especially with his current appearance. He was just bleeding heavily from his head just now. I really think he might be drunk…”

Several people loudly laughed. But at this time, someone cried out.

“What’s happening, Empress Sheng Mei is also…”

With this shout, everyone turned their attention away from Lin Ming and towards Sheng Mei. Sheng Mei was the most outstanding elite of the spiritas and also the leading character of all those who came here to attempt enlightenment.

They were left panic-stricken by what they saw.

Sheng Mei’s current situation wasn’t good either.

The hazy soul force around her body became increasingly unstable as if it could dissipate at any moment. The color had disappeared from her beautiful face and it was clear she had consumed a massive amount of soul force.

“Empress!”

Some people nervously cried out. They were all admirers of Sheng Mei.

“Do not disturb the Empress!”

Jade Lifestone shouted out loud. On the Fallen God Mountain Range, a martial artist would spend the majority of their time in rest. After all, there was a limited number of shrine platforms. Ever since Jade Lifestone saw Sheng Mei arrive, he hadn’t spent much time trying to grasp the principles, but instead spent the majority of his time focused on her current state. Now that something was happening to her, he immediately noticed it.

After almost an entire year, this was the first time that Sheng Mei’s soul force seemed to weaken. To use one’s soul force to gain enlightenment was risky to begin with and Jade Lifestone didn’t allow anyone to disturb him during this process. Now that some minor phenomena were occurring under unknown circumstances, he naturally couldn’t allow anyone to disturb her either.

“Even a peerless existence like Empress Sheng Mei whose talent defies the heavens, will also encounter a situation where her soul force weakens?”

People began to think. As they looked at the increasingly ruddy Lin Ming, they felt this strange. Just what was Sheng Mei experiencing?

“The Empress possesses a potent soul force, but she likely consumed a great deal of it too…”

Someone began to say, voicing everyone’s thoughts. But at this time, around Sheng Mei, a dim halo appeared. This halo grew larger and larger, spreading out like waves.

Seeing this, everyone on the cliff began to fidget with excitement. This was…

Hu - !

The light completely diffused outwards. Fog wound around Sheng Mei’s shrine platform. The fifth soul sea mark had lit up!

“Empress Sheng Mei has lit up the fifth soul sea! It’s only been one year!”

In truth, for the martial artists who visited the shrine platforms, many of them had already lit up their fifth soul sea marks.

In fact, many of those proud children of heaven that were currently here had already lit up their fifth soul seas.

But, they often had to spend five years or more before the soul sea marks emitted the dimmest of lights, like a candle flickering in a storm.

No one managed to accomplish this as fast as Sheng Mei nor were their soul sea marks as bright as Sheng Mei’s. Her soul sea mark was like a brilliant boom, emitting a holy and enchanting light.

“Truly worthy of being the Soul Empress. Even though she seemed to be overdrawing her soul force, that was a critical moment in grasping the principles, thus the reason for her appearance. Still, she managed to break through that hurdle.”

Some people heavily praised. To light the fifth soul sea so quickly caused many people to think that this time, Sheng Mei really might be able to obtain the golden page of the Fallen God Mountain Range.

But the possibility wasn’t too high. For time immemorial, countless people had tried and failed, including even young True Divinities.

The impossible difficulty of grasping the principles on the shrine platforms had become firmly rooted in the hearts of the people.

As these people were speaking, behind them, another dim halo spread out, rippling like waves.

“Mm!?”

Everyone was shocked. They turned and were amazed to see that not too far away, Lin Ming’s shrine platform was emitting a faint light like a lighthouse in the dark sea.

“It’s Lin Muk!”

“He also lit up the fifth soul sea mark? How is this possible!?”

“Also within a year! He’s comparable to Empress Sheng Mei!”

Watching these ripples of light grow increasingly large and dense, everyone was so shocked their jaws nearly hit the ground. With this phenomenon occurring, they could confirm that Lin Ming had also lit up the fifth soul sea mark!

“Why would this happen? He’s clearly a human so why would he be able to comprehend our spiritas inheritances?”

People glanced at each other with dread, unable to say a single word.

Many of them also felt a deep sense of frustration and despondence. In truth, the reason they endlessly mocked Lin Ming and hoped that he would falter was because they were afraid of him. They were afraid he would really manage to comprehend something here and would cast them all away.

This was because in terms of combat strength and talent, Lin Ming already left them all in the dust. At the same boundary he was easily able to roll over them all!

As the top spiritas youths of their universe, they always held a certain pride in their innermost feelings.

They acknowledged that they couldn’t defeat Lin Ming in battle, but at the very least in terms of soul force and mental power, they wouldn’t be worse than he was.

But the reality they were shown made them a joke.

This was just like a go master playing against a chess master. They would play go first and even after a single move they realized they would fail and lose 100% to Lin Ming.

But even after trying to play chess, they discovered that even in chess they fell far behind Lin Ming, and extremely far behind at that.

Unable to win even in their own specialty, this could be called being trampled to the ground. Just what kind of proud children of heaven were they? Compared to Lin Ming they were just a joke!

These people didn’t know that the truth was the creator of the Holy Scripture wasn’t the ancestor of the spiritas. And, the inheritance he left behind belonged to all life, to those who possessed the ability to take it. It had nothing to do with any race!

Chapter 1851B – Life and Death

At this time, the outstanding spiritas elites on the Fallen God Mountain Range all had ugly complexions, as if their parents had died in front of them.

In particular, those that mocked Lin Ming and said he was forcing himself had burning red faces. Even though they still wanted to mock Lin Ming, the facts were laid out in front of them. Rather than smacking themselves in the face again they decided to simply shut up.

“This Lin Muk, is it really the first time he came to the Fallen God Mountain Range!?”

Someone asked in hushed whispers. However, before he finished speaking, an even more unbelievable matter occurred.

The halo of light around Lin Ming grew increasingly bright, overlapped again and again as it diffused outwards. First it seemed like ripples, then it seemed like surging waves. Wave after wave, even the surrounding space for hundreds of feet was affected. Faintly, a blinding radiance shot up into the skies from around Lin Ming’s head, filling the world with a brilliant luster. It was like a star was shining, leaving everyone shocked to the extreme.

This sort of phenomenon even surpassed Sheng Mei’s!

Sheng Mei’s light was like a bright full moon, but Lin Ming’s light was like a blazing star. Every person produced different phenomena as they tried to grasp the principles on the shrine platforms. This was because every martial artist comprehended different Laws on the shrine platforms. No martial artist could comprehend the complete Laws of the Holy Scripture, but only a tiny part of them.

According to the difficulty of this part of the Laws, as well as different levels of comprehensions, various phenomena could occur that differentiated the strong and the weak.

But now, if one had to ask if Lin Ming’s phenomenon was greater or Sheng Mei’s phenomenon was greater, everyone would have to say that the light radiating off of Lin Ming’s shrine platform was a bit more dazzling!

“Empress Sheng Mei actually cannot compare with this Lin Muk?”

Many people felt as if they were living in a dream. Although Soul Empress Sheng Mei was only at her seventh revolution and still had a tremendous capacity for future growth, who could say that Lin Ming also didn’t have equal potential?

“Stop speaking nonsense! Empress Sheng Mei lit the fifth soul sea mark first, and phenomena cannot be differentiated based on how bright the light is! How can we hope to understand Laws of such complexity?”

Many of Sheng Mei’s diehard supporters argued. They weren’t willing to believe that Lin Ming had surpassed Sheng Mei.

And at this time, whether it was Lin Ming or Sheng Mei, neither person knew what was happening in the outside world.

Trying to grasp the principles was like climbing a thin ladder to the heavens. It was an endless and lonely path.

Their minds were completely focused, without the least bit of distraction.

After lighting the fifth soul sea mark, the journey to light the sixth soul sea mark would be long indeed.

Lin Ming was like an ancient tree rooted in rock, standing solid and steady on the ground.

Sheng Mei was like a lake without wind or waves, incomparably quiet and peaceful.

The phenomenon that Sheng Mei saw was different from what Lin Ming saw. She forcefully relied on her incredible talent and her understandings of life and the soul to seek out a path in that dense fog.

But as for Lin Ming, he was always staring at the image of a raindrop. He looked at this small raindrop day after day in a trance-like state.

It was only when he felt that he had comprehended everything he could from this raindrop image, and that the other Laws were impossible to understand even if he could see them, that he slowly stopped.

And as he shifted his eyes, Lin Ming discovered that the mysterious woman had already disappeared.

Moreover, this part of the world had grown dim, as if a pall of dark clouds covered this land.

“Senior has disappeared…”

Lin Ming said with some regret. As the mysterious woman vanished, the Laws she left behind also vanished. The innumerable Laws she carved down were all incomparably exquisite, containing endless mysteries within them. If one could copy them and bring them outside, then any single one would be a top miracle treasure. Even True Divinity Holy Lands would regard them as priceless treasures that would be passed down as core inheritances.

However, even though Lin Ming had fallen into a mountain of treasures, the treasures he had managed to take away were limited. He had only become aware of the raindrop diagram and even then he hadn’t completely grasped it.

It could only be said that the difference in boundaries was far too great. Lin Ming still had a long road ahead of him.

As Lin Ming regretted that he wasn’t able to comprehend more things, the skies became increasingly dark. Black clouds overlapped and a ghostly fog rolled towards him.

The blue stones were covered by this darkness. They slowly lost their blue luster and began to turn as black as ink.

The blue stones turned to black stones.

The black stones were quiet and plain. As Lin Ming looked at them, he didn’t know why but he felt that they were all like tombstones.

This was an extremely bizarre feeling. Moreover, this world was clearly filled with an unspeakably suppressive atmosphere.

Thick black fog filled the air, completely shrouding the world. Once again, Lin Ming couldn’t see the road ahead of him.

Lin Ming’s thoughts stirred. He revolved the Daevic Eye Dao Palace, wanting to see through this thick fog.

However, layers of hazy death energy filled the heavens and earth, covering the point between Lin Ming’s eyebrows and making it so that his daevic eye wasn’t as keen.

Lin Ming could feel the point between his eyebrows be covered in a mass of black energy. To be described by a fortune teller, Lin Ming’s forehead had gone black.

“The daevic eye can’t see through this...”

Lin Ming took a deep breath. He faintly felt that what flooded his surroundings was the Concept of Death.

If a life was born, death naturally followed.

Death, was the home which all life returned to.

There was no life that could live forever. Even a great race had their prosperity and decline. Even a universe was born and eventually destroyed.

If one could rid themselves of death… then that was the legendary Law of Eternal Life. But… even the creator of the Holy Scripture wasn’t able to perfectly summarize the Law of Eternal Life.

In this situation, all life had to experience the concept of death, and this was also the most important part of life. This was because for all lives, the time they were alive was insignificant compared to the time they were dead.

“But how do I comprehend the Concept of Death?”

Comprehending death was far more difficult than comprehending life. This was because Lin Ming was a living being to begin with, so understanding life was easier for him. It was impossible for Lin Ming to commit suicide to experience death.

As all sorts of thoughts were racing through Lin Ming’s mind, a red light flashed and Ruby appeared beside him. She said, “Brother Lin, t-t-t-there’s some people there…”

Ruby pointed towards the black fog. Lin Ming couldn’t see through it at all.

“What sort of people?” Lin Ming asked, startled.

“Many… many people. They all look different. Some have wings. Some have horns. Some have tails. And some don’t even look like people but look like fierce beasts or strange beasts. They are all crawling out from the ground beneath the black stones.”

“Crawling out from beneath the black stones?” Lin Ming’s mind chilled. That was the same as crawling out from a grave. No wonder he had felt that these black stones were similar to tombstones.

Yet even now, Lin Ming couldn’t see these figures that Ruby spoke of.

“Ah…” Ruby gasped.

“What is it?” Lin Ming hurriedly asked.

“They… they are being killed. Someone’s killing them. That… that person is… so scary. They are holding a scythe in one hand and a black book in the other…”

“Scythe? Black book?” Lin Ming’s thoughts raced. These two things caused him to think of legendary depictions of the god of death.

In particular, that black book caused Lin Ming to form even more associations.

He remembered that in the ancient ruins within the Akashic Dream Battlefield, in the great battle between the Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture, the creator of the Holy Scripture had been holding a black book in his hands.

“What kind of book is it? Is this person a man or a woman?”

“A black book. There’s a blood red pattern upon it. A man…”

Ruby rapidly breathed out. For some reason after this black figure with his black book appeared, she felt a deep sense of unease swell within her.

Lin Ming could already confirm that the black book Ruby spoke of was likely the black book he had seen in the ancient ruins within the Akashic Dream Battlefield.

If so, then was this person the creator of the Holy Scripture?

Then who was the mysterious woman from before?

Lin Ming’s thoughts became increasingly tangled. Were there two creators of the Holy Scripture?

Without a doubt, the black figure that Ruby saw was more similar to the creator of the Holy Scripture that he had seen in the ancient battlefield ruins. At the very least they were both men.

“Black book. Are they really golden pages?”

Before this, Lin Ming had always believed that the golden pages were parts of the Holy Scripture that had fallen down. And, the portions that had been collected and organized together formed the Spiritas Holy Scripture that was in the hands of the Soul Emperor. But now, it seemed that he had been mistaken.

In fact, just thinking about it a little more carefully, the golden pages were far too large. When they were fully unfolded they were the size of a small kasya; they just didn’t seem like pages at all. Moreover, there were only 10 golden pages. If one had to form a book with them, then this book would be far too large and far too thin.

“Unfortunately, I cannot see the form of this killer and I also don’t know what the appearance of this mysterious black book wielder is like…”

Lin Ming revolved the daevic eye but was still completely unable to pierce through the black fog. The mysterious death energy was even able to cover up the vision of his daevic eye.

He was faintly aware that after comprehending the raindrop diagram, he had likely lit up the fifth soul sea mark. But what followed after that was the sixth soul sea mark!

The fifth soul sea mark was life and the sixth soul sea mark was death!

At this point, Lin Ming felt that grasping the principles on the shrine platform was no longer as simple as obtaining a golden page from the Fallen God Mountain Range.

This was a chance! A turning point that allowed him to peep into the Law inheritances of the Holy Scripture’s creator!

Thinking of this, Lin Ming sucked in a deep breath and became increasingly excited.

The Asura Road Master and the creator of the Holy Scripture were two peerless characters that existed 10 billion years ago. But, the two of them walked down completely divergent roads of martial arts.

One focused within, one focused without – if he could simultaneously obtain the inheritances of these two peerless powerhouses and cultivate the outside and inside worlds, just what boundaries would he reach?

If he could fuse the two together then his future achievements would be unimaginable!

He might even surpass the Asura Road Master and surpass the creator of the Holy Scripture, establishing a new boundary that had never been reached before!

Realizing this, Lin Ming was increasingly sure that the shrine platforms on the Fallen God Mountain Range were in truth a rich trove of inheritances and also a massive lucky chance. However, wanting to obtain any enlightenment from here was far, far too difficult. Since ancient times, countless spiritas elites had attempted to grasp the principles here, but they had all returned with nothing.

Because so many people failed over the years, many people arrived here with thoughts of only ‘giving it a try’ and believed that not comprehending anything here wouldn’t be a loss at all. The simply didn’t think about obtaining the golden page and only wanted to come here and take a brief look around.

In fact, many people believed that it wasn’t suitable to cultivate here for a long period of time because the Laws were chaotic. But, they didn’t realize that it was because of these chaotic Laws that they couldn’t comprehend anything.